Chapter 849: A Use of the Underworld’s Dark Mist

The Great Demon King gawked, then he nodded and said, “Mister, you don’t need to worry. I will be waiting for your word.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then that’s great. We need to take Holy Light City, that will be our first foothold in the Divine Realm.”

The Demon Dragon King smiled, “We have two Domain Weapons, taking Holy Light City shouldn’t be a problem. Mister shouldn’t worry about it.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “I hope so. Before, when we waged war with the Divine Race, we didn’t really have so much understanding about the inner works of the Divine Race. Although we had killed a lot of them, they weren’t really high level members of their society. However, Fei’er told me that the city has a defensive formation and a lot of magic cannons guarding it. We need to deal with these things carefully.”

The Demon Dragon King had followed Zhao Hai these days, naturally he knew about things, so he nodded. The Great Demon King was himself a clever man, he didn’t need further explanation as he said, “Mister, rest assured. When the time comes, I certainly won’t hold back.” Zhao Hai nodded. At this time, the dishes that the Demons prepared was also delivered. One has to recognize that although the Demons didn’t have a lot, their food still had flavor that was different compared to the Ark Continent.

After having eaten their meal, Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space’s villa. Then Zhao Hai inspected the processing machine. The timer was still going on, everything was normal. Then after that, Zhao Hai looked at the situation of the spatial rift’s defense, everything was also good. Then Zhao Hai changed the monitor to show the Atlanta Plane, he wanted to see what was going on there.

The Atlanta continent was still on the process of preparation. Zhao Hai saw plenty of things that they took care of. Besides military cargo, there were also items that Zhao Hai couldn’t recognize. Some looked like magic armor parts and some seem to be the power source needed by the magic armors.

Zhao Hai discovered that the energy used by the magic armors was called energy crystal by the Atlanta continent’s people. However, Zhao Hai has not yet figured out what this energy crystal was. But it should be more or less like Zhao Hai’s crystal stones.

Zhao Hai’s surveillance centered on Axe. But after this fellow went back to the family and attended the conference, he didn’t do anything else. This caused Zhao Hai to be unable to see much further into magic armors.

After seeing the state of the Atlanta Plane, Zhao Hai reckoned they would need a few months before they can invade. This enables Zhao Hai to have some time to breathe.

While Zhao Hai was looking at the monitor, Cai’er flew towards Zhao Hai. She was carrying a map on her hands and stretched it out, “Young Master, look. This is the Demon Realm’s map.”

Zhao Hai looked at the map and said, “We mapped it this quickly? Good good. I’ll give this to the Great Demon King. Then we’ll take our iron armor beasts to open up mines in the Demon Realm.”

After Zhao Hai gave the map to the Great Demon King, the Great Demon King immediately marked the ore deposits of the Demon Realm. Zhao Hai took the map back to the villa and immediately made Cai’er send the iron armor beasts to mine the ores.

One has to recognize how suitable the iron armor beasts were to mining. Their digging speed was very fast. Not even stone can stop their advance.

Moreover, these iron armor beasts weren’t low level anymore. This caused them to have more wisdom. At this point, they didn’t need a Dwarf guiding them in order to dig for ores.

The number of iron beasts in the space was quite a lot. In addition to being sent to the Demon Realm, ZHao Hai also sent a lot of them to mine in the Ark Continent. There were still some untapped mines back there. Zhao Hai used to mine with his undead, however, their mining speed was not ideal. Zhao Hai only remembered about the iron beasts quite recently. With how fast the beasts were in mining, Zhao Hai had to recognize that they were indeed born to excavate.

After handling these matters, Zhao Hai discovered that the skies had turned bright. After a few more hours, it would be the opportune time to attack Holy Light City. Since there were still some mystery about the Divine Race being routed, Zhao Hai and the others need to attack Holy Light City. This would allow them to see whether the Divine Race were planning to lure them or they were just having trouble with defending.

Since there was still time left, Zhao Hai took the chance to look into the state of the Beastman Prairie. The situation wasn’t looking great. At this point, the underworld had covered 80 percent of the prairie.

The speed of the dark mist was very fast. Suddenly, Zhao Hai had a thought. Didn’t the hell background had a dark mist similar to the underworld? If this was the case, then can he use the underworld’s dark mist to upgrade the hell background?

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai couldn’t sit still. He immediately opened a rift and drew some dark mist into the Space.

After the underworld’s dark mist entered, a prompt was suddenly heard, “Darkness attribute poison mist detected. Has aggressive properties. Has benefits towards darkness lifeforms and robots. Can improve hell background.”

Zhao Hai laughed, he didn’t expect his idea to actually work. This was great news.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that getting any more dark mist was useless. It’s effects can only be gained on the first absorption.

But this was still good. If the dark mist was useful for the hell background, then wouldn’t other things in the underworld be useful as well? If that was the case, then going to the underworld would have to be placed on the list.

After taking care of the dark mist, Zhao Hai discovered that the time was almost up. Zhao Hai switched the monitor off and then went to the Demon Space. The Demons were currently very busy. After all, they had just entered the Space, they still had plenty of things to take care of.

However, after the Great Demon King heard the situation from the Demon Dragon King, he didn’t rest that evening and just took care of the matters of the Demon Race. At the very least, he had assigned people to various tasks.

Fortunately, taking care of things came quite easy because of the Space’s environment. The Demons didn’t need to worry about food and drink, this allowed them to focus on constructing their own homes.

When Zhao Hai arrived in the Demon Space, the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King had almost finished their matters. Then Zhao Hai asked the Great Demon King to arrange the Devil Legion to the spatial rift where the defensive line was being rebuilt by the undead.

Currently the Devil Legion wasn’t very strong, so Zhao Hai couldn’t bear to let them enter the battlefield. Zhao Hai believed that the potential of this army was immeasurable.

Zhao Hai can cultivate powerful people in the Space. However, trained people who hadn’t killed before will have limited performance during a fight. On the other hand, the Devil Legion were people brought up by mountains of corpses and seas of blood. Although their strength was low and couldn’t express great fighting prowess, their potential was very high. Once they have  the power, no person in the Space would be able to face them.

For Zhao Hai, the Devil Legion was a treasure, so having them fight at this time would be a waste. Because of this, he didn’t have the Devil Legion participate in the upcoming fight. After the Devil Legion grows stronger, only then can they display their might.

People could experience rapid promotion, but their mental states couldn’t be trained quickly. After they go to the battlefield, they may panic or even go crazy. The Devil Legion didn’t have this problem. They had already fought many battles and had withstood the pressure of killing. What they lack right now was strength. But with Zhao Hai as their backer, it would be only need a short time before this issue is solved.

After taking care of the Devil Legion, Zhao Hai led the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King into the Divine Realm. At the same time, Fei’er and the other had just eaten their meals.

After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Fei’er and the others immediately went to greet them. But upon seeing the Devil’s Chariot, their faces couldn’t help but change. They could feel that the chariot was yet another Domain Weapon.

At this point, Zhao Hai already had his blood ghost staff. This was the weapon he was most comfortable with. He had handed it over to the Great Demon King before, now he had taken it back.

After Zhao Hai saw Fei’er and the others arrived, he smiled faintly and let go of the staff. The staff flew out front and then formed into a huge platform. In this platform, there were furnitures and other things such as teacups and pots. Whether it be furniture or utensils, all of them had a red translucent appearance, they looked quite attractive.

This startled Fei’er and the others once more. Fei’er had been with the Divine race for some time. But he hadn’t seen nor heard of an artifact capable of doing this.

Zhao Hai beckoned his hand and then said, “Come toward the platform. Let’s sit and have a talk.” Then he led the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King to sit. At the same time, Fei’er and the others looked at the platform and also stepped on it.

When the group had sat down, Zhao Hai took out some tea leaves and began to soak it with water in the teapot. After having settled, Zhao Hai gestured to the Great Demon King and said, “This is the Lord of the Demon Realm, the Great Demon King. I asked His Majesty today to help us break through Holy Light City. With two Domain Weapons, we should be able to take the city with ease.”

Fei’er frowned and said, “Mister, the ship you used yesterday was quite strong. If you take that ship out, then wouldn’t we be able to take the city in a blink of an eye?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and replied, “I also wanted to use it. However, I can’t right now. I discovered a weak point on the ship when I used it yesterday, so I decided to refine it once more. I won’t be able to use it while it’s being upgraded. If we want to use that ship, then we would need to wait for a couple of days.”

Chapter 850: Domain Weapon vs Domain Weapon!

Although Zhao Hai just blurted those words out like it was nothing, Fei’er and the others comprehended something else. In their opinion, the ship was already the world’s most powerful weapon. However, such a weapon actually had a weak point in Zhao Hai’s eyes. Moreover, he was even proceeding to upgrade it!

They looked at each other and saw the color of surprise on their eyes. However, Fei’er still kept his calm as he said, “That is also good. I believe that with two domain weapons, there would be no problems in taking the city. We’ve also sent people to contact our races. We’ve given them five days to return. Even if they have troubles, they can still see our situation and then return. But if they don’t return in five days, then we can assume that an accident has happened.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then let’s start taking over Holy Light City.”

The group nodded before they left the platform to command their army, only the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King remained. Currently, the Devil Legion was already guarding the defensive line. However, the undead were still going on with their work.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and then smiled before taking out a spatial bag and giving it to the Great Demon King. Then he said, “Your Majesty, after you head back to the Demon Space, give this to your people. This way, they’ll have a way to message you whenever they need it.”

The Great Demon King looked into the spatial bag and saw a lot of messenger fish bottles, numbering way more than ten thousand. The Great Demon King immediately looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Mister, thank you very much. This will be very useful for us.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “At present, the messenger fishes have limited functions. Later on when we improve it, you can use the messenger fish to contact many people.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “Its state right now is still very good. With them, my life would be much easier.”

The Demon Dragon King smiled as well and said, “It surely will. Sending letters is sometimes very inconvenient. With the messenger fish, everything would be more convenient.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll give some to Fei’er and the others as well. But not too many, just enough for them to command their army more efficiently. After all, they’re still our allies.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King laughed. At this time, Zhao Hai’s platform slowly moved forward. Following the platform was the undead army. The Barbarian, Winged Pegasus, and Thunder Clan were also following closely behind. Their advance was slow, but in turn, they maintained a solid formation.

Although the army’s advance wasn’t quick, they were also quite close to Holy Light City. Before long, Zhao Hai could see a huge city in the horizon.

The city was huge, enough for more than 20 million people to settle in. It’s walls reached a height of over a hundred meters, and panning about a thousand li(500km). It was bigger than the cities of ancient china by many folds.

Such a city can only appear in a world with magic, it was impossible for it to exist back on Earth.

At this time, the entire Holy Light City was surrounded by a layer of translucent light. They had already erected their formation and was ready to meet Zhao Hai’s attack.

Zhao Hai slowly stood up and walked to the edge of the platform. He gazed at the city and exclaimed, “It’s majestic. I’m afraid it’s much bigger than your capital, Your Majesty. I didn’t expect huge cities like these to exist in the Divine Realm.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King also stood up and went to either side of Zhao Hai to look at Holy Light City. The Great Demon King exclaimed in surprise as well, “It’s truly grand. No city in the Demon Realm and Ark Continent could compare to this one. I’m afraid only the Divines can make it. It seems like there are some truths to the greatness of the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Their claim to be gods seems to hold some truth. However, they shouldn’t have provoked me. Even if they are gods, they still wouldn’t escape my revenge.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King both laughed. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai was joking, he did have the strength to back his words.

As they got closer to Holy Light city, the view got clearer and clearer. On the walls of the city were Divine Race soldiers. The walls were very wide, allowing more than soldiers to be occupied on top of it. Magic cannons and ballistas used to defend the city were also on the walls, ready to fire a full salvo when the fight starts.

Zhao Hai’s platform stopped, causing the entire alliance army to stop as well. Their position was beyond the range of both magic cannons and ballista so they weren’t worried of any attacks coming their way.

Then Zhao Hai had his platform move around the city. Holy Light City was indeed really good. The walls were made of stone and looked very tough.

After some time, Zhao Hai returned to his original position. At this time, Fei’er, Yue, and Shan had arrived at the platform. The three people didn’t show their surprise, they were already used to seeing it.

Zhao Hai gave a spatial bag to each of them and telling them about the messenger fish. After that, he asked them, “What is Holy Light city’s status in the Taurus Continent? Is it a big city in the Divine Realm?”

Fei’er was very happy upon receiving the messenger fish, and when he heard Zhao Hai, he immediately placed the bag aside and answered, “There aren’t a lot of cities as big as Holy Light City in the Taurus Continent, only ten. As for its ranking, it’s about at rank five. Shan, did I remember it correctly?”

Shan shook his head and said, “If I can remember, Holy Light City is 4th biggest in the Taurus Continent. Their biggest is Divine Will City, then Divine Purpose City, Divine Light City after that, fourth is Holy Light City, and fifth is Holy Earth City. Then the next five is Sacred Artifact City, Divine Scripture City, Divine Grace City, Taurus Holy City, and Holy Sea City.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “What ranking is this based on? Is it by area or population?”

Fei’er nodded and said, “It’s calculated based on both land area and population. The Taurus Continent’s biggest city, Divine Will City, is said to be the place where the Deity first appeared. Therefore, it held great significance to the Taurus Continent. It’s area is about twice as large as Holy Light City, but the population is roughly the same.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s really amazing how they are able to make cities that big. Imagine the resources they needed to use.”

Fei’er smiled bitterly and said, “The Divine Race spent a lot of manpower and materials in order to further expand their cities over the years. I even heard that when they conquered the Ark Continent, they would proceed to do their expansion once more. They would gather several people from the different planes to help them expand their cities.”

Zhao Hai’s expression turned cold, “They would use this method to exhaust the strength of our planes. So even if we want to resist them, then it would be impossible.”

Fei’er sullenly nodded and said, “If not for this, we wouldn’t have been anxious in rebelling. If we don’t rebel, then we would be weakened forever. Actually, our move is too hasty, we weren’t even able to make proper preparations. However, we don’t have any other choice other than to make a move.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he smiled faintly and then said, “However, the Divines didn’t expect to encounter a problem in the Ark Continent. In their minds, they thought that the Ark Continent didn’t have any God-ranks. As long as they change the laws of the plane, then it would be very easy to conquer the continent.”

Fei’er and the others kept silent. They themselves knew that what Zhao Hai said was the truth since this was what they thought as well.

Zhao Hai looked at the time and then gave a nod. He looked at the others and then said, “It’s time. Prepare the army. Your Majesty, Demon Dragon, it’s time to show your strength. As long as you deal with the shield, then everything can be left to us. Fei’er, you and the others go back and wait for my signal.” The group nodded and went on to prepare. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai stayed on the platform and stayed still. At this time, Demon Dragon and the Great Demon King returned to their carriages and then supported their Domains. The Demon Dragon King established his Black Dragon Domain, then the dragon’s clawed hand grasped the sword chariot before throwing himself towards Holy Light City.

On the other hand, the Great Demon King’s Domain was a giant devil. After his Domain turned into a giant, he grasped on the chains of the devil’s chariot, turning the chariot into a large morningstar. After that, he also soared towards Holy Light City.

Those at Holy Light City didn’t expect Zhao Hai to send two Domain Weapons after them. They thought Zhao Hai would use his magic cannons and javelins so they were very eager to teach him a lesson. Unfortunately for them, their plans had become useless.

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King arrived outside Holy Light City. They were completely unaffected by the magic cannons and the arrows. Demon Dragon held his sword and swung straight towards the city. The Great Demon King did the same thing with his morningstar.

Both attacks smashed towards the city, however the translucent shield just trembled slightly. It seems like the two attacks didn’t affect the shield.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry. Although the two attacks seem to have no effect, Zhao Hai can sense the shield weakening, it’s power has been reduced by a lot. Zhao Hai believed that with a few more attacks the shield of the city will be broken through.

Zhao Hai also discovered that the Domain Weapons were able to block both the magic cannons and the ballista. Naturally, this was because Domain weapons were higher levelled items compared to the magic cannons and ballistas. Moreover, they reinforced one’s Domain, this allowed the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King to almost ignore all of the attacks from Holy Light City.

Just as Zhao Hai thought about how easy it would be for the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King to break through, two figures suddenly appeared from Holy Light City. These two figures were two knight type Domains. Moreover, these two Domains held two spears in their hands.

The appearance of these two people made Zhao Hai stare. He didn’t think that the Divine Race would prepare two Domain Weapons to deal with him.

In fact, Zhao Hai didn’t know, but just like what Demon Dragon said, the Divine Race were prepared in dealing with Zhao Hai. They took the people from the town and villages into Holy Light City while arranging two Domain Weapons in the spatial right. However, Lu Wei suddenly gave word that he wanted to personally deal with Zhao Hai. Because of this, the Divine Race changed their plan and relocated the two Domain Weapons to Holy Light City. They believed that with Lu Wei present, the two Domain Weapons wouldn’t need to be used.

Unfortunately, Lu Wei failed, causing Zhao Hai to continue his advance towards Holy Light City after routing the army. This caused them to be caught off guard.

Fortunately, the two Domain Weapons were stationed in the City. This caused the city to have some form of resistance. With the two Domain Weapons, Zhao Hai should be dealt with.

But unexpectedly, Zhao Hai’s side had two Domain Weapons as well. This caused the two Domain Weapon experts to make a move ahead of time. These two were initially meant to deal with Zhao Hai, first they were relocated by Lu Wei, and now they have to deal with the two Demon experts. Their purpose had been driven back once more.

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King similarly didn’t expect that the enemy would have two Domain Weapon experts. But since the two of them were veterans in battle, they immediately went and fought the enemies two on two.

Both the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King were peak existences in the Demon Realm, nobody was stronger than them when it came to battles. For them to reach their current level meant that they were extremely rich with battle experience.

Similarly, those bearing Domain Weapons in the Divine Realm were elites of their clans who had fought in many battles. This fight had turned into an intense battle. There was no clear winner between two sides.

From what Zhao Hai saw, the Great Demon King held an advantage against his enemy while the Demon Dragon King was falling behind. Deciding this battle in a short period of time would be impossible.

Chapter 851: Second Improvement?

Zhao Hai understood why the Demon Dragon King was at a disadvantage. This was because the Demon Dragon King had just acquired his Domain Weapon. Therefore, he wasn’t as skilled in handling it as his opponent. On the other hand, the Great Demon King had his devil’s chariot for a long time, causing him to be comfortable when using it.

Zhao Hai wanted to see if there were more Domain Weapon experts left in Holy Light City. But after looking for some time, it seems like there were no other experts waiting inside.

At this time, Fei’er and the others arrived by Zhao Hai’s side. They were looking at the fight with an ugly expression.

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “What’s wrong? Worried that they’ll lose?”

Fei’er shook his head and said, “From what I can see, it seems like the fight couldn’t be finished quickly. I’m not worried that the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King would lose, but this is not good for our plan. With no Domain Weapons available, we won’t be able to pierce the city in  a short time.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, let’s just stay here for some time. Besides, aren’t we waiting for your messengers to come back? Let’s just observe the Divine Race for some time.” When he heard this, Fei’er couldn’t help but stare. Then he quickly understood what Zhao Hai meant. They would tussle with the Divine Race while waiting for the messengers to come back. If they went on to capture Holy Light city right now, then they would definitely be met with the Divine Race’s counterattack. In this case, the Divine Race might block their troops from coming over.

Time is what they need right now, not Holy Light City. And just waiting outside the city works for them since Zhao Hai will be providing the supplies. They won’t need any outpost nor supply chains. Where Zhao Hai was is where their base is located.

Fei’er nodded and then he asked, “Mister, when can you use your ship?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Fei’er and smiled, “Rest assured, it’ll be done soon.”

Fei’er didn’t say anything else. He knew that Zhao Hai had a great hatred with the Divine Race. He definitely won’t make them feel any better.

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were still fighting with the two Divine Race experts. Zhao Hai didn’t stop them nor did he attack the city. It seems like he was just waiting for the fight to end.

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King had already been fighting for two hours. Nobody can help them. Everyone present understood that this fight would take a few days before some result can be seen.

Both sides drew back, they knew that there was no point in battling it out at this time. Zhao Hai saw this happening and then waved his hand. Behind him a bell sound has been heard. This was a signal for the army to retreat.

After hearing this sound, the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King immediately made a slow retreat. At the same time, the two Divine Race experts didn’t chase them and instead headed back to Holy Light City.

The two Divine Race experts knew about Zhao Hai’s strength. If Zhao Hai attacks Holy Light City, then he might take it. However, Zhao Hai would still lose a lot. It was because of this that the two Divine Race experts weren’t afraid. They knew that Zhao Hai couldn’t lose too much people, or else he would be finished. This was accentuated by the fact that Zhao Hai only sent the Domain Weapon experts to attack, he wanted to break the city in one go. But now that those two experts were blocked, Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t let his ordinary army attack.

The Great Demon King Demon Dragon King retreated to Zhao Hai’s platform. Both of them had ashamed expressions as they made a salute to Zhao Hai, then the Great Demon King said, “Mister, we have disappointed you.”

Zhao Hai looked at them and laughed, “It’s fine, the other side also had two experts, I can see that. Let me tell you about my plan. I want to stay here in Holy Light City for a few days. What do you think?” The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King had rich experience in battle, so when they heard Zhao Hai, their eyes immediately shone. The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, you mean you want to drag time?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Yes. Your Majesty, there’s no need to go all out in the fight. Your life is valuable, it’s not worth it to expend all your energy. Just tussle with those experts for a few days. I’ll take care of the rest.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King laughed as well. On the other hand, Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but force a smile. They knew that those Domain Weapon Experts of the Divine Race weren’t ordinary people.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “Alright, let’s end today with this. After we retreat, go back and take a rest. Let’s see if Holy Light City dares to sneak an attack. If they come, I’ll personally give them a lesson.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “I think they won’t come. They know that we have Domain Weapons. It would be foolish for them to attack.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s true. Alright, everyone go and take a rest. Don’t attack in the next few days. We aren’t capturing the city, we’re only delaying for time. Conserve your strength so when the time comes we won’t have any mishaps.”

Fei’er and the others nodded before they turned around and left. After they left, the Demon Dragon King immediately said, “Mister, I’m very sorry for disappointing you.” Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Dragon King and smiled, “It’s fine, I’m not disappointed at all. You just obtained the sword chariot so you aren’t very familiar with it. Don’t put it to heart.”

The Great Demon King also comforted, “Demon Dragon, don’t let it get to you. You had just obtained your Domain Weapon. Being able to wield it like you did was already quite a surprise. I remember the first time I obtained my devil’s chariot, it took me a long time before I could use it comfortably.”

At this time, Zhao Hai can hear a prompt, “Universal Processing Machine has come out with a supplementary design. Needs host’s confirmation to proceed with the improvement. Can use crystallization ability to improve the item’s armor as well as increase the cannons’ aggressiveness.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he turned to the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King before he said, “Your Majesty, Demon Dragon. I’m afraid I’ll have to leave you here. I have a small matter to process. Please take the time to take a rest.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King didn’t ask Zhao Hai what his matter was. They just nodded and turned around to head towards their carriages while Zhao Hai’s figure appeared on the Space.

Laura and the others were also in front of the processing machine. They don’t know what just happened but they could understand that it was related to the Hell King’s ship.

After seeing Zhao Hai come, they immediately made way. Zhao Hai looked at the processing machine and into the image of the ship. He discovered that there was an additional description shown there.

Zhao Hai selected the description and saw the image of the ship change. The entire Hell King’s ship had turned into a ship made out of transparent crystals. It still had its eighteen story deck and 9 cabins. On both sides were cannons that totalled to 162. Below the cabin was another deck, Zhao Hai can see that the yin-yang pool has been moved to this deck.

After seeing this design, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. It was truly good. Zhao Hai looked at the whole ship again, the yin-yang pool still powered the whole ship, like a reactor providing energy to the whole structure. This pool can also absorb energy from outside, no matter what source, it would take it in.

The ship was now covered with this unknown crystal. It made the ship more sturdy, almost to the point of being invincible.

At the same time, the cannons looked more interesting as well. The cannons can emit energy beams that are much stronger than a God-rank expert. As for how strong it was? Zhao Hai couldn’t wait to try it out.

This ship had many designs unique to the immortal cultivation world. It can fly in the sky, run on land, swim in the water, and even drill underground.

Besides these, it can also change it shape into big or small with no changes to its speed. Most importantly, the ship had absorbed some abilities from the Space. The entire ship except the topmost which was reserved for Zhao Hai, are fully enclosed decks and cabins. They can be loaded with both people and undead, 100 thousand people or ten million undead!

Chapter 852: How to Deal With the Divine Race?

Zhao Hai wondered why there was a huge disparity between the amount of people and undead being loaded to the ship. Upon thinking about it, people would need rooms to stay, therefore, the Space would allocate bigger spaces for them. On the other hand, the undead were different. It was just like buses, if you don’t care for comfort, then you could place more people inside than the amount prescribed.

Such a design might be good, but it held no significance to Zhao Hai. He has the Space, so he didn’t need to think about loading people on the ship. But no matter what, this design was still quite good.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai wanted to see how much it would cost to upgrade the ship once more. If it was several millions of gold coins, then Zhao Hai was afraid that he would definitely go broke this time.

But after he looked at it, Zhao Hai felt great happiness. The upgrade was actually free! He can just directly confirm and it would add 12 hours to the overall production time. Without hesitation, Zhao Hai pressed confirm.

After waiting for Zhao Hai, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what happened?” Then Zhao Hai told them about the second improvement to the Hell King’s ship. This caused them to be happy, after all, the more formidable the ship was, the better it would be for them.

Once the group returned to the villa, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, are you really planning to spend a few days fighting the Divine Race?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Why not. Let the Divines be happy right now. But after Fei’er’s people arrive, then we can deal with the Divine Race. And as long as the Hell King’s ship is completed, I can deal with them quickly.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “We can afford to wait a few days. The underworld and the Atlanta Plane has no immediate threat to us. We can just focus on dealing with the Taurus Divines. Right, did the past few days have any effect on Fei’er and the others?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s great if there’s some effects, that is exactly what I want to see..”

Lizzy and the others stared, at this time Megan opened her mouth and asked, “Brother Hai, what do you mean? Do you want to receive Fei’er and the others to the Space?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Why not? If their people lost too much, then wouldn’t it be easier for us to take them to the Space? In any case, we have so many backgrounds, it wouldn’t be bad if they were to migrate.”

Laura and the others chuckled. At this time, Cai’er arrived by Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, the God-rank potions are done. Will we be sending them to the Ark Space?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go and deliver them.” The ten God-rank potions have been made, but they were yet to be given to the people of the Ark Continent.

These ten potions were going to be distributed according to Green’s arrangement. Each race would have two bottles. Although the Humans had several big Empires, they can still be considered to be one group, so they only had two bottles to share among themselves.

Zhao Hai already thought about it. After the races had enough God-ranks, he will take them out of the Space and have them participate in the battles to let their strengths improve as soon as possible.

The delivery of the potion went by smoothly. Now that the power of the Space has been proven, the people’s attitude towards Zhao Hai had undergone a fundamental change. Part of it was due to the broadcasts while some were caused by the Space.

After handing the potions over, Zhao Hai came out of the Space. Then he had his staff turn into a platform and just stayed there, looking at Holy Light City’s direction.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also wanted to see the plants in the Divine Realm. The place had plenty of fauna, majority of them were better versions of the ones in the Ark Continent. After Zhao Hai sent the those to the Space, there was no prompt. It seems like the Space still classified them as the same plants.

Also, after the plants of the Ark Continent were taken to the Space, they themselves had been upgraded. It might even be possible that they were better than those in the Divine Realm. So it wasn’t a surprise that there was no prompt from the Space.

Before long, the Demon Dragon King and Great Demon King arrived at Zhao Hai’s platform. They looked at Zhao Hai staring into the distance and the looked at each other. They didn’t know what Zhao Hai was doing.

At this time, Demon Dragon opened his mouth and said, “Mister, did something happen? What’s wrong?” Zhao Hai turned his head to the two of them and then said, “Nothing, I was just looking at the Divine Race and then thought about the Ark Continent. Your Majesty, Demon Dragon, how do you think we should treat the commoners of the Divine Race?”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King gawked. Then they found out that they too were unable to reply. If they were to decide, then they would just kill all of them. But after listening to Zhao Hai, they thought that it not all of the Divines were cruel enough.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and smiled bitterly, “To be honest, I was thinking of killing them all. However,  I found out that I couldn’t bear being as cruel as the Divines. Those commoners also had things they were good at.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King were stuck not knowing what to say. After some time, Demon Dragon said, “How about turning them into slaves?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly. To be honest, if he were to turn them into slaves, then he might as well kill them all. Zhao Hai was a person born in the modern age, he had a strong dislike towards slavery.

Demon Dragon saw that Zhao Hai doesn’t agree to this idea. He was then again stuck with not knowing what to say. There were too many Divines, dealing with them would be too difficult.

After some time, Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Forget it, let’s just wait until that time comes. The two of you still need to work hard tomorrow. Go challenge them and just drag it on for another day. Let’s wait for my ship to be done and then we’ll deal with the city.”

The two nodded, then the Great Demon King looked at Holy Light City and said, “The Divines have been used to being overbearing these years. It’s time to teach them a good lesson.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Being overbearing is no good, sooner of later, they would collapse. Alright, let’s stop thinking about them. Let’s share a few cups, I’ll call Fei’er and the others as well.”

After the Great Demon King heard that Zhao Hai wanted to call Fei’er and the others, he said, “Mister, do you also intend to take Fei’er and the others to the Space?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and smiled, “Your Majesty already guessed it? To be honest, I’d like to do that. However, I still need to look at what they think. If they don’t want to, then we can just forget it. If they agree, then giving them a Space would be no problem.”

The Great Demon King smiled, if anything, this only made him more curious about Zhao Hai’s Space. He already knew about the Ark Space and the Demon Space, he wanted to know what other things Zhao Hai had.

The day went by calmly, the Divines in Holy Light City didn’t dare to attack Zhao Hai and the others. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai and the others had a rare moment of relaxation. They drank quite a bit of liquor, Fei’er and the others were even somewhat drunk.

The next morning, Zhao Hai made an order to have the army set up outside of Holy Light City. Then the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King went on to attack the two Domain Weapon experts before retreating just like the day before.

The Divine Race felt strange. Why did Zhao Hai choose this method? Would he just attack them like this time and time again?

In the evening, after Zhao Hai went back to the Space, he took a look at the processing machine. The time was reflected there, in about ten hours, the upgrade would be completed.

Ten hours. After seeing the timer, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but show a brutal smile. In ten hours, he would personally break through Holy Light City.

They had a good night’s rest. The next morning, Zhao Hai had his breakfast before going back to the processing machine. It showed that only two hours remained. Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry so he came out of the Space and informed the people that they need to wait for two hours.

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King knew what Zhao Hai meant, so they just stayed in their carriages and waited for two hours to go by.

At the same time, although Fei’er and the others didn’t know the reason why Zhao Hai decided to wait for two hours, they still didn’t ask questions. They were now relying on Zhao Hai, so naturally they wouldn’t offend him over this very small matter.

On the other hand, Holy Light City was waiting for the enemies to arrive. However, they actually didn’t come, this caused those inside the city to be anxious.

Two hours was neither quick nor slow. At that time, Zhao Hai was in the Space looking at the Atlanta continent and the underworld’s actions. When a few minutes remained, Zhao Hai and the others proceeded towards the processing machine, quietly looking at the timer as it counted down.

As time passed, the groups’ heartbeat almost harmonized with the ticking down of the clock. Although they already knew what the ship would look like, they were still anxious to see it in person.

Finally, the timer turned to zero. The processing machine released a white light. As the ship appeared in front of them, Zhao Hai and the others were stunned.

What appeared in front of Zhao Hai was a palm-sized ship. It was golden and looked like it was made of crystal. It looked very beautiful, just like a piece of art.

Zhao Hai gently rotated the ship in front of him. It was really good, this was the Hell King’s ship that he was looking forward to!

Chapter 853: The Hell King’s Ship Shows It’s Might!

Beautiful, it was too beautiful. Although they knew that it was a lethal weapon, Zhao Hai still couldn’t bear to admire the beauty of this thing.

Laura and the others were also looking at the ship with shining eyes. To be honest, Laura was thinking that the name ‘Hell King’s Ship’ was now unsuitable for the ship. This was because the ship seemed to have abandoned its ghastly nature. The engravings were still terrifying, but it it didn’t express evil. A lot of people liked to engrave scary images not to be evil but just to intimidate their enemies.

Laura grabbed the ship on Zhao Hai’s hand and said, “It’s beautiful. Brother Hai, how about we make more. Can we do that?”

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and smiled, “Rest assured, if you like it, we can have as many of them as you want. But unfortunately, I don’t have the ability to make more of them at this time.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, I believe you. But Brother Hai, can this small thing, really expand countless times?’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as the ship on Laura’s hand started to fly away and increased in size. It got bigger and bigger as it became as large as a city. In the Ark Continent, it could be considered to be a major city.

The changes on the ship made Laura and the others exclaim in surprise. Zhao Hai’s appearance was also somewhat similar. If he kept increasing its size, then it might not be able to exit the spatial rift.

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “How is it? Good? Come, let’s head up. Let’s ride the ship as I direct the undead to battle.”

As soon as they heard this, Laura and the others immediately flew towards the ship. Zhao Hai smiled before he urged the ship to go forward.

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were quite anxious. Their strength was still on its peak. Their battles in the past two days were quite short, so they didn’t lose too much power. It can be said that their fights were more of a warm-up than anything else. When Zhao Hai told them to wait for two hours, the two immediately knew that Zhao Hai’s ship was on the verge of completion. It was because of this that they were that anxious, they wanted to see what Zhao Hai’s ship looked like.

Fei’er and the others were also waiting. They weren’t that worried about their situation. In any case, Zhao Hai already told them that he intends to drag the time for a few days.

At this time, a huge spatial rift suddenly appeared in mid-air. Almost everyone present noticed the huge crack, even the Divines in Holy Light City. While their attention was focused on the rift, a incomparably huge ship slowly appeared from it.

Everyone looked at the huge ship. It was too beautiful. The golden translucent hull, the dark blue waves underneath it, the sharp and long tip, the ship’s high tower, the wind chimes, all of them were magnificently crafted. They collectively were able to make the ship extremely gorgeous.

Zhao Hai and the others calmly stood on the ship’s bow, calmly looking at Holy Light City. At this time, the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King reacted. They looked at the ship with amazement. They knew that Zhao Hai was upgrading the ship, they just didn’t expect that it would change to this degree.

The two Demons looked at the ship and then to their carriages. At this time, they felt that their carriages were incomparably tiny.

After the Hell King’s ship completely stopped, the Great Demon King and the others flew towards it, this included Fei’er’s group as well. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Is everyone prepared? We’ll be taking Holy Light City today.”

The Great Demon King was amazed at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is your upgraded ship? It’s so beautiful. I can’t imagine that a ship could be this dazzling.” The Demon Dragon King nodded, “It’s truly beautiful. In the past, the ship had this ghastly nature, as if it came from the underworld. But this ship didn’t have that feeling at all. Mister, this achievement is too astonishing.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t comment. He turned to the group and said, “We’ll talk about that later. We’re taking Holy Light city today, does anybody have any opinions?”

The group shook their heads. To be honest, after Zhao Hai had upgraded his ship, they had already lost their desire to be treated as equal. At this point, they only wanted Zhao Hai to deal with the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “Alright, since nobody has any other thoughts, then we’ll proceed. Your Majesty, Demon Dragon, you can store your carriages and step on the ship. You’ll not be needing them today. Fei’er, order your army to follow behind the ship. After we break the defensive formation, I will send the undead army to block their retreat. Meanwhile, you and the others will move and clear all those who resists.”

The group gave an assuring nod. Then Zhao Hai smiled as he commandeered the ship to head towards Holy Light City. The Divines on the city had already seen the ship. They haven’t seen a ship as huge as this before, all of them couldn’t help but panic.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about their reaction as he slowly led the ship forward. Zhao Hai didn’t let the ship speed up, he wanted to use this opportunity to pressure the Divines to react.

Before long, the Divine Race responded. The two Domain Weapon experts proceeded to rush out from the city. They had no other choice, otherwise, deserters would start to crop up. Like what Zhao Hai’s group had guessed, the soldiers of the city weren’t comprised of regular ones. There were citizens who took up their weapons to fight. Although they weren’t weak, their battle sense was worse than the Divine Race army.

The two Domain Weapon experts quickly increased their size. When they finally saw Zhao Hai, they immediately launched an assault. However, the scene quickly turned into a joke. It was just like two knights heading out to see in order to stab a megaton-class ship.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and smiled. The ship stayed on its current speed and didn’t react. It leisurely advanced as the two experts approached.

At this moment, a sudden wave hit the two experts, destroying their Domains. Their whole person immediately turned to ice as their Domain Weapons were taken into the ship. The bodies were also taken in by Zhao Hai. After a wave of his hand, two new undead walked out of the cabin.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s method, Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but be more afraid. They didn’t know how strong the ship actually was, but they knew that it’s true might didn’t rely on the waves below. Still, the waves were still able to decimate the experts that the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King were on equal strength with. They were even turned into undead immediately, they couldn’t help but shiver in fright.

However, the surprises didn’t stop there. The Hell King’s ship proceeded to fly slowly towards the city. The Divines in the city also saw their experts being erased in front of them. Now that there was nobody capable of blocking the ship, the Divines couldn’t help but get flustered. They panicked even more. However, the soldiers were still able to stabilize their situation. It didn’t take too long before magic cannons and ballistas started to attack the ship.

But people soon discovered that these attacks were useless. The ship might not be completely closed in, but on could see the waves beneath it block the attacks from going through.

At this time, the ship had finally arrived in front of the city’s protective shield. The ship’s front proceeded to clash with shield despite its slow advance. However, like a balloon being pricked by a needle, the protective shield eventually popped. It dented for a moment before it totally vanished.

But the ship still kept going directly towards the city. Aside from its front bow, the hull was also quite formidable as it slammed towards the city’s wall. The originally thick wall seemed to become as fragile as paper. The ship didn’t have any difficulties smashing through as it continued its advance towards the city.

The Divine Race finally devolved into total panic. Not only the new recruits, even the veterans were panicking. And as this spectacle played out, the magic cannons on both sides of this ship automatically changed their aim and before long more than 100 beams of red light blasted through the rest of the city walls.

The explosion wasn’t something one would expect. There was no earth shattering noise. As the red lights hit the walls of the city, the white stone immediately vaporized. The walls, including the magic cannons, ballistas, and Divine Race soldiers, had disappeared into thin air.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation as he expression changed. He bit his lip as he whispered, “It’s too strong!”

Laura and the others who were near him could hear his voice. They looked at Zhao Hai and laughed. Their actions elicited a response from the Great Demon King and the others. They couldn’t help but turn their heads towards the women.

Zhao Hai restored his expression as he waved his hand. Then large quantities of undead started to come out of the ship’s cabin and headed towards the city. Fei’er and the others saw this and also had their armies join.

At this time, there was no resistance inside Holy Light City. This was because Zhao Hai had underestimated the ship’s attacking strength. He didn’t expect the magic cannons and ballistas to disappear just like that. Millions of people on the walls were vaporized by the ship’s cannons.

The Great Demon King looked at all of these and then looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, how do you want to deal with the Divines? To be honest, it’s quite difficult being on your side. We rarely get any chances to feel accomplished.”

When Zhao Hai and the others heard the Great Demon King, they couldn’t help but laugh. They didn’t expect the ruler of the Demons to be able to crack a joke.

After some time, Zhao Hai calmed down. Then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, how do you want to deal with the Divines? They’re full of hatred towards me.”

Laura looked at the panic-stricken Divines, she had no immediately answer to the question. After some time she said, “Brother Hai, what do you want to do? You can’t just kill them all. Didn’t we used to be on the same state as them?” Zhao Hai smiled bitterly. To be honest, he didn’t have the heart to kill the children. Although he knew that the Divines were his enemy, he still couldn’t bear being too cruel to those uninvolved.

After some time, Zhao Hai said, “Kill all who resist. As for those who surrendered, throw them into the Space and just let things run their own course.”

Laura smiled bitterly, in his mind this was already the best decision. Moreover, Zhao Hai had found out that there were a lot of commoners inside Holy Light City.

Holy Light City can house 20 million people. But now, the population inflated to near 30 million.

At first glance, one could see that they were the people who used to occupy the empty villages a few days ago. Zhao Hai understood that they must have been afraid and thought that Holy Light City was safe.

Zhao Hai didn’t become polite. He had his undead take those who didn’t resist into the Space. The place he took them was a background with no inhabitants within. He would leave them there and see where they’ll end up. As for those who resisted, they were killed and made into undead.

Zhao Hai still had sympathy, but too much of it is harmful in the battlefield. If you sympathized with an enemy who didn’t share the same thought, they you would end up suffering huge losses. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t hold back against those who decided to rebel.

Holy Light City had turned chaotic. But as the skies darkened, the place started to calm down. This didn’t meant that the Divines had hidden themselves, instead, it was due to Zhao Hai killing all who resisted while throwing those who didn’t to the Space.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also plundered all of the weapons in the city. Besides daily necessities and food, everything was thrown to the Space. The supplied that remained were all handed over to Fei’er and the others. This would provide them with enough food for the following days, so Zhao Hai didn’t need to give them supplies anymore.

Chapter 854: Foreign Races Appear

Zhao Hai was currently inside the Space’s villa. In front of his tea table was the Hell King’s ship. At the same time, displayed on the monitor was the scene of the transported Divines inside the Space.

Zhao Hai looked at this people not because they were acting well. On the contrary, he discovered that the Divines were really good at destruction.

It’s not wrong, they were good at destroying things. Ever since they entered the background, they started to destroy everything inside it. There were some bread trees inside the background. Zhao Hai had these trees on those backgrounds so that these people would survive. He also sent some magic beasts inside.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Divines to destroy everything upon entering the background. They wiped out the bread fruits and kicked the fruit trees down. They also killed all of the magic beasts they came across. Probably this was because they wanted to vent their anger.

Laura and the others were also in front of the screen, shocked at what they saw. After some time, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, if they destroy things like that, won’t they starve to death?”

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and coldly said, “Yes, if I don’t save them, then they would definitely starve. But I don’t have the mood to save them right now. It’s fine to be angry, but being foolishly angry is stupid. I left them a way to live, but they instead chose to destroy it.”

The women looked at the screen and smiled faintly. They didn’t know what to say. What were these Divines thinking? Do they want to be slaves? Or are they tired of living? If they don’t want to love, then they might as well kill themselves. They didn’t need to anger Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to stop the Divines. In any case, there was nothing good in that background. Even if they destroy everything inside, Zhao Hai’s losses wouldn’t be that great.

Zhao Hai changed the image to Holy Light City. Although there were some damage to the city, most of the buildings were still intact. There would be enough room for Fei’er and the others to stay.

Moreover, since Zhao Hai didn’t take any supplies away, Fei’er and the others were living in relative comfort. There were even some people boiling water in order to take a bath.

Zhao Hai looked at their situation and nodded. Then he turned the image to the Atlanta Plane. Zhao Hai wanted to know what preparations they had done. To be honest, Zhao Hai wanted them to attack the Ark Continent as soon as possible. He wanted to get his hands on those mechas as soon as possible.

Currently ,the education of the Goblins had gone smoothly. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recognize the Goblins’ astonishing learning capabilities. The undead creatures that Zhao Hai sent had already taught them about the words of the Ark Continent. They had also been given books about magic formations to study from.

One must know that manipulating magic formations wasn’t easy. Some formations needed special materials to activate. Some needed metal, some worked better with wood.

Because of this, magic formation research doesn’t only involve the formations themselves. The materials and the methods to make them were also crucial for success.

It can be said that magic formation study was a comprehensive field. Aside from magic formations, one also needed to have studied other subjects such as alchemy and botany.

However, the Goblins were innately skilled on these matters. While they started to study fundamental formations, there were already Goblins who proceeded to study medium-grade formations used by the Ark Continent. It seems like their progress was doing very well.

Zhao Hai was very happy with this development. With the innate talents of the Goblins, they would be able to manufacture magic armors later on. For Zhao Hai, this was great news.

After looking at the Goblins, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to the Fishmen. To be honest, the Fishmen were living very comfortable lives. This was especially true for the Mermaids, they were extremely thankful to Zhao Hai.

This was because the Mermaids had a flaw in their bodies. It was because of this flaw that they were unable to produce God-ranks. Now that Zhao Hai had given them God-rank potions, they finally had a God-rank expert. For the Mermaids, there was no greater gift.

Most importantly, it seems like the God-rank potion was a key to the Mermaids. Their bodies were like treasure chests filled with riches. But since they had no key, they had no way to access it.

Now that Zhao Hai gave them the key, this treasure can now be attained. Once this treasure was opened, the God-rank Mermaids had discovered that their cultivation speed had skyrocketed.

On the same day the two God-rank Mermaids drank the potion, they were immediately able to establish a Domain without the need for combat. This caused Zhao Hai to have some envy towards them.

However, this also made Zhao Hai happy. Now that the Mermaids had this potential, he now had another strong race in his arsenal. This was definitely a good thing.

Then Zhao Hai looked at another race that he had neglected for a long time, the Sea Dragons. Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention to them after he transferred them to the Space. Now Zhao Hai wanted to see how they were doing.

Once he changed the display, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised. There were several God-ranks among the Sea Dragons. This was beyond his expectation.

Zhao Hai didn’t give them any God-rank potions. This meant that they had reached God-rank on their own. Although they were still Demigods, this was already quite remarkable. They haven’t entered the Space for long, only about a year or so. Having this result in that short time was already great.

The Sea Dragons were also very earnest. Those who hadn’t reached God-rank were working hard to break through. Those who have risen to God-rank were also working hard. It seems like the sight of the Divine Race had lit a fire inside them.

This was good for Zhao Hai. After looking at the other places for a while, Zhao Hai had discovered that he had nothing to do.

They were currently fighting the Divine Race, but they were also waiting for the news coming from Fei’er and the others. They needed to know about the situation before they could proceed to the next step.

Originally, Zhao Hai thought that he would need to expend his strength in order to defeat the Divine Race. But now that he has the Hell King’s ship, he was fully confident that he can win against the Divine Race with his own power.

In this plane, the Hell King’s ship was definitely a cheat-like existence. Currently, the most powerful weapon in the Space were the Domain Weapons. But now, those Domain Weapons no longer held importance to Zhao Hai.

Currently, the only thing Zhao Hai has curious with were the mechas of the Atlanta Plane. Were they better than Domain Weapons?

Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t worry about attacking. He just had his undead go to the hell background to train themselves.

While Zhao Hai was being carefree, Fei’er and the others were actually worried. After seeing the strength of the Hell King’s ship, they knew that maintaining an equal standing with Zhao Hai was impossible. Even if they can defeat the Divine Race, the three races still couldn’t beat Zhao Hai’s ship.

Naturally, Fei’er and the others knew that the most fearful thing wasn’t the ship, but Zhao Hai himself. They had seen the ship before, and had felt how strong it was. But in the hands of Zhao Hai, the ship actually improved by a lot. This was a huge blow to Fei’er and the others.

Zhao Hai defeating the Divine Race’s Deity was already beyond Fei’er’s imagination. Then They were even more startled by the fact that Zhao Hai was able to upgrade the ship.

Upon seeing the Hell King’s ship dealing with the Divine Race, Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but feel their hearts surrender.

In the past, Fei’er wanted to get in touch with their people in order to express Zhao Hai’s abilities. They wanted Zhao Hai to have a good image in their people’s mind.

But now, Fei’er and the others chose to withhold Zhao Hai’s information. This was because they were afraid of the Divine Race knowing about the Hell King’s ship. The ship was their ultimate weapon, the later it gets revealed the better.

The reason they thought about this was because the Divine Race still didn’t know about the ship. They were successful in conquering Holy Light City, not allowing anyone to escape. At this point, the Divines had no idea about what happened inside the city.

Shan and Yue held the same sentiment as Fei’er. The Barbarians and Winged Pegasus had some hatred towards Zhao Hai. Although Zhao Hai had apologized to them many times, there was still a small lump in their hearts.

But after they saw the ship, this lump immediately vanished. They didn’t want to offend Zhao Hai, or else they would just be courting death.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about what Fei’er and the others were thinking about. He was now being relaxed and carefree. All of these was because of the Hell King’s ship.

The ship was too formidable. Although Fuwa had vanished due to the fusion between the pagoda and the ship, Zhao Hai discovered that he didn’t lose anything. The Hell King’s ship seemed to be internally connected with him. As long as he gave an intention, the ship would do his bidding. This was enough for Zhao Hai.

Three days after Holy Light City fell, Fei’er’s messengers had come back. Moreover, they had brought good news. It seems like the Taurus Divines were short on military strength. Although they weren’t like Zhao Hai who managed to take Holy Light City, they were still able to hold a stand-off against the Divine Race. The Taurus Divines seem to lack troops to deal with them.

Upon hearing this information, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel relief. It looks like there’s no plot from the Taurus Divines. Instead, they were really short on soldiers. This allowed Zhao Hai to boldly deal with the Divine Race.

After reporting the state of their people to Zhao Hai, Fei’er and the others immediately sent another letter. This letter informed them about the Hell King’s ship. They expressed their request to fully cooperate with Zhao Hai.

Just when Zhao Hai was preparing to attack the Ark Continent, the arrival of some guests stopped him from going forward. These people weren’t Divines, they were from the foreign races.

After hearing the reports from Fei’er and the others, Zhao Hai prepared to attack the Taurus continent the next day. Before Zhao Hai went to sleep at night, it was already his habit to look at the monitor. But this night, he suddenly spotted a small team appearing on the monitor. This wasn’t a squad of the three races, instead it was a team of the Foreign races.

The foreign races of the Ark Continent had already entered the Space. Without Zhao Hai, it would be impossible for them to leave the Space. Moreover, the ones on the monitor had different mounts and were evidently stronger than the ones in the Ark Continent.

There were about a thousand people in this team. Beastman Race’s Wolf cavalry numbered 500, Elven Race’s unicorn cavalry numbered 200, and Dwarf Race’s Iron Armor beast cavalry numbered 300.

Although they weren’t many, one could see that they were elite. Their strengths reaching God-rank.

Upon seeing them, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be curious. One must know that Holy Light City was not on the edge of the Taurus Continent. So how did this cavalry team sneak in? Did the Taurus Divine army let them go? Are they that incapable of blocking troops in their border?

Zhao Hai’s guess was both right and wrong. The Taurus Divines were indeed lacking in troops. Therefore they could only guard important places in the continent. This was because they were afraid of the attacks coming from the foreign races.

At the same time, these Foreign races had the ability to sneak into the Taurus Continent. This was because of the lack of manpower from the Taurus Divines. And the other reason was the foreign races’ meticulous preparation. Even during the Taurus Divines’ heyday, they were still able to sneak in, much less now.

Chapter 855: Arrogant Foreign Race

However, before he decided to meet these foreign God-ranks, Zhao Hai decided to bring the Beast King, Elf Queen, and Dwarf Patriarch along.

They were the leaders of the foreign races in the Ark Continent. Now that the foreign races of the Divine Realm had appeared, Zhao Hai decided to have them meet. At the same time, Zhao Hai also had them bring their Divine Artifacts.

After the three leaders heard Zhao Hai, they immediately went along and appeared in Holy Light City. The three were now 9th ranks. With their Divine Artifacts in hand, their expressions were somewhat excited.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and said, “Don’t be too anxious. We’ll see your people soon. Your people in the Divine Realm.”

The Beast King, who held his Beast God’s Spear, smiled faintly and said, “I’m somewhat excited. I don’t know what kind of life they lived in here. But they shouldn’t be very different compared to us.”

The Elf Queen smiled as well as she said, “I didn’t think we would meet in this manner. Meeting our clansmen from the Divine Realm, hehe.”

Billy was also excited, but he didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he summoned a Bone Dragon. Then the group stood on the dragon’s head before they flew outside the city.

Zhao Hai already knew where these foreign God-ranks were. Therefore, he didn’t pretend to be clueless and just went directly straight towards them.

Before long, Zhao Hai can see a team in front of him. This team was no other than the group of foreign race God-ranks that he saw on the monitor. The other party was also alerted. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, they immediately got into formation.

Zhao Hai slowed the Bone Dragon’s speed. He didn’t want them to misunderstand his approach. At this time, conflict was the last thing that he wanted. After all, the enemy of an enemy is a friend, Zhao Hai can clearly understand this line.

The opposite party, seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t have any hostility, relaxed their formation. However, they didn’t lower their guard.

When Zhao Hai was about a kilometer away from them, he smiled faintly and said, “Hello. Are you the foreign God-ranks of the Divine Realm? My name is Zhao Hai, and I’m from the Ark Continent. These three are the Beast King, the Elf Queen, and the Dwarf Patriarch.”

The three leaders immediately gave these God-ranks a salute. On the other hand, the Foreign God-ranks were looking at them with a blank stare, they didn’t know what to say.

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “There’s no need to be startled. We made a counterattack on the Taurus Continent and had seized Holy Light City. Might I know why you’re here today?”

The Foreign God-ranks looked at each other, they were still silent. In the end, they can affirm that these people were indeed from the Ark Continent. These rulers were all 9th rank, and being leaders despite being 9th rank  was rare in the Divine Realm.

At this time, A Beastman God-rank said, “You’re deceiving us. The Beastman Race’s Royal Tribe are the Diamond Apes. When did the leadership change to the Tiger Tribe?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Beastman God-rank and smiled, “This needs explanation. You haven’t contacted with the Ark Continent for a long time, so you might not know about the continent’s situation. The Diamond Apes are certainly the Beastman Race’s Royal Clan, however, they managed to lose the Beast God’s Spear on the Northern Icefield. Because of this, they were sent to exile by the Beastman Race. Currently, the Lion and Tiger Tribes take turns in leading the Beastman Race.”

The Beastman God-rank looked at Zhao Hai and said, “And who are you? I’m speaking to my lesser clansman. What does it have to do with you?”

Zhao Hai gawked, he looked at the Beastman God-rank’s eyes and could see disdain. It seems like he was looking at him as though he was an enemy.

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows, but his voice remained gentle, “You, let me ask. What do you mean by lesser clansman?”

The Beastman God-rank revealed his disdain as he said, “Human, you’re not qualified to speak to me. You, little tiger. You are just a lower grade clansman. How dare you look at me with those eyes.”

This shocked not only Zhao Hai, the Beast King and the others were stunned as well. This was because they discovered how their Divine Realm clansmen look at them. Their gaze was no different than the look the Divine Race had.

The three were staring blankly. They expected to be received warmly by their people in the Divine Realm. But instead they were met with this look, it was very difficult to accept.

Zhao Hai saw the three’s change in expression, so he stopped being polite as he looked at the Beastman God-rank and said, “You, I think you have misunderstood. We’re not any lesser than you. All these years, you’ve been suppressed by the Divines and can only huddle up in your three continent. On the other hand, the Ark Continent not only defended ourselves, we also mounted a counter attack on the Taurus Continent. We did all of these without your help. You have no qualifications to talk like that to us. If we didn’t defeat the Taurus army, you wouldn’t have sneaked in this easily.”

Zhao Hai’s impolite speech stunned these Foreign God-ranks. Meanwhile, it made the Beast King and the others vent some of their anger.

Zhao Hai was not wrong. When the Divine Race invaded the Ark Continent, Zhao Hai alone led the continent to defend. At that time, what help did these races give? And now they had the gall to be arrogant? They’re too shameless.

These Foreign God-ranks had ugly expressions as they looked at Zhao Hai. Then an Elf came forward and said, “Sure enough, Humans are indeed arrogant and conceited. My lesser clansman, what do you want to do now? Will you stay with this Human, or will you join us and return to the Virgo Continent. The true home of our Elven Race.”

The Elf Queen looked at the God-rank Elf and then gave a smile as she calmly replied, “I’d rather stay with mister Zhao Hai. The Virgo Continent is not the home of the Elves. As far as I know, anywhere in the 13 continents can be our home.”

The Beast King and Billy smiled since the Elf Queen wasn’t wrong. As long as Zhao Hai was present, then anywhere in the 13 continents would be their home. To be honest, they really didn’t care about the Divine Realm.

The Foreign God-ranks were stunned. They didn’t expect the Elf Queen to be refute the Elf. The God-rank Elf’s face turned blue as she berated, “Do you know what you’re talking about? The might of the Divine Race is beyond your imagination. Do you want to be enslaved by the Divines? Are you crazy?”

The Elf Queen couldn’t help but smile, she looked at the God-rank Elf and said, “I’m not crazy. The Divines are indeed very powerful, but the current Taurus Divines aren’t. After a few days, the Taurus Continent will fall into our hands. Moreover, we have no interest in the other continents.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Elf Queen, he looked at the Foreign God-ranks and said, “I don’t know what you’re doing in the Taurus COntinent, but this information might help you. The Taurus Divines doesn’t have the means to deal with your team. Rest assured, the Divine Realm will soon hear the news that the Taurus Continent have been conquered by the alliance of the Ark Continent, the Thunder Clan, the Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus.”

When these God-ranks heard this, their complexion couldn’t help but change. They knew about the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus. They were enslaved by the Divine Race so they had a few tussles with the Foreign races. Although these people weren’t born in the Divine Realm, one couldn’t deny that their might was quite strong.

Now, Zhao Hai actually said that the three races were their allies. This divided the foreign God-ranks between those who believed Zhao Hai and those who didn’t.

Zhao Hai looked at their eyes and said, “You don’t have to be as careful as you are now in the Taurus Continent. Besides some big cities, I believe there won’t be Divines in other places. Well then, we will be returning to Holy Light City. By the way, Holy Light City is now under our control. If you need any help, you can find us there.”

After that, Zhao Hai steered the Bone Dragon to head back towards Holy Light City, not paying anymore attention to the Foreign race God-ranks. The Beast King, Billy, and the Elf Queen all had disdainful expressions as they looked back at their kin in the Divine Realm.

Once they arrived back at Holy Light City, Zhao Hai released his Hell King’s ship and welcomed the group inside to sit. After being offered some tea, Zhao Hai looked at the others and said, “It looks like we don’t have to count on the Foreign God-ranks. But it’s somewhat strange for them to be in the Taurus Continent.”

The Beast King and the others didn’t think that their clansmen would treat them that way. At this time, the one who calmed down first was the Elf Queen, she knit her brows and said, “Mister, it might be because of the Thunder Clan and the others.”

Zhao Hai stared, he understood what the Elf Queen meant. Fei’er said before that they would coordinate with the Foreign God-ranks once their operation began. In the end, this prior cooperation wasn’t needed because of Zhao Hai. This means that Fei’er and the others already had contact with the Foreign Races before and they had reached an agreement. But after not being in contact with Fei’er and the others, these Foreign Races decided to send a team to the Taurus Continent to see the situation.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That is possible. I’ll deal with this matter, you can go back to the Space. There’s no need for you to take refuge with your kin.”

The three didn’t decline. To be honest, they had been used to living inside the Space, they now preferred it compared to outside.

After Zhao Hai sent them off, he immediately called the Great Demon King, the Demon Dragon King, as well as Fei’er’s group. Upon embarking on the ship and seeing Zhao Hai sat there with tea and some snacks, they didn’t become polite and immediately took their seats. At this point, they were used to Zhao Hai’s behaviour.

Chapter 856: A Place to Train In

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled faintly, “I just saw a group of Foreign Race God-ranks earlier in the Taurus Continent. They appeared not far from Holy Light City. I took the leaders of the Ark Continent’s Foreign races met them. However, those people didn’t look good to us, so I didn’t invite them back here. Fei’er, did you have a prior agreement with the Foreign Races?”

Fei’er remembered the attitude of those Foreign God-ranks, his face turned ugly as he nodded and said, “We did have an agreement with them. We planned to cooperate and split what we gained. I think they came here since we haven’t sent some people since we came out of the Ark Continent. To be honest, I really don’t like those guys, they’re too arrogant. If I could say, the Divines didn’t like them because they were also too proud.”

As soon as the Great Demon King and the others heard Fei’er, they couldn’t help but laugh. Zhao Hai laughed as well. Fei’er liked to joke, especially now when they didn’t have too much to worry about.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Those people are truly arrogant. I think they will stay in the vicinity in the next few days. We need to proceed with our plan and clean the entire Taurus Continent.”

Fei’er and the others nodded. They were now quite eager to try conquering the Taurus Continent. They understood that with the Hell King’s ship, cities would be easily taken care of.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled, “Good. Then go and prepare your army. We’ll move tomorrow. Right, after you head back, have your people clean the entire city. We’ll take them with us inside the Hell King’s ship.”

The group nodded before they turned around to leave. The Great Demon King, along with the Demon Dragon King remained. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “How’s life in the Space doing? Are you satisfied?”

The Great Demon King laughed and said, “Satisfied, beyond satisfied. To be honest, this is the dream of the entire Demon Race. Our people are now properly settled down, we’ve even started to learn how to farm. Mister can rest assured that we won’t disrupt the Space’s environment.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s great. Let me tell you something. I’ve also given the same environment to the Divines we captured. I want to leave them there and see where they’ll develop. But who would’ve thought that they would proceed to frantically destroy everything inside, including the Bread Trees I’ve prepared for them to eat. Without those fruits, I don’t believe they would last for long. It’s a pity, I’ve given them a chance, but they decided to throw it away.”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King stared blankly, disbelief written on their faces. Then the Great Demon King said, “Did the Divines really do that? Why?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “They must have thought that I would enslave them. In any case, their Space is completely different to what it used to be. They’re different from the Demons who lived in the Demon Realm. The Divines in the Divine Realm hardly encountered anything bad. They’re used to being proud, looking down at those different than them. They had completely lost their judgement. And they call themselves Divine Race, hahahaha!”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King proceeded to laugh as well. However, the two Demons can understand Zhao Hai’s underlying emotion. Zhao Hai was angry. The Divines were unappreciative to what Zhao Hai gave them. The opportunity that was offered to them was completely trashed.

The two were stuck not knowing what to say. They couldn’t help but think about the Demon Race. If the Demons were defeated by Zhao Hai, what would they do after being sent to the Space? Would they do the same as the captured Divines?

The two thought that the outcome would just be the same as right now. Demons were simple beings, and living in the Space had given them great comfort. They would still take care of the grass and the trees there. This was because the environment was much better compared to the Demon Realm.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and smiled, “Right, later on, I want the Devil Legion to go to a Space to train. That way, maybe they can break through to God-rank.”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were stunned. They looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll take you to another Space, but you might not like it very much.” Then he waved his hand as they disappeared from the ship. The next moment, the three of them appeared inside the Hell background.

The two Demons couldn’t help but stare blankly at the surroundings. It was quite similar to the Demon Realm, no, it was much worse than the Demon Realm.

The Great Demon King looked around him before turning his head to Zhao Hai and asking, “Mister, this place is?’

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This is my Hell Space. It isn’t very different compared to the Demon Realm. Here, I can promote the level of my undead and can plant some special plants. These special plants will be used to make my God-rank potions, allowing 9th ranks to become God-ranks. But it’s a pity that I can’t make much of the potion at this time, otherwise I would’ve given them to the Devil Legion.”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King looked at each other and saw the amazement on their eyes. Breaking through from 9th rank to God-rank was very difficult. There were countless 9th ranks in the Demon Realm, but there were only few God-ranks due to the suffering and hardship that came with it. It can be said that in ten thousand 9th ranks, it would be lucky if one of them were able to break through.

Who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai would be able to make a potion to make 9th ranks to God-ranks. This was too astonishing. It seems like they were still underestimating Zhao Hai’s capabilities.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “This is one of the most recent backgrounds I’ve gained. Although its environment isn’t good, Demons can certainly cultivate here. In fact, I will send some people from the Ark Continent here to train. I want the Devil Legion to train here as well. What do you think?”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King looked at each other before nodding. Although this background was quite treacherous, the Devil Legion still needed that final push before breaking through. Once they upgrade their strength, their accomplishments would surely be limitless.

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King and said, “I opened this Space before. It was during the Demon Realm’s beast tide. At that time, I had them sent here. With fierce magic beasts inhabiting this place, I believe that it would be the best training ground there is.”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King stared, but they also nodded in the end. The magic beasts of the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm were totally different compared to those in the Demon Realm. Magic beasts of the Demon Realm had the savagery found nowhere else. In terms of training, the magic beasts of the Demon Realm were indeed the best.

Originally, the Great Demon King was worried that the Demons would lose their tenacity after living in a good environment. But now that this place existed, the worry vanished into thin air.

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Alright, I agree to mister’s plan. When I head back, I’ll let the Devil Legion train here.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s no need to be anxious. It’s fine if we don’t send them all at once. Let’s do it in batches. What do you think?”

The Demon Dragon King gave a nod, “Alright. If we send them in all at once, then we might experience  a shortage of people. We’ll just move slowly and have them slowly accumulate experience here.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then it’s settled. Let’s have the first batch be 100 thousand people. They can come in at any time.”

The Great Demon King nodded. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as they returned to the Hell King’s Ship in the Divine Realm. At this time, Fei’er and the others were preparing for tomorrow’s attack. Zhao Hai looked at the two Demons and said, “Your Majesty, Demon Dragon, you go and prepare as well. When the time comes, I’ll call you over. Right, inform the Devil Legion about the Foreign God-ranks. Have them be vigilant. If those guys decide to attack the Devil Legion, then don’t hesitate to fight back.”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King gave out a short laugh before they turned around and left. At this time, Laura and the others walked out of the cabin. Meg cleaned the table and placed some snacks. Meanwhile, Laura said, “I didn’t think the Foreign Races in the Divine Realm would be that disappointing.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s possible that they had gone dull after living in the Divine Realm for some time. They had become arrogant. Hehe, let’s stop caring about them. If they aren’t doing well, they will surely beg us for help.”

Laura shook her head and said, “I hope they won’t ask us for help. Or else Brother Hai would surely give a hand.”

Zhao Hai smiled, then he drank some of his tea as he looked at the horizon. After some time, Zhao Hai said, “To be honest, the Divine Realm looks very good. I’m not cruel enough to come and just destroy it.”

Laura and the others also looked at the scenery. Then Lizzy sighed and said, “It would be nice if we weren’t enemies. Unfortunately, the Divines are too ambitious for their own good.”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, there’s no need to worry over it. Remember the Divines in the Space? They’ve brought this onto themselves.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled. To be honest, he was indeed thinking too much about this matter. He didn’t understand why the Divine Race were too arrogant. Was it because they thought that they were invincible? They didn’t expect to be defeated by someone other than their own kin? Perhaps this was why they couldn’t accept their current defeat.

Chapter 857: Shock!

Early next morning, Fei’er and the others took all of the things inside Holy Light City and sorted them out before taking them into the Hell King’s ship. Everyone who went on board the ship were curious about everything inside. However, they were left disappointed upon seeing that the cabins were just empty rooms.

However, the Hell King’s ship was still able to surprise them. They didn’t think the ship would have enough of a capacity to take in everything inside Holy Light City.

To be honest, they don’t need much when they advance. Bringing daily necessities was useless since everything was supplied by Zhao Hai. However, both the Demons and the Goblins needed these things.

All of those involved were strong so it didn’t take too long for them to take everything inside Holy Light City. After that, Zhao Hai urged the ship forward as the rest followed behind.

Zhao Hai also noted the Foreign God-ranks not far from the ship. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about them too much. Them following along was doing him a favor.

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King weren’t inside the ship. Instead, they were on each of their Domain Weapons, flying on both sides of the ship. As for the two recently acquired Domain Weapons, Zhao Hai didn’t give them to anybody else. He just had their undead owners keep them for now.

The large army advanced towards the Taurus Continent. Their speed wasn’t fast since Zhao Hai was looking after Fei’er and the others. He was afraid that flying too fast would diminish their fighting strength.

Their current enemy was the Divine Race and Zhao Hai didn’t want to eliminate them by himself. The merit of this action was too big. In this operation, Fei’er and the others also need to do feel like they were significant. This would be good for the alliance’s future development.

The Foreign God-ranks weren’t too far from the army. They wanted to see how Zhao Hai plans to deal with the Divine Race. At this point, they still didn’t believe that Zhao Hai was able to mount a counterattack against the Divine Realm.

Just like Zhao Hai thought, they didn’t meet any other Divines. It seems like the Divines did indeed evacuate to the big cities and were preparing to fight against the alliance army.

Although Zhao Hai can affirm that nobody was able to escape from Holy Light City, the other cities should still be able to sense something wrong judging by the fact that Holy Light City had been silent for quite some time. Therefore, those cities would surely make corresponding arrangements. Not seeing any other Divine on the way was a normal scenario.

Ryder’s complexion was heavy as he looked at Zhao Hai’s army. Ryder was a Dwarf. To be honest, he was quite happy when he saw Billy. However, Billy not giving him a salute the moment they met angered him. Therefore, he can only give a negative look towards Billy and the others.

As Zhao Hai said, they had been in the Divine Realm for too long that they had developed some arrogance deep within. They started to think that they were superior, especially compared to those back in the Ark Continent. They thought that those from the Ark Continent don’t deserve to have equal footing with them. Actually, they didn’t intend to offend Billy and the others.

Although Ryder was somewhat arrogant, we wasn’t heartless. He had the same temperament as the Dwarves back in the Ark Continent. For him, good was good and bad was bad. In his mind, there was no such thing as a grey area.

And even if he didn’t like Billy’s conduct, and sees the Ark Continent as inferior, he still wanted to look after the Dwarves, the same was true for the other two races. At the same time, they followed also because they wanted to see whether Zhao Hai did indeed have the ability to fight against the Divine Race.

Just like what was suspected, Ryder and the others came to the Taurus Continent in order to contact the Thunder Clan, the Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus with regards to their prior agreement.

The Thunder Clan and the others didn’t reach out. Therefore the foreign races decided to send this team to take a look. They wanted to see if a problem had cropped up.

But they didn’t expect that upon arriving at the Taurus Continent, they would actually meet Zhao Hai’s group. Moreover, Zhao Hai even said that they would deal with the Divine Race themselves. This evoked the curiosity of Ryder and the others. Because of this, they decided to follow behind Zhao Hai’s army.

The situation on the road made Ryder and the others understand that Zhao Hai wasn’t lying. It seems like they did have a way to deal with the Divine Race. Otherwise, the Taurus Divines wouldn’t have acted like this. They had been flying for so long and they had yet to meet a single Divine. All of the citizens from the villages and towns had been evacuated.

They certainly didn’t believe that the Divine Race had gone on a mass vacation. The reason of the move was certainly Zhao Hai and the others. In other words, the Divine Race knew that Zhao Hai was coming, and they were currently increasing their defenses by clearing the fields!

This tactic of increasing defenses by evacuating everyone had also been used by the Foreign Races. Moreover, they haven’t only used it once. When the Divines proceeded to attack their three continents, they had to use this method to deal with the invasion. In the end, they were able to endure long enough to reclaim the three continents.

Even during their strongest period, when the Foreign Races attacked the Taurus Continent, they still weren’t compelled to use this tactic. However, Zhao Hai managed to force the Divines to do so, this explained Zhao Hai’s strength.

It was because of this that Ryder and the others had unlikable expressions right now. They understood that Zhao Hai was telling the truth. They were indeed capable of attacking the Divine Realm. This meant that their kin in the Ark Continent were now in equal standing compared to them. And this thought left a bitter taste in their mouth.

At this time, they turned their heads back to Holy Light City. They had noted that the city’s walls had all vanished.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others arrived nearby a medium sized city. There were Divines defending the city, majority of them being civilians.

Zhao Hai inspected the city. It was a city that contained roughly more than 1 million people. It couldn’t be considered as a big city even in the Ark Continent, it can only be regarded as average.

The city didn’t have any Domain Weapon experts guarding it, its defending troops weren’t much either. The only troublesome thing in the city was the defensive formation. But this wouldn’t be a problem for Zhao Hai. At this time, Zhao Hai decided to have Fei’er and the others deal with the Divines in this city. As long as he breaks the city’s shield, then everything will be left for them.

When the Divines in the city saw Zhao Hai and the others, they immediately manned the magic cannons and ballistas. Zhao Hai didn’t care about them as he just made the Hell King’s ship crash into the city’s barrier, immediately breaking it’s protective shield.

Zhao Hai didn’t use the ship’s cannons this time. The magic cannons were too powerful, using this on this small city would be overkill.

After Zhao Hai destroyed the shield, Fei’er and the others immediately made their attack. Fei’er and the other had long waited for this day. To be honest, they felt great fighting with Zhao Hai since every troublesome thing was already taken care of.

But at the same time, this was also a problem. This meant that they had no chance to show their strength. This made them look like toadies following Zhao Hai just for the sake of it. This made them feel quite terrible.

Now that they had the opportunity to perform, the three armies immediately overran the city. The Divines in the city were also going all out in defending themselves.

Zhao Hai stood on his ship as he gazed calmly at the ongoing fight. He reeled his sympathy right now, the Divines didn’t deserve it. Even if you feel bad for them, they certainly don’t feel to bad for their previous victims..

Ryder and the others who followed behind were all shocked at what happened. A city with 1 million Divines and was defensively prepared wasn’t a good place to attack. Taking such a city would take more than 18 million troops, and might even need a Domain Weapon expert.

The most troublesome thing in attacking a Divine Race city was its defensive shields. Powering these shields were crystals. Crystals were naturally growing ores and some even form inside the bodies of magic beasts.

Magic crystals also exist this way in the Ark Continent, but the energy they contain was completely inferior compared to those in the Divine Realm.

A magic formation in a city of 1 million needed about ten thousand crystals to activate. Moreover, a Domain Weapon expert would have to make ten full attacks to dispel the shield.

Also, magic crystals can be added as the damage was dealt. This meant that with enough crystals, a city would be close to impossible to break through.

However, this powerful shield was actually turned to trash in front of Zhao Hai. He only used his ship to crash the shield into nothingness.

This was the first time they had seen something like this. To be honest, this scenario only happened in their dreams.

The battle inside the city was very intense. The Divines were very tenacious in their defense. However, their morale was constantly declining. This was caused by none other than Zhao Hai.

The Great Demon King, the Demon Dragon King, and the two undead Domain Weapon experts were making moves as well. They would use their Domain Weapons to destroy any strong resistance in the city. It didn’t take too long before the Divines were pushed into a defensive stance.

Zhao Hai’s was still the same, he didn’t want Fei’er to lose too many people lest the three races would blame him. They knew that Zhao Hai was strong, so if he didn’t offer any help, then these people would surely blame him afterwards.

Zhao Hai had a fair understanding regarding a person’s nature. These people would rush to battle in the name of military merit, but once their losses mount up, they would immediately forget why they rushed in. In the end, they could only blame Zhao Hai for not helping them by eliminating the enemies.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to use the Hell King’s ship. This ship shouldn’t exist in this plane. Compared to the Divine Race, it was too strong, the Divines simply had no way of countering it. But Zhao Hai still released his undead to help Fei’er and the others.

There was an important reason for this move. Zhao Hai was afraid that if he used the ship too many times, then it might provoke a response from the laws of the heavens and the earth, kicking him out of the plane. This was not a good outcome, and Zhao Hai still had a lot of things he needed to do. Because of this, Zhao Hai chose not to use the ship’s might as much as possible.

After the undead joined the fight, the battle soon came to an end. All those rebelling were killed while those who surrendered were thrown inside the Space. Whether they would survive or not wasn’t something that Zhao Hai cared about.

After taking care of that, Zhao Hai immediately had the battlefield cleaned. Then with the city at the center, the army proceeded to take a rest. At this time, Zhao Hai paid attention to the team of Foreign race God-ranks.

These Foreign God-ranks were closely behind them, but they were also at a fairly safe distance away. Zhao Hai didn’t care too much about them as he shifted his attention to Fei’er and the others’ victory as well as their casualty count.

The battle was intense. The Thunder Clan lost about 3000 people while both the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus lost about 2,000 people each. The losses were still in their acceptable range.

Standing on the ship was Fei’er as he gave Zhao Hai today’s report. Zhao Hai’s mood was quite heavy, to be honest, he didn’t want the fight to continue like this. However, he didn’t have a way to stop it. The were too far in to halt their advance.

If he decided to stop, then the Ark Continent and the Demons might not have problem, however Fei’er and the others surely will. Fei’er and the others already went all-in in this operation. Besides Fei’er and the others, the Foreign God-ranks were also aware of the situation here. Once they get involved, the Divines from the other continents would surely make a move. This would certainly ignite a fire in the entire Divine Realm.

Most importantly, the Atlanta Plane and the Underworld were yet to be dealt with. Zhao Hai believed that the Underworld wouldn’t be too simple. It’s possible that their population was much more than the Divine Realm. In this case, didn’t this mean that they would also have more God-ranks? It was because of this that Zhao Hai couldn’t just withdraw. If he retreats, then nobody would be able to deal with the Divines. Also, there were also the other planes. No matter where he went, the fate of battle will always meet him.

After Fei’er and the others gave their report, they remained standing there looking at Zhao Hai. They saw that Zhao Hai was thinking about something. After some time, Zhao Hai was still silent. Finally, the Great Demon King opened his mouth and asked, “Mister, is there something wrong?”

Zhao Hai recovered, he looked at the group and discovered that they had worried looks. He couldn’t help but smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine. I only thought that the casualties from this fight is not small. From what I can see, how about we have the undead lead the charge from now on? Let’s reduce our casualties as much as possible.”

Fei’er and the others remained silent. To be honest, they really wanted to elevate their standing in front of Zhao Hai. However, they were still sane enough to not gamble with the lives of their people.

At this time, a Thunder Clan member flew towards the ship. Then he gave his report to Zhao Hai, “Mister, I have a report to make. Several Foreign race members are outside. They said they wanted to see you.”

Chapter 858: Ultimate Weapon!

Zhao Hai stared. One of the reasons he had Fei’er and the others attack today was to show these foreign God-ranks that they were indeed in an alliance.

Showing one’s strength was one of the effective ways of gaining allies. These foreign races in the Divine Realm were potential allies for Zhao Hai, so he needed to show them what he got.

Although Zhao Hai had this intention, he didn’t expect the Foreign God-ranks to be this quick to react.

Zhao Hai looked at the Thunder Clan member and said, “Lead them here.” The Thunder Clan member turned around to get the Foreign God-ranks. Zhao Hai looked at the others and said, “It seems like those arrogant guys had seen our strength. Hahaha. How about we act arrogant as well?”

When they heard Zhao Hai, the group stared for a moment before they laughed. At this time, the Thunder Clan member had led the foreign God-ranks to the side of the ship.

Zhao Hai bowed to the three leaders and smiled, “Please come up and have a seat. How about we drink a few cups?”

The three leaders gawked, then they looked at each other before flying over to the ship. Zhao Hai waved his hand as additional tables and chairs appeared.

Zhao Hai gestured to the chairs and said, “Everyone, please.”

The three paused for a moment, they didn’t know what to say. They looked around them and saw, Fei’er’s group along with the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King. However, they didn’t see the people they wanted to see, which was the Beast King and the others.

Upon seeing the look on the three’s faces, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Are you looking for the Beast King and the others? They’re not here. In fact, they wouldn’t participate in our counter-attack against the Divine Race. Although they had already consumed a potion to reach 9th rank, their strength still couldn’t contend with the Divines. Therefore, I didn’t allow them to participate.”

Ryder looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, you mean they aren’t in the Divine Realm?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, they’re not here. Last time, I just took them in order to meet you. In any case, you are of the same race. Also, you’ve sent them their divine artifacts, so they wanted to show them to you. Hehe, what a pity, you didn’t give them the opportunity.” When they heard this, Ryder and the other couldn’t help but feel awkward. Zhao Hai looked at the three people and laughed, “Anyway, come sit down. May I know the reason for your visit today?”

The three immediately took their seat at the table upon hearing Zhao Hai. Fei’er and the others also sat back down. Zhao Hai looked at the three and then smiled, “Right, I forgot. This is Fei’er, a member of the Thunder Clan. This is Barbarian Shan, while this is Yue from the Winged Pegasus race. These two are the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King.”

Ryder looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Dwarf Race, Ryder.”

The Beastman then said, “Bingya, Wolf Tribe.”

Then the Elven person said, “Elven Race, Yehta.”

Zhao Hai nodded and asked, “What matter did you come here for?” The three looked at each other before Bingya said, “We followed mister today to see your fight against the Divine Race. To be honest, you’re battle was far from what we expected. We didn’t think mister was this strong.”

Bingya’s conduct made Zhao Hai stare. Before, Bingya and the others were so arrogant, looking like they won’t accept defeat. He didn’t think that Bingya would become this poilite.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I was just lucky. You have lived here in the Divine Realm for a long time and had many contacts with the Divine Race, so you must know about their Deity. This ship wasn’t mine initially. The Divines summoned their Deity in order to deal with me. In the end, I defeated him and took this ship for myself.” When Bingya and the others heard this, their complexion changed. They had been fighting with the Divine Race for a long time, so naturally they were aware of their Deity. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have the ability to defeat the Deity’s projection.

After seeing the expression on Bingya and the others’ faces, the Great Demon King smiled and said, “And it’s not only a single time. Mister has defeated the Deity twice. The first time happened back in the Ark Continent. At that time, the Divines summoned the Deity to kill mister, but in the end, he ended up gifting his pagoda artifact to mister. The second time, he gave mister a ship. Moreover, the current ship looked way better than it used to be.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This ship is the combination of the pagoda and the ship from before. An improved version.”

Bingya and the other two looked at each other, shock evidently plastered on their faces. They didn’t think that it would be like this. Zhao Hai’s abilities startled them.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled, “Let me just ask, do you want to form an alliance with us and deal with the Divine Race together?”

Bingya and the others nodded. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s great. Being in an alliance just makes things easier. But I think it would be best if you send this information to your territories and discuss it with your people. If you agree, you can just tell me. I’ll use this period of time to deal with the Taurus Divines.”

As soon as Bingya and the others heard Zhao Hai, they nodded. They knew that what Zhao Hai said was correct. An important matter such as forming an alliance wasn’t something they themselves can decide. Moreover, it seems like the Demons were with Zhao Hai while Fei’er and the others were already taken in by him. Adding Zhao Hai’s incalculable strength, the team leaders definitely needed to report this matter to their people.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled, “Everyone, not involving you in our attack of the Taurus Continent was my idea. The hatred between your three races and the Divine race is too deep, you should already know this. If you participated in our attack, then the entirety of the Divine Race would counter. At this time, we have yet to capture the Taurus Continent, if that happens, then it would be disadvantageous for us. Therefore, I planned to deal with the Taurus Divines first before informing you. An enemy of an enemy if a friend. As long as we eliminate the Divines, only then could we relax. Because of this, I’m willing to form an alliance with you.” Bingya and the others kept silent. But their faces couldn’t hide their awkwardness. Their conduct last time was indeed too poor. They had treated Zhao Hai and the others as lesser people. Now that they were facing the strong Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but feel disgusted by themselves.

They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would still propose an alliance. Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled, “I won’t hold you here for too long. I hope that you can contact your people and give me a reply as soon as possible. If you agree to the alliance, then preparations would be needed.”

Bingya and looked at the others and then the three simultaneously stood up. They gave Zhao Hai a salute before they turned around to leave. After seeing that Bingya and the others had left, Fei’er chuckled and said, “To be honest, I’m getting tired of seeing arrogant people. Mister, I think after seeing the battle today, they will definitely start to behave.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I truly hope that they will agree to the alliance. But to be honest, I also wouldn’t be bothered if they decline.”

Fei’er laughed. When they contacted the three foreign races before, it seemed like they were at a disadvantage. This made him feel terrible. Now that Zhao Hai said this, he realized that what they felt might be the same as what those three team leaders must have felt right now. They felt that if they don’t ally with the foreign races, then they would have no way to contend with the Divine Race. In the end, they would have to be compelled to enter the alliance.

Zhao Hai was different, whether the foreign races wanted to become allies or not, his strength can still take him to his destination. It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai could have the initiative to propose the alliance. He would hold an equal position to the

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, since our attacks had been smooth, I have something to tell you. I heard that the Divines of the 13 continents had their ultimate weapons. Once their continent met a critical situation, they would us it. I heard that the might of this weapon is enormous. But as to what degree, I don’t know.”

Zhao Hai said, “Ultimate Weapon? Hmm, perhaps this is the reason why the three races are yet to eliminate the Divines on their own continents. Hehe. It doesn’t matter, now I want to see how strong these Ultimate Weapons are.”

After seeing Zhao Hai so relaxed, Fei’er couldn’t help but caution him, “Mister, being careful of this point is important. I heard that this weapon can even move mountains. It’s extremely strong!” Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, I will pay attention. No matter what, we need to take the Taurus Continent for ourselves. So sooner or later, we would have to meet this weapon. We’ll strengthen our offensive from now on. We’d rather have the Divines use this weapon on us compared to your people.”

Chapter 859: Nibbling at the Taurus Continent

As soon as they listened to Zhao Hai, Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but stare blankly. Then they soon understood his point. If the Divines decided to use their ultimate weapon on their people, then they would no doubt be defeated.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and the others and comforted them, “It’s going to be fine. Don’t worry, we’ll quicken our advance tomorrow. I also want to see what this ultimate weapon looks like.”

Fei’er and the others stayed silent. Then Zhao Hai said, “Fei’er, after you go back, send a letter to your people. Tell them to refrain from pushing too hard against the Divines, let us take care of it.” The three nodded, then they stood up and said their goodbyes before leaving.

After seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. The Great Demon King smiled as well, “Mister, you really scared them. To be honest, if I was the ruler of the Taurus Continent, I would definitely use that ultimate weapon to eradicate their three clans first. Only then would they have no extra worries when fighting a decisive battle against us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s true. That’s the reason I decided to remind them. But it’s quite strange that Fei’er only told me about this ultimate weapon now. Did he forget about it?”

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King looked at each other. They felt strange as well. It seemed like Fei’er forgot, but he didn’t express his lapse in memory. Zhao Hai looked at the two and smiled, “It’s fine, don’t worry. It doesn’t matter if they forgot or they withheld it from us. The result is still the same.” The Great Demon King smiled and said, “Perhaps they didn’t want mister to gain another weapon.” Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai laughed.

Zhao Hai being relaxed wasn’t because he was looking down on the Divine Race’s ultimate weapon. It was because he was confident with the Hell King’s Ship. If the ship couldn’t defeat this ultimate weapon, then Lu Wei had no qualifications to become the Divine Race’s Deity.

If Lu Wei wants to become the Deity of the Divine Race, then he would need to establish his dominance. Both the pagoda and the ship were very powerful artifacts. Although they hadn’t undergone Zhao Hai’s upgrades, they still allowed Lu Wei to subdue the Divine Race. In other words, these two treasures should be more formidable compared to this ultimate weapon. Otherwise, the Divines wouldn’t have submitted to him.

If Lu Wei’s two weapons were more powerful than the ultimate weapon of the Divine Race, then how strong would Zhao Hai’s fused treasure be? This was the reason behind Zhao Hai’s confidence.

But although he was confident, he still didn’t want to take his enemy lightly. Even lions go all out in wrestling rabbits. Zhao Hai was also the same.

After Fei’er and the others returned to their own camps, they immediately sent letters to their people. They were afraid that Zhao Hai’s words would come true.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others carried on with their attack. Zhao Hai had changed their way of fighting against the Divine Race. He asked Fei’er about their location and it seems like they were now in the southeast part of the Taurus Continent. Their direction yesterday was headed towards the continent’s northwest. This meant that if they continue, then they would slash through the continent in a diagonal line.

Zhao Hai didn’t want this to happen. Therefore, he changed their heading. To minimize being attacked in the rear, he decided to clear the southeast of the continent first before heading forward.

The current military strength of the Taurus Divines wasn’t a lot, but their southeast didn’t cut back on their defense. Almost all armies were centralized on large and small cities. This had given Zhao Hai the opportunity to pick them out one by one, just like how one removes one nail at a time. At the same time, the Space’s map of the Taurus Continent would expand as well.

After only three days, Zhao Hai cleared dozens of cities in the southeastern side of the Taurus Continent. Every Divine that was alive were thrown into the Space.

Zhao Hai didn’t really want to starve these captive Divines. Although they had destroyed a very large area in the background that they were in, that space was still very big. As long as they calm down, they should be able to understand that they shouldn’t destroy their environment. But as for how long they come to terms with their situation, Zhao Hai didn’t know.

At the same time, Zhao Hai wasn’t counting on them to provide him with Faith Power. He only threw them to the Space so that he wouldn’t have to deal with the nuisance of killing them.

After clearing the whole southeast of the Taurus Continent, Zhao Hai’s group started to advance further. However, Zhao Hai didn’t blindly go forward. Instead, he directly headed towards the largest city in the Taurus Continent as well as their capital, Divine Will City.

Their advancement went quick, going forward almost at a straight line. Every city they encountered was captured. Zhao Hai’s army was just like an unstoppable force.

Zhao Hai’s speed of attack made the Taurus Divines panic. There were even some people in the continent who started to prepared their ships, intending to seek refuge on the other continents

At this time, Fei’er and the others got some news from their people. It seems like they had stopped the Taurus attack. Moreover, they were sending over some people to meet Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious to fight with the Divine Race. He just chose this method so that the Taurus Continent would focus on him. Zhao Hai knew that he can’t push the Taurus Divines too much. It would be troublesome if they were to ask for help from the other continents.

Because of this, after Zhao Hai received information from Fei’er about the state of their people, he slowed his advance.

He slowed down, but that didn’t mean that he did nothing. Instead, he dealt with the areas he went through. If his previous advance was a straight line, his advance now was like a flat uniform plane.

Although he has slowed down, the area he conquered had gotten bigger and bigger. Zhao Hai did this to first, get a bigger territory, second, to give the Thunder Clan and the others a place for themselves, and third, to wait for the response from the Foreign Races.

Zhao Hai also paid attention to the response of the other continents. He already had Fei’er send a letter to their people. After they stopped the attack from the Divines, Zhao Hai asked them to have some of their elite troops monitor the state of the other continents. They need to make sure that the Taurus Continent doesn’t ask for reinforcements.

This request was unexpectedly accepted by the Thunder Clan and the others. Originally, they were feeling quite terrible for not being able to help deal with the Divines. The third day after Zhao Hai had occupied the southeastern part of the Taurus Continent, the representatives of the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus finally arrived.

This time, their lineup could be said to be extravagant. The Thunder Clan sent 200 thousand elites, the Barbarians sent 500 thousand, and the Winged Pegasus sent a million elites; all of which were God-ranks. Their leaders were quite remarkable as well. The Thunder Clan and the Barbarians sent their Great Elders, a position only surpassed by the Patriarch. Meanwhile, the Winged Pegasus sent their Council Speaker. In the Winged Pegasus race, besides the Patriarch, there was also a council participating in ruling the people. The power that a Council Speaker held was about the same as the Great Elders of the Barbarians and the Thunder Clan. It can be said that the three races had sent their 2nd highest ranked official.

Their status, compared to Fei’er and the others, was certainly much higher.

Their collective army arrived where Zhao Hai was. At this time, the Hell King’s ship was parked inside a medium grade city. After Fei’er and the others overran the city, they immediately set some huge camps. After the army arrived, they immediately settled inside their respective areas.

Zhao Hai didn’t care too much. In any case, they were just allies and he wasn’t their king. The newly arrived army weren’t required to see him after they arrived. They would visit their people first to get briefed about the situation before they go and see Zhao Hai. However, the three races didn’t make Zhao Hai wait for long. Immediately after settling down, the leaders came together to see him.

Zhao Hai stood on top of the Hell King’s ship as he looked at the three leaders arriving. These people were fairly old, they were also wearing traditional clothing from their clans. The Barbarian Great Elder was wearing a fur robe. His build was quite stout and on his hand was a staff. Although his robe made him look like a formidable warrior, he actually let out a scholarly vibe.

The Thunder Clan’s Great Elder was quite tall and big. He was also wearing a long robe and had a stick on his hand. This stick was like the totems the other Thunder Clan members had, but it was smaller, about the size of a cane.

The Winged Pegasus’ Council Speaker had magnificent clothes. He had a pure white staff and had a bearing of a Great Noble from the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai went to greet the three leaders as he gave a bow and said, “Zhao Hai has seen the leaders. For you to see me this early makes me feel honored. Please come on board and have a seat.”

The three immediately returned the bow as the Winged Pegasus Council Speaker smiled and said, “Winged Pegasus Fang has seen mister. Mister is too polite, it’s given that we would need to pay a visit.”

The Barbarian Great Elder also gave a salute as he said, “Barbarian Jiang greets mister. Thank you for helping our fellow Barbarians.”

The Thunder Clan Elder gave a salute and also introduced himself, “Thunder Clan Wushuang has seen mister. Fei’er had told us about mister’s abilities, I couldn’t help but admire mister’s strength.”

Chapter 860: I’m Quite Disappointed

Zhao Hai smiled at the three and said, “There’s no need to be polite, come and have a seat. I’ve prepared quite a lot of food.”

It wasn’t only Wushuang and the others who were present. Fei’er and the others also came. The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were already with Zhao Hai.

After the group sat down, Laura and the others immediately delivered the prepared food. Zhao Hai served Chinese dishes, something that cannot be found in the Ark Continent, or anywhere else.

The Great Demon King and the other guests gawked at the table. Although they were people with high status, they hadn’t seen a magnificent feast before. Everyone was speechless.

Zhao Hai raised his wine glass towards his guests and smiled, “Everyone, these are unique dishes of the Buda Clan. There aren’t a lot of people who have eaten it. I’m glad that everyone came here today. Please, join me in this toast!”

The others immediately raised their glasses to return the courtesy before downing it in one go. Then Zhao Hai refilled his glass, but this time he didn’t make a toast. Instead, he looked at the group and said, “Please have a taste of our dishes, there’s no need to be polite.”

Defeated by their curiosity, the guests decided to have a taste of the food. Let alone it’s tasty appearance, it’s aroma was quite outstanding as well. They couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai and express their praise by raising their glass. After drinking a few more liquors, Zhao Hai looked at the three newly arrived leaders and said, “You came to see me this time, do you have something to ask?”

Barbarian Jiang looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “We’ve been ordered by our Patriarchs to express our gratitude to Mister Zhao Hai. Not only did you forgive us for attacking the Ark Continent, you even allied with our group. We’re also grateful that you consider our people whenever you fight against the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’re too polite. We’re allies, that’s what an ally is for. Moreover, the Divines are our common enemy. It’s only appropriate to deal with them together.”

Jiang smiled as well and stayed silent. At this time, Thunder Clan Wushuang opened his mouth and said, “Besides expressing our gratitude to mister, we also brought an army to support the war. Naturally, we know that mister didn’t lack in military strength, but since we’re allies, we still need to contribute in one way or another.”

Winged Pegasus Fang nodded and said, “Right, although Mister is taking good care of us, we still need to help in the fight against the Divine Race. Otherwise, we will feel restless.”

Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “You’re all being very polite. It’s really fine. Having your people charge instead of my undead isn’t something that I would do. We’re allies, it’s not like I want to control your people by exhausting your strengths.”

Winged Pegasus Fang didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be this frank. Winged Pegasus Yue smiled upon hearing Zhao Hai as he said, “Speaker, Mister is always this frank. He talks like this to all his friends. Only when speaking to his enemies would mister change his tone.”

Fang nodded, he gave an appreciative look at Zhao Hai as he raised his glass and said, “Let me offer this cup to Mister. You’re a genuine friend. Also, this wine is really good.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “If you like it that much, then I’ll give you some when you head back. I also have some Beastman milk wine as well as fruit wines. At this point, the Ark Continent already has many types of liquor. All of them taste very good.”

What Zhao Hai and the others were drinking was Rice Wine. It’s not very strong so even those who hadn’t drunk any liquor could still bear a few glasses.

After the group drank another glass, Zhao Hai said, “I’ve already talked to the Foreign Races in the Divine Realm. I’ve proposed an alliance and hoped that they won’t begin attacking the Divines. Does anyone have any opinion on this?”

Fei’er and the others had already written about this matter. Therefore, when the three Elders heard this, they shook their heads. Then Winged Pegasus Wushuan said, “Mister, we’ve also considered this before. However, we were afraid that our allies wouldn’t be strong enough. Therefore, we needed to ask for their help in dealing with the Divine Race. But now that Mister is here, we can change our plan. Otherwise, things would be disadvantageous for us. Also, I need to thank Mister for reminding us about the threat of the Ultimate Weapon. Ever since we have been enslaved by the Divines, we had never seen that weapon before. Therefore, we aren’t even sure if it existed or not. Mister, we apologize for not telling you about it before.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “It’s fine. You’re not even sure of it so I can’t blame you. Don’t worry about it. Right, I’ll give you messenger fishes later. This way, it would be more convenient for us to communicate. You should also give some to the people monitoring the seas so that they can notify us as soon as possible.”

Thunder Clan Wushuang nodded and said, “Fei’er also wrote about those messenger fishes to the clan. To be honest, those things are convenient to use.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This fish is actually found in the Ark Continent. The Fishman Race has been using this fish to communicate with each other. But since the Radiant Church started to suppress the different races of the Ark Continent, the continent never knew about the existence of this fish.”

Wushuang and the others nodded. They have some understanding regarding what happened in the Ark Continent. The means used by the Divine Race were more sinister than what was done on the three races. If it wasn’t for Zhao Hai, the Ark Continent might have been enslaved a long time ago.

Then Zhao Hai said, “But these fishes also has a weak point. A fish can only talk with one other fish. This isn’t very good. I’m still finding ways to improve on it. I hope that it would be more useful in the future.”

Upon hearing this, Winged Pegasus Fang asked, “So Mister is saying that, later on, the fish can communicate with multiple people? If that’s the case, then that would be very good. Right, let’s go back to the current situation. I’m afraid it wouldn’t be long before the Taurus Divines use their Ultimate Weapon. Does Mister have any plans?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “In my opinion, there is no need to be afraid of that ultimate weapon. It’s quite obvious that the Divines couldn’t use it easily, they surely will pay a huge price whenever it goes out. Instead, I’m quite curious about  this weapon. Not only for the Taurus Divines, I’m interested in the ultimate weapons of the other continents as well.”

Fang and the others smiled. They were appreciative of Zhao Hai’s self-confidence. The group continued to chat for some time. After everyone was full and had drunk to their heart’s content, Fang and the others proceeded to leave.

After the guests had left, Laura and the others went out and looked at their departing backs. Then Laura asked, “Brother Hai, what did those guys come here for?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They wanted to see what kind of person I am. Then they asked me about how I plan to deal with the Divine Race. Not too complicated, just normal stuff.”

Laura nodded, “It looks like they’re quite satisfied. So Brother Hai, what do we do?” Zhao Hai replied, “Earlier I expressed my interest on these ultimate weapons. I can’t wait to meet them in the battlefield. I wanted to see if they can add more functions to the ship.” As soon as they heard this, Laura and the others chuckled.

The next day, Zhao Hai still kept advancing into the Taurus Continent. Although their speed wasn’t as fast as before, their stable advance caused the Divines to get a headache.

On the other hand, Fang and the others felt their horizons expand. The Hell King’s ship was more powerful than they imagined. Although they already received reports from Fei’er and the others, witnessing the ship themselves was a completely different thing.

Five days after Fang and the others met Zhao Hai, information arrived from the Foreign God-ranks. The ones delivering the message were still Ryder and the others. They told Zhao Hai that they agree to the alliance. They also agreed to Zhao Hai’s proposal of not attacking the Taurus Continent in order to prevent the other continents from joining the war. But if the other continents sent their troops, then the Foreign God-ranks would send troops to their continent, supporting Zhao Hai in the background.

After Ryder and the others reported the details, Zhao Hai began to attack the Taurus Continent according to his original plan. This time, he didn’t advance slowly. He sped his movements to force the Divines to use their ultimate weapon.

Zhao Hai’s plan was successful. On the tenth day after he formed his alliance with the Foreign God-ranks, the Divine Race dispatched their ultimate weapon.

At this time, Zhao Hai was attacking a Divine Race City. The shield of the city was broken in an instant as the undead started to pour in. Zhao Hai stood at his ship while looking at the battle, the Foreign God-ranks were at his side.

After giving their report to Zhao Hai, Ryder and the others didn’t leave. Instead, they followed Zhao Hai at the side. They saw Zhao Hai breaking defensive shields one after another. The Divines who weren’t taken away were turned into undead.

In the beginning, they were shocked upon seeing this. But after a few more cities, they began to become numb to the scene. Only one thing remained in their hearts, it was to never have Zhao Hai as an enemy.

At this moment, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a powerful aura coming from the distance. Aside from Lu Wei, Zhao Hai hadn’t felt a stronger presence like this one before.

A light flashed inside Zhao Hai’s eyes. Then he turned his head to Ryder and the others and said, “Everyone, it seems like the Taurus Divines had sent their ultimate weapon. Please disembark from the ship. I’m afraid I won’t be able to take care of you once the fighting starts. Moreover, it’s likely that you would get injured if you stay here.”

The status of Ryder and the others wasn’t low, so they were privy to the information about the Divine Race’s ultimate weapons. Therefore, once they heard Zhao Hai, their expression changed. Then after giving him a salute, they proceeded to leave the ship. After that, Zhao Hai urged his ship to go forward and meet the powerful aura.

Zhao Hai thought that the ultimate weapon of the Divine Race must be very large and powerful. But when he saw it, he couldn’t help but feel shocked. The ultimate weapon was too small!

There was a normal cow sized metallic bull, its four hooves solidly stepping on the air. On the back of this bull was a person. The person’s clothes, hair, and beard were all white. He was quite big and tall. Although he looked like an old person, one could still feel a ferocious aura coming out of him.

Zhao Hai stopped the Hell King’s Ship and looked at the approaching bull-riding person. At this point he was doubting whether this was the ultimate weapon or not.

The old person stopped about a hundred meters away from the ship. He looked at Zhao Hai and calmly asked, “Are you Zhao Hai?” Zhao Hai looked at the old person and smiled, “Correct. I am Zhao Hai. And who are you?”

The old person replied, “Kid, you actually dared to cause trouble in my Taurus Continent. Now that I’m here, it’s time to make you understand that someone from a lower realm had no right to do whatever you want in this place.” ZHao Hai looked at the old person and smiled, “Cause trouble? From what I know, it’s the Divines causing troubles in places where they shouldn’t be. And you want to teach me a lesson? And how would you do that? Using your ultimate weapon? To be honest, I have been waiting for this day. But I didn’t expect you to come this late, I’m very disappointed.” The old person’s expression didn’t change. But Zhao Hai can see a slight disturbance in his beard. It seems like his ego was pricked.

Zhao Hai can guess why this was the case, it must be because of the ultimate weapon. There weren’t many people in the Divine Realm who were aware of these artifacts. Moreover, those who knew would keep it as a secret. And now, Zhao Hai even dared to insult it. It’s no wonder the old man was affected.

Zhao Hai did it intentionally because he was still unsure if the old man with the metal bull was the ultimate weapon. Because of this, he probed to see if his speculation was true. And it seems like he hit the mark. Zhao Hai can confirm that the metallic bull was indeed their ultimate weapon.

The old man looked at Zhao Hai and said with an ice cold voice, “I didn’t expect to see the day where a person from the lower realm would insult me like this. Since there’s no use in talking further, it’s time for you to die!” Then the old person waved his hand. Zhao Hai saw a very small formation plate appear. At the same time, Zhao Hai was suddenly found himself surrounded with nearly 20 Domain Weapon experts.

The Domain Weapons were ten spears, five swords, and five shields. Although their size was nothing compared to the Hell King’s ship, they were still Domain Weapons, their strength couldn’t be weak.

Chapter 861: Golden Saint Seiya? What in the world?!

Zhao Hai didn’t look at who were the Divines using the Domain Weapons. Instead, he looked at the small formation plate in the hands of the old man. The plate looked extraordinarily pure. It had a yellow metallic sheen on its body, looking very beautiful.

In just a glance, Zhao Hai knew that this plate wasn’t simple. Otherwise, these Domain Weapon experts wouldn’t have appeared. It was certain that they were escorting this old man. The formation plate actually had a function to hide these people.

When the old man looked at Zhao Hai, his expression couldn’t help but shrink. Then the old man’s left hand gently patted the bull’s head. A round hole appeared on the head as the old man placed the formation plate in it. Then the round hole disappeared.

The action was very subtle. But even though the old man was quite far from Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai can still see the moves made by the old man. He also saw how the metallic bull absorbed the formation plate into itself.

After the old man settled the formation plate, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You’re the first person who managed to cause this much damage in the Taurus Continent. That’s quite the achievement. However, you cannot just trample on the pride of the Taurus Divines. You need to die!”

Zhao Hai looked at the old man and he smiled faintly, “You want to take my life? Do you really think that your ultimate weapon and domain weapons are enough to threaten me? Stop dreaming. I’ll make you understand what true might is.” After Zhao Hai said this, the cannons of the Hell King’s ship started to aim at the Divines.

The old man calmly looked at Zhao Hai. He didn’t believe that a few cannons would be able to make any damage. One couldn’t blame the old man for not being well-informed. Aside from Holy Light City, Zhao Hai didn’t use the cannons at any other place. At the same time, no Divine was able to escape their attacks. Therefore, the Divine Race weren’t aware of how powerful these cannons really were. In the eyes of the old man, these cannons wouldn’t be able to break the Domains experts.

The same was true for the Domain Weapon Experts. They were peak existences in the continent. Normal Divines were already arrogant, they were even more so.

Because of this carefree approach, they had given Zhao Hai an opportunity to deal a fatal blow. Although they saw the ship’s cannons being aimed at them, nobody moved. They wanted to show Zhao Hai how dominant they were.

At this time, the ship’s cannons began to let out red lights. The next thing that happened can be described as a sword puncturing paper. The Domains of the experts were broken though immediately and each of them were vaporized. With no owner present, the Domain Weapons began to fall. But before they reached the ground, they vanished, taken into the Space by Zhao Hai.

After destroying each Domain Weapon expert, Zhao Hai looked at the old man and said, “You plan on relying on those people to take my life? Continue dreaming.” If this was before, the old man might not care. He would just think that Zhao Hai was being arrogant. But this time, the old man couldn’t help but be terrified.

The old man can see a monster in the shape of Zhao Hai. He didn’t think that 20 Domain Weapon Experts would get vaporized just like that. Even if the old man used his own weapon, he wouldn’t be able to do the same. This was the first time that the old man had felt his heart shake.

Zhao Hai looked at the old man as his voice started to turn cold, “You’re telling me that we’re causing trouble in the Taurus Continent? Do you think that you have the right to say this? Who began this war? Who opened a spatial rift and changed the Ark Continent’s laws? Who sacrificed millions of my people? It’s you. You people are killers. Sooner or later, all debts shall be paid in full. Since you forced my hand, then you can only accept your fate. I actually want to thank you for giving me this many Domain Weapons and the ultimate weapon as well.”

When the old man heard Zhao Hai, his expression couldn’t help but change. Although he still had a pale face, he snorted at Zhao Hai and said, “Don’t think that you will be able to deal with me after killing those Domain Weapon experts. I’ll make you understand the power of our ultimate weapon!” The the old person loudly shouted, “Transform!”

And with his words, the metallic bull suddenly turned into a yellow light, wrapping the old man’s body. After the light vanished, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare blankly at the scene.

In front of Zhao Hai was still the old man. But this time, he wasn’t riding a metallic bull. Instead, his body had a beautiful golden armor complete with a helm. Upon seeing this Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recall something from his memory, a Golden Saint from Saint Seiya![1]

The armor worn by the old man was very similar to those worn by Gold Saints. But the armor still looked more gorgeous than the ones he saw back on Earth. The originally tall old man looked even more imposing with the armor on.

The old man slowly opened his eyes as he coldly gazed at Zhao Hai. He had no expression in his eyes, he seemed just like a statue.

Upon being swept by the old man’s stare, Zhao Hai recovered. Before he felt danger, Zhao Hai tapped his head and muttered, “What world is this? Why do things back in my old world keep appearing? Who can tell me what’s going on?”

The old man didn’t care about Zhao Hai’s mutterings. He coldly stared at Zhao Hai and said, “Anyone who dares to insult the Taurus Divines shall be punished by god. You will die!”

Zhao Hai looked at the old man and then shook his head, “It’s useless. Although you are indeed more dangerous now, I can also feel that the toll on your body is quite high. You simply don’t have the requirements to fully utilize this armor. Now that you forced yourself, let’s see how long you can stay in this form.”

The old man nodded at what Zhao Hai said, “That’s true. I can’t hold this form for a long time. However, it’s already enough to deal with you!” Then the old man rushed forward as he yelled, “Battle March!”

A weak light came out from under the old man’s feet as he soared towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s face changed, he can feel that this charge was quite formidable. Therefore, he didn’t dare to ignore it as he whispered, “Waves!” After that, water started to spray from the ship before it turned into rough waves. They crashed together to block the incoming figure.

Boom! The rough waves collided with the incoming charge. The rough waves dispersed the speed of the old man. Before long, the flashing image showed itself. It was a translucent bull charging straight towards the ship. The  bull was more than ten meters high. It had huge pair of horns that certainly had powerful impact force.

However, the property of Zhao Hai’s waves was sinister. Waves unceasingly crashed on the bull, reducing its charge by a degree each collision. The bull became slower and slower while also getting smaller as it hit each wave. Finally, it vanished into thin air.

When the bull vanished, the waves returned to the Hell King’s ship. Although the collision looked simple, its effects had manifested in the surroundings. Everyone was shocked upon seeing the degree of the fight. There were some undead and some Divines who were reeled in by the collision turning all of them into piles of dust and mists of blood.

The old man looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You really do have your means. But your luck has run out! Taurus Charge!” The old man wound his right arm around before punching forward. Another manifestation of a bull came out and charged towards the Hell King’s ship. Although it wasn’t as big as the translucent bull, one could see that it was more solid and much quicker.

Zhao Hai saw this move and immediately shrank the ship until it was only at the size of rice. At this point, Zhao Hai was standing in mid-air as he said, “Cleave!”

The ship immediately rushed forward, reaching its maximum speed in an instant as it met with the approaching bull.

The next scene can be described as a bull being stabbed by a sword. The bull immediately vanished, but the ship still kept going forward towards the old man.

The old man’s face changed, then he quickly shouted, “Turning Bull!” Then he turned his body. At this time, an image of a lazy bull turning over can be seen. Although it looked very clumsy, it was actually able to affect the impact of the ship.

Once the impact had passed, the old man immediately readied his fist as he shouted, “Eat this, Rampaging Bulls!”

Then the old man continually threw one punch after another. He was using this opportunity to make a move since the ship still haven’t returned to Zhao Hai.

The old man threw more than a hundred fists in an instant. Each fist forming a bull as it charged forwards. Zhao Hai seemed to not care about this as he silently said, “Hundred Cannon Salvo!”

As Zhao Hai said this, the Hell King’s ship suddenly appeared beside him. The ship didn’t increase its size but there were small cannons which projected red lights. The old man was quick to discover that although these lights were small, they still held their might regardless. Red and yellow lights continued to clash in the air causing quite a spectacle to those who were around.

* * *

https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/saintseiya/images/2/2a/Gold_Taurus_Aldebaran.jpeg/revision/latest?cb=20130521111326

Chapter 862: Starting to Repel

At this moment, the old man made another move. However, this one wasn’t based on punches. This time, he had his index finger out on both hands as he shouted, “Double Horn Strike!” Then he pushed his fingers directly in front of him.

Along with his movement appeared a pair of bull horns projecting towards Zhao Hai. At this time, Zhao Hai’s figure moved and returned to the Hell King’s ship. The ship was like a sword, going straight forward to crash into the old man.

It was at this time that Zhao hai opened his mouth and said, “Collision Formation!”

The old man had just extended his fingers, so he didn’t have enough time to change his action as the ship proceeded to ram him. The old man’s face changed, at this time, he thought that moving away was impossible. He crossed his two arms in front of him and waited for impact.

Unfortunately for him, when Zhao Hai hit his elbow, the old man heard a crack. His elbow along with his armor was cracked. The old man looked like he was hit by a truck as his body went rolling back. Blood also started to spurt out from the old man’s mouth.

The Hell King’s ship was also slowed down by this collision. The old man flew about a kilometer away just by the force of the collision. Then the man didn’t come back to clash with Zhao Hai. Instead, his figure moved as he quickly disappeared from the area.

This move was completely out of Zhao Hai’s expectation. After seeing the figure vanish, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head. He knew that he didn’t have the time to pursue the old man. Also, it was certain that the old man wasn’t going at a straight line. Who knows which direction he was currently heading now.

Zhao Hai shook his head and stopped thinking about this matter. He just waved his hand as he took something from the ground. It was the elbow part of the old man’s armor which was just broken off in the earlier collision.

Zhao Hai inspected the object, he discovered that the elbow thorn was silver white. It was very beautiful and at the same time, sharp.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and threw this elbow thorn into the Space. Then he turned his head from the old man to the city. He wanted to see how the attack had gone.

The people in the city were also paying attention to the battle. Now that Zhao Hai had defeated the old man, the Divines in the city were immediately sent into panic. There were those who tried to resist while some tried to escape. At the same time, Fei’er and the others had become more confident in their attack. Before long, the city was pacified. According to their previous arrangement, those who were captured were immediately thrown to the Space..

After Zhao Hai completed all of these, Thunder Clan Wushuang’s group as well as the Beastman Race’s Bingya’s group arrived on the Hell King’s ship. They had just witnessed the fight and they knew that the old person just used the Taurus Continent’s ultimate weapon. Upon seeing Zhao Hai defeat the old man, they couldn’t help but get startled.

Because of this, when the group arrived on the ship, their gazes towards Zhao Hai had become different. Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and smiled, “What’s wrong? Everyone shouldn’t be surprised. If we really think about it, it would be difficult for me to deal with that weapon. But since the old man didn’t have the proper requirements to use the armor, he could only get injured and retreat.”

Wushuang and the others weren’t fools. Naturally, they knew that Zhao Hai was just being modest. However, none of them said anything, they just went on and reported the casualties of the fight.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “Currently speaking, we are making good progress. But since that old man managed to flee, I think troubles will start to come. That armor was the Taurus Continent’s ultimate weapon. Now that they were aware that the ultimate weapon can’t deal with me, they will certainly ask for reinforcements. Elder Wushuang, Elder, Jiang, Speaker Fang, I hope that you can send a message to your clans requesting to allocate more power to keeping watch over the seas. I’m almost certain that the Taurus Continent would ask for help from the other Divines.”

The three nodded. They had also thought about this point. The Taurus Continent’s ultimate weapon was the Taurus Divines’ last refuge. Now that the weapon had lost, they can only wait for death unless they ask for help. The Taurus Divines aren’t braindead, they will certainly do something.

Zhao Hai turned to look at Wolf Tribe Bingya’s group and said, “Please tell your patriarchs to prepare. Your time to move might arrive.”

Bingya and the others stood up and gave a respectful salute. At this point they were afraid of Zhao Hai. They were still clueless about Zhao Hai’s other abilities.

After following Zhao Hai for several days, they had come to understand the various cards in Zhao Hai’s hands. There were the magic cannons, the crystals, the undead, the ship, all of them made Zhao Hai a capable person.

But today, Zhao Hai made them understood how terrifying he really was. They also had their own ultimate weapons in their respective clans. They took advantage of these weapons to defend their own continents.

However, Zhao Hai seemed to be able to take care of two or three ultimate weapons at once judging by how he dealt with the old man. At this point, they wouldn’t dare act arrogant in front of Zhao Hai.

After seeing that the group had agreed to his arrangements, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then everyone needs to prepare. In the next few days, we will hasten our advance. We need to get enough territory before the reinforcements arrive.”

The group gave a small bow before they turned around to leave. Whether it be Wushuang or Bingya’s group, all of them had already regarded Zhao Hai as the alliance leader. Therefore, they would certainly listen to his words.

After arranging these matters, Zhao Hai returned to the Space. After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Laura and the others immediately came to greet him. Then Laura said, “Brother Hai, how is it? Are you alright?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “i’m fine. But the ultimate weapon is actually quite powerful. Although I didn’t use the full strength of the ship, being able to block it’s attack is already very good.”

Laura nodded and said, “Right. I didn’t think that the ultimate weapon would be a full body armor. But Brother Hai, if the other continents collectively use their ultimate weapons against you, how will you deal with it?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, there won’t be any problems. I can easily deal with all of them. However, at best, I don’t want to use the ship’s full strength. I had just discovered that the laws of this plane had started to reject me.”

Laura and the others stared, they looked puzzled at what Zhao Hai said as they asked, “Really? How does it feel?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and answered, “It’s like going to a place where everyone is hostile to you and wants you gone. Moreover, everyone is very strong, you won’t be able to resist if they throw you out. Because of this, I don’t dare use the ship’s complete strength.”

Laura and the others nodded, but they didn’t know what to say next. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “It’s fine, don’t worry about it too much. I won’t be leaving this plane soon. Although the plane had started to repel me, it hasn’t reached to a point where I get thrown out. To be honest, if not because of Fei’er and the others as well as the Atlanta Continent, I would’ve opted to leave this plane. With my current strength, nothing in the Divine Realm is of use to me anymore. I’m also quite curious about why Lu Wei decided to suppress the Goblins while the Atlanta Plane went completely fine. After all, the next place where we’ll be heading towards is the Immortal Cultivator Realm. There, we would face Lu Wei with his real strength. Because of this, I want to gain as much advantage as possible so even if we do ascend we still have some life-saving measures in place.”

Laura and the others nodded. They didn’t know about Lu Wei’s true strength, but they knew that he was certainly more powerful than his incarnations. Moreover, Lu Wei was an elder in his sect. It’s possible that the sect had plenty of elders like him. And it was also certain that people more powerful than him existed. If this was the case, then they would face an overpowering enemy once they arrive at the Immortal Cultivation Realm.

Upon facing such an enemy, one should get all the advantages he can to maintain his life. Everything that can save them was good. Because of this, Laura and the others agreed to Zhao Hai’s plan.

To be honest, Laura and the others didn’t care too much for the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus. For them, as long as the Ark Continent was safe and the Demons who submitted to Zhao Hai was safe, then that’s enough. Those three races mentioned before were just Zhao Hai’s allies, there was definitely no need to care about them for now.

However, Laura and the others were also the same as Zhao Hai; they were quite curious about the Atlanta Plane’s magic armors as well. Items allowing someone to have God-rank strength was always good.

If they can improve these magic armors and find a way to mass-produce them, then their fighting strength would certainly soar.

Most importantly, Laura and the other would like to obtain the various ultimate weapons in the Divine Realm. Compared to the magic armors, these ultimate weapons were more formidable. If they can obtain these weapons, then their strength would naturally increase. When the time comes, they would no longer worry about the problems they were facing.

Chapter 863: The Final Battle

The war kept going on. And just like Zhao Hai said, they sped up their attack on the Taurus Divines. At this point, Zhao Hai has no shortage of troops. He had already sent the first batch of Devil Legion soldiers to the hell background to train. The undead in Zhao Hai’s hands had already exceeded 100 million.

Zhao Hai’s undead numbers has also been increasing every day, and all of these undead were God-ranks. Once could say that Zhao Hai’s current military strength can hold up against another continent in the Divine Realm.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai had more than 20 Domain Weapons. Having such a quantity made one formidable in the Divine Realm.

At this time, besides asking for help, the Taurus Divines couldn’t do anything else to deal with Zhao Hai. The Taurus Divines truly had their backs against the wall.

With the increase of Zhao Hai’s undead, his speed in attacking the cities of the continent shot up. Zhao Hai selected his strongest undead and gave them Domain Weapons, sending each of them to attack the other cities in the vicinity.

Five days after Zhao Hai’s fight against the old man, news came from the Barbarians. They discovered a team of Taurus Divines heading towards the Capricorn continent. It seems like they were going to ask for reinforcements. This team wasn’t big, about 10 thousand Divines or so. However, among them was an old man riding a metallic bull as well as two domain weapon experts. They rest were elite Taurus Divine cavalry.

After seeing this composition, the Barbarians didn’t dare to block them. When Jiang and the others heard this part, they were relieved. If they decided to block this team, then they would definitely be slaughtered.

Once Zhao Hai heard that the old man went out of the continent, he immediately had the Barbarians and the other two mount a full attack on the Taurus Continent.

In order to deal with their fear of being defeated by a Domain Weapon expert, Zhao Hai gave each clan three undead domain weapon experts.

But what Barbarian Jiang and others didn’t know was that these undead had a piece of token on their bodies. These tokens were fragments of the blood ghost staff and can be used to monitor things around them.

With the three clans joining in, in addition to the large number of Domain Weapons, Zhao Hai and the others had gained the winning side in the war. At this time, the Taurus Divines had given up on defending small cities. Instead, their armies were centralized on its big cities. Only commoners were left behind.

However, before Zhao Hai and the others came at ease, the Taurus Divines suddenly gave the commoners a decree. As long as a commoner was able to kill Zhao Hai or his undead and escape, then they will be rewarded by the Royal Family and even have them become a member of the noble class.

For ordinary Divines, this was an extremely attractive offer. In the Divine Realm, every commoner’s dream was to become a noble.

This was because if one was a Noble, then it was possible that they would lord over a plane in the near future. But in the past, bestowment of noble titles had been severely restricted. This ended with the nobles in the Taurus Continent to be small in size.

But now that they suffered losses against Zhao Hai and was inching towards destruction, the Taurus Continent issued this decree. This caused the commoners to leave the cities and begin doing guerilla warfare.

This tactic had impacts on Zhao Hai’s group, especially to the three clans. They were always worried that they would be attacked by the Divine Race.

Although Zhao Hai was affected as well, it’s impact wasn’t too big. After all, he has the Space. Those people who would ambush them would be spotted by the Space first. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried.

However, this matter still angered Zhao Hai. The three clans began to have casualties. This made them hesitate in moving forward, affecting Zhao Hai’s plan in a major way.

Zhao Hai wanted to deal with the Taurus Divines before the reinforcements arrive. With this, they would have more of a strategic edge in defending. But the decree made their advance slow down. When the time comes, he would become more passive when the support arrives.

Moreover, the situation had aggravated. In the past, as long as Zhao Hai dealt with the garrison troops and the rebelling commoners, the other Divines would stop their struggle. It was at this time that they encountered something new. Since there were no defenders in the city, the Divines seemed to behave. But when Zhao Hai sent the undead to throw them into the Space, he discovered that some undead went missing. Upon counting, Zhao Hai discovered that he had lost more here than in the siege. This made Zhao Hai furious.

Once Zhao Hai became angry, the consequences became serious. Zhao Hai, who couldn’t bear to kill, suddenly gave an order. If more than 100 undead became missing in the city, then he would completely wipe the city’s population. This order was spread out. Before they start their attack, he would tell the Divines to refrain from resisting. Or else everyone will be killed!

In the beginning, the Divines didn’t believe this order. However, when more than 1000 undead disappeared from a medium grade city of over 1 million people, Zhao Hai ordered the extermination of every Divine inside. More than 1 million people were killed, no living witness remained.

Besides killing everyone, Zhao Hai also used the Hell King’s ship to erase the city from the map. And just like that, a medium grade city that can house more than 1 million people had disappeared.

The Taurus Continent was very big. And although people were doing guerilla tactics against Zhao Hai, they would still need supplies to survive. Because of this, they became aware of Zhao Hai’s attacks on their cities. When the news of Zhao Hai’s elimination of an entire city had spread out, every Divine became angry. But at the same time, they were terrified, they knew they had no way to resist, Zhao Hai was too strong.

There were some benefits in Zhao Hai’s actions. There were small cities in the continent who didn’t resist and just had the undead take them to the Space.

For those who didn’t resist, Zhao Hai gave them some rewards. He returned some of their living materials so that they could live a better life inside the Space.

Although more and more Taurus Divines had entered the Space, their rebellious attitude had gotten milder and milder. The Divines who came in earlier had destroyed a large chunk of land, but they quickly came to know that those things were useful to them. If they don’t want to starve, then they would have to behave.

Zhao Hai didn’t force them to do anything either. As long as they don’t cause any trouble, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t care much about them.

The Divines also discovered that although the Space couldn’t compare to their life in the Divine Realm, there were still some positives. Back in the Taurus Continent, whatever they do would get taxed. Whether they farmed, bred, or hunted, the nobles would still get a share. But inside the Space, they didn’t need to pay any taxes.

In order to further pacify the Divines, Zhao Hai treated them like what he did with the Goblins. He also erected churches, allowing the Divines to trade for goods while inside the Space.

Zhao Hai’s thunderous method pacified the small cities. At the same time the guerilla armies had started to discover that no city was able to supply them anymore. Every supply available was gone. If they continued to do their guerilla warfare, then they would need to forage for food themselves.

The Taurus Continent was huge and there weren’t any shortages on magic beasts. This might be good for the guerilla armies, but soon they had found out that they lack salt. Salt cannot be produced anywhere in the continent. Guerilla armies would need the cities to provide them with salt.

Now that Zhao Hai took all the small cities into the Space, not only salt, but grain and other commodities had vanished from the continent.

Lack of salt(sodium) in their bodies would make people ill. In this case, the guerilla armies had no other choice but concentrate on the cities that Zhao Hai had yet to take. This caused the supply problem to increase in each city. Soon, the Divines would need to fight a decisive battle against Zhao Hai.

It was at this time that Zhao Hai discovered that these Divines have become weak after being starved of salt. There was no need to fight them, they couldn’t even resist being captured.

The decree given by the Taurus Royal Family did create some troubles for Zhao Hai. However, the Divines were soon to discover that they had no way to cause any major problem for Zhao Hai. Instead, they only gave Zhao Hai more people to take away. Their plan had completely failed.

The Taurus Divines had truly reached a dead end. They found that Zhao Hai’s speed had gotten much faster. The Taurus Divines expected Zhao Hai to take about several months to a year to deal with every city. As long as the Taurus Divines hold on for four to five months, the support from other continents would surely arrive.

However, they discovered their mistake. According to Zhao Hai’s present speed, it would only take less than one month before he arrives at Divine Will City. When that time comes, everything would be over.

After looking at Zhao Hai’s daily progress, the Taurus Royal Family decided to make a move. They secretly had some of their juniors pack up and seek asylum from the other continents. Those who remained would hold Zhao Hai back.

Zhao Hai was aware about those who escaped, but he didn’t stop them. He still kept his speed as he advanced. As the resistance got weaker and weaker, his advance also got faster and faster.

A month after Zhao Hai knew that the old man had left the Taurus Continent, they had already killed their way towards the Taurus Continent’s Divine Will City. This was the biggest city in the Taurus Continent with a capacity that surpassed 60 million. But at this time, all 60 million people present in the city were all Divine Race soldiers. All the commoners have been moved to smaller cities. Naturally, those commoners were already inside Zhao Hai’s space. At this time, the only remaining city under the control of the Taurus Divines was Divine Will City.

The city was reinforced, it’s magic shield had already been erected. Magic cannons filled the walls, and the soldiers had expressions saying that they were ready to die.

Zhao Hai stood on top of the Hell King’s ship as he looked at Divine Will City. Standing on his side were the Great Demon King, the Demon Dragon King, the Barbarian Race’s Patriarch and Great Elder, the Pegasus Race’s Patriarch and Speaker, the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch and Great Elder, Wolf Tribe’s Bingya, Dwarf Race’s Ryder, and Elven Race’s Yehta.

Ten days ago, Zhao Hai had already convened with the Barbarians, Thunder Clan, and the Winged Pegasus. They used these ten days to completely conquer the Taurus Continent, the only place left to conquer was Divine Will City.

The Patriarchs of the three clans provided great support to the war. With Zhao Hai’s strength, they had already found themselves blindly following his instructions.

While looking at Divine Will City, the eyes of these people couldn’t help but shine. They had been conquered by the Divines, so they didn’t expect that they would be able to see this day. Who would’ve thought that they would surround the Taurus Continent’s largest city.

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King were also moved. After fighting the Divines, they became aware of how strong the Divine Race really was. If not for Zhao Hai, then the Divine Race would surely take the Demon Realm after conquering the Ark Continent. They would reach a situation that was the same as right now, their capital would get surrounded by soldiers as they made their last stand.

But the ones who were moved the most were Bingya and the others. The Foreign Races had battled with the Divine Race for tens of thousands of years. And all those years they had been at a disadvantage. If it weren’t for the Divine Race not being united, and the fact that they managed to get their hands on ultimate weapons, then they would’ve been reduced to the same state as the Goblins.

For many years, the Divine Race had always attacked the continents held by the Foreign Races. The Foreign Races were always on the side of defense, they had no ability to retaliate. In the current time, dealing with an entire continent was more difficult than it seemed. Seeing Zhao Hai able to do it this easily really made them feel flustered. They didn’t know what to say.

Chapter 864: A Bloody Battle

Zhao Hai looked at the battle-ready Divine Will City. To be honest, he had come to admire the Divines. Not giving up until this point wasn’t easy.

But although Zhao Hai held admiration towards them, they were still his enemy. Naturally, he wouldn’t hold back.

Zhao Hai urged the Hell King’s ship to slowly head near Divine Will City. After he reached some distance away, he stopped then said, “Divine Will City, I want to talk with your leader.” The Taurus Divines in the city were preparing for an intense battle. Nobody thought that Zhao Hai would actually have words to say. Nobody responded for a while but after some time, an old sounding voice was heard, “Taurus Divine Patriarch, Maurice, has seen Mister Zhao Hai.” Along with his words was a Domain Weapon slowly rising from the city. It was a sword-shaped Domain Weapon. Standing on top of it was a magnificently armored man. His hair and beard were both white and his bearing was astonishing. Although his Domain Weapon couldn’t compare to the Hell King’s ship, his imposing presence was no less than Zhao Hai.[1]

It was quite like Zhao Hai. If there was no war, then this person might not have been quite notable.

Zhao Hai looked at Maurice before he gave a slight bow and said, “Patriarch Maurice, hello. I want to talk about the current situation. With how things are right now, the Taurus Divines can do nothing, there’s no use for defending your city. I want to ask Patriarch Maurice to think about surrendering. I can personally guarantee your safety and I will not treat you as slaves.”

Maurice was looking at Zhao Hai with eyes full of hatred. After hearing Zhao Hai’s words, he laughed and said, “Zhao Hai, don’t think that you’ve won. The Taurus Divines will not fall. One day, you will all die!” Zhao Hai looked at the maddened Maurice and frowned. It seems like his appeal was a failure. The hatred on Maurice’s eyes could be clearly seen At this point, it was impossible for there to be a peaceful ending to the Taurus Continent’s war.

Zhao Hai took a deep breath and said, “Patriarch Maurice really made this Zhao Hai speechless. The result of the war has been decided by you, I hope you’re ready to shoulder the consequences. Please head back, we will be attacking soon.”

Maurice looked at Zhao Hai for a moment before he snorted and returned to the city. At this time, the Thunder Clan Patriarch standing behind Zhao Hai said, “Mister, you’re wasting your time on Maurice. That person is a complete lunatic. He will never recognize defeat, his arrogance is basically bordering craziness.” Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “The war has taken too many lives, I don’t want to add more. It’s a pity that peaceful means are impossible. We can only fight. Let’s go according to our previous tactic. I will break their shield and use the undead as the vanguard.” Then the group nodded.

Zhao Hai didn’t delay. After negotiations have failed, there was nothing else to do but fight. Zhao Hai commanded the ship to rush forward. The Divines in the city were prepared for this, but they still underestimated the speed of the ship. It was too fast that it almost instantly appeared outside the city when it was just quite a distance away a moment ago. Before the Divines could react, the ship had already rammed itself into Divine Will City’s shield.

Because of the ship’s speed, there was no time to reinforce the shields. After getting rammed, the shield immediately broke.

Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t let go of this opportunity. The cannons of the ship immediately attacked as large quantities of undead appeared in the city.

Although the Divines had met this attack many times, they still couldn’t grasp a counter to Zhao Hai’s attack.

However, Divine Will City wasn’t this easy to deal with. Although it’s shield has been broken, had received the Hell King’s ship’s cannon attack, and was overrun by undead, the sheer number of soldiers inside the city was a problem. Tens of millions of soldiers crowded the city for the decisive battle. This allowed them to block Zhao Hai’s surprise attack. While the Divines were battling it out with the undead, the Divines on the walls proceeded to fire their cannons towards the various armies outside the city.

Zhao Hai was aware of this situation, but he wasn’t worried. The number of undead in his hands right now was more than the soldiers inside Divine Will City. Therefore, there was no need to be afraid. He didn’t stop releasing undead as he gained more and more ground inside the city.

The battle immediately became heated at the very beginning. Those left in Divine Will City were people very loyal to the Taurus Royal Family. And with the Patriarch personally taking command, these people were already resolved to die in battle. This caused the casualties from the attacking allied army to also mount up.

The first minute of battle already caused deaths on both sides. The Divines used their entire flesh and blood in resisting the attackers. Zhao Hai couldn’t deny the fact that these Divines were truly brave and fearless. However, these people were his enemies, they didn’t merit Zhao Hai’s mercy.

The fight went on. This was the most bloody battle that Zhao Hai had experienced. Everyone involved seem to go mad. Their eyes were blood red as their bodies were covered with blood. The weapons in their hands swung endlessly. One would either kill the enemy or be hacked to death.

There were only a few participants in this battle who managed to keep a calm mind. The undead were already emotionless. The only thing they existed for at this time was to kill.

The situation had devolved into a complete brawl. Even Zhao Hai knew that using magic cannons at this time was impossible unless he would risk killing people on his own side.

But Zhao Hai didn’t worry. Although there were more than 20 Domain Weapons on the enemy side, he also had the same number in his hands. Domain Weapon experts on both sides were evenly matched.

Zhao Hai didn’t participate in the battle, at the same time, no Divine went for him. They knew that it would be impossible to kill Zhao Hai. The Divines were also aware that they would lose, they were just making their final struggle.

Time passed, one hour, two hours, three hours…. One day, two days, the war was still going on. Three days had passed and the battle still going. Atkept  this time, the entire Divine Will City was turned into a pool of black, brown, and red liquid. The fighting strength of those present were already affected after three days of zero nourishment. However, nobody stopped from waving their swords at their enemies.

Finally, when the curtains of the night descended, the last enemy was killed, formally ending the resistance of the Taurus Divines.

At this time, the combatants immediately fell to the ground; only the undead were left standing. Zhao Hai was still looking at Divine Will City on top of the Hell King’s Ship. No Divine surrendered in this fight, nobody escaped, they fought until the last soldier. However, this didn’t have an impact on Zhao Hai. War is war, no matter how tragic it was, war would need to go on.

Zhao Hai waved his hand to take all the Divine corpses inside the city. Then he waved once more as a huge ball of water appeared on top of the city. This ball drizzled water on the city, washing away all the filth.

Divine Will City had been completely destroyed. Hardly any building was left untouched. There were weapons strewn everywhere along with some cut limbs.

Soldiers lying down felt the rain falling. The rain was warm, reminding them of a hot bath. The rain was very comfortable. As they were lying there, the felt their strength slowly returning. Their sore limbs started to recover as well.

They couldn’t help but open their eyes and look at the huge ball of water up in the sky. The ball was not far from the Hell King’s ship. At this moment, the sun was proceeding to go down in the west, dying the ball in golden yellow hue. The originally golden Hell King’s ship had its color further enhanced, looking incomparably holy in their eyes.

The scene made the exhausted soldiers lie down for much longer. They don’t want to move as they just looked at the Hell King’s ship, a bit of reverence appeared in their eyes.

Zhao Hai looked into the state of Divine Will City. The ball of water was taken out of the hot spring. The water was initially hot, but as it drizzled into the city it began to cool down. After the droplets reached the ground, it had already reached a temperature that was comfortable for those lying down.

The bloodstains of the city began to be washed away. Although the city was critically destroyed, its sewage system was kept intact. Because of this, the water began to flow out of the city, cleaning it bit by bit.

The water not only bathed the soldiers, it healed their wounds as well. There were various soldiers in Divine Will City who noticed their wounds closing up.

After seeing that there were no bloodstains left in the city, Zhao Hai stopped the rain. At this time, several shadows began to fly towards the Hell King’s ship. There was no need for Zhao Hai to look to see that it was the Great Demon King and the others.

The fight involved more than 200 million people. The Taurus Divines had more than 60 million troops while the alliance army had more than 140 million troops altogether..

The Taurus Divines were completely wiped out, nobody surrendered. On Zhao Hai’s side, Zhao Hai lost more than 20 million undead. The Thunder Clan lost 5 million, the Pegasus Clan lost 7 million and the Barbarians lost about 14 million. Since only the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King participated, the Demons lost nobody. As for the team of Foreign God-ranks, the originally 1000 people were reduced to less than a hundred.

* * *

It said Patriarch, not King, but let’s just assume that.

Chapter 865: Not Short On Money

This was a big victory. They had finally destroyed the Taurus Divines. The three clans had already gained their freedom. From this point on, nobody would ride on their heads and command them.

However, this was also a hard victory. The losses on the three clans wasn’t small. Because of this, even if they had won, the faces of the Thunder Clan and the others weren’t smiling. At the same time, they also knew that a more brutal fight was waiting for them later on.

The group stood quietly as Zhao Hai gazed at the setting sun on the horizon. He was appreciating the sunset. Nobody talked for some time.

Moments later, Zhao Hai said, “i didn’t think the fight would be this bloody. The losses on your clans have been quite serious. You need to take a rest and regain your strength. However, I don’t expect the Divines to give us some time. I believe that soon, the armies from the other continents would arrive.” Upon hearing this, the expressions of those present became heavier. They knew that what Zhao Hai said was right. It had already been a month after the Taurus Divines had sent for reinforcement. Although they were yet to arrive, everyone knew that it was only a matter of time. The Taurus Divines just underestimated Zhao Hai’s speed, thus explaining why they had yet to return.

However, once they do come back, there would be an army behind them. At that time, the situation would be more severe.

The Thunder Clan Patriarch sighed and said, “I still underestimated the strength of the Divines. I thought that their blunder in the Ark Continent would affect their strength. The war was too bloody. Our victory is too tragic.”

The others nodded. Although the Thunder Clan had the least losses in the battle, their population wasn’t a lot to begin with. Once one looked at the impact of the casualties, the Thunder Clan had suffered the most.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Does anybody have a plan? The Taurus Divines are now gone, but the other Divines will surely come. I can handle ultimate weapons, but I’m not sure about the rest of you. Our future casualties might be bigger than it is now.” The Patriarchs held heavy expressions. They did defeat the Taurus Divines, but this only gave them even more powerful enemies. If they don’t handle this well, then they would be in danger of being destroyed.

It was at this time that Wolf Tribe Bingya suddenly said, “Mister, I have an idea. But I don’t know if it would work.” Zhao Hai turned to Bingya and said, “Oh? Then please tell us.”

Bingya looked at the group, everyone’s focus was already on him, then he said, “Mister, there are other clans who had been enslaved by the Divine Race. We have connections to those people and we’re quite certain that they’re also not satisfied with being ruled by the Divine Race. We can spread our victory in the Taurus Continent and maybe it would incite other people to rebel. This way, the pressure that we will face would be smaller.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before thinking into it, then he said, “That is a very good idea. But how about the other clans conquered by the Foreign Races? If we use our victory as a tool, then they might also rebel.” Bingya forced a smile and said, “Mister doesn’t know this, but the Foreign Races don’t conquer planes. First, one would need a method to break the plane’s barrier. However, this method was bestowed by the Divine Race’s Deity. It is a closely kept secret by the Divine Race. Because of this, there is no way for the Foreign Races to conquer another race.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Bingya and said, “That’s good. Then please report our current situation to your family and see if they can contact those races. Things have already happened so there’s no need for us to hide. Talk to those races and see if they would want to rise up against the Divines. Then we’ll cooperate.”

Bingya nodded, it’s good as long as Zhao Hai agrees. In fact, the Foreign Races had been thinking of ways to deal with the Divines. The Divine Race’s conquests on every smaller plane can indeed increase their strength. However, this also came with hidden dangers.

After the Divines conquer a race, then they would force those people to change their faith. This might not be a big deal back on Earth. But for the people here, their faith was more important than their lives. The Divines changing their faith would naturally plant a seed of hatred deep inside those people’s hearts.

The Foreign God-ranks had no such fears since they haven’t conquered other races. However, this caused them to be at a disadvantage because the Divines could force those who they conquered to fight for them while the Foreign God-ranks can only fend for themselves.

In order to change this situation, the Foreign God-ranks had found a solution. They secretly sent letters to those who were enslaved by the Divine Race to see how satisfied they were with the Divine Race. If these people hated the Divines, then the Foreign God-ranks wouldn’t attack them once the war starts. Naturally, those races chose to agree.

The Foreign God-ranks have been in contact with those races for some time, this explained why Bingya suggested this action. After seeing Zhao Hai’s combat prowess and knowing that he was an enemy to the Divines, then there was no reason for him to hide this matter.

Zhao Hai looked at the Thunder Clan Patriarch and the others and said, “The Taurus Divines has been destroyed. Now, the entire Taurus Continent belongs to us. The other Taurus Divines have also been taken away by me. However, I don’t want too many troops stationed in the continent. I’ll be using the tactic I’ve used in the Buddha Empire to deal with the incoming Divines.”

Fei’er and the others had experienced this firsthand, so they knew what Zhao Hai meant. To be honest, they were still left with no solution with this tactic, causing them to suffer some losses.

The Thunder Clan Patriarch and the others also understood what Zhao Hai meant. Fei’er and the others hand already reported what happened back in the Ark Continent. However, since they hadn’t seen it in action, they still held some doubts.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “You guys need a proper rest. How about this, you should withdraw your army and return to your own planes. Leave the Divines to me. Mister Bingya, when you send word to your people, tell them that there are still reinforcements coming to attack us. However, tell them to refrain from acting early. The other Divines are still cautious of us. We’ll weaken them first before you make your move. It won’t be too late at that time.”

Bingya couldn’t help but stare, he didn’t know where Zhao Hai’s self confidence came from. However, he believed that Zhao Hai must have some basis for this. Therefore, he didn’t argue and just nodded and said, “Alright, this won’t be a problem. But sir, do we continue with our plan to contact the other races conquered by the Divine Race?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Naturally.. Moreover, we need to do it as soon as possible. Tell them that if the Divines tell them to send some troops, then those troops shouldn’t try too hard in battles. If they do, then this Zhao Hai would have to be impolite.”

Bingya nodded. If this was before, then he might not have believed Zhao Hai’s words. But after seeing Zhao Hai’s strength, Bingya knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t joking. Then Zhao Hai turned to the others and said, “If you need anything, don’t hesitate to tell me. I can definitely provide you with what you need.”

The reason Zhao Hai had such huge confidence was because he wasn’t lacking in money at this time. The gold in the Demon Realm were very easy to mine. Currently, the amount of gold in Zhao Hai’s hands had exceeded his previous amount. Additionally, the 20 ordinary and 10 magic backgrounds have already been bought. With the addition of the other backgrounds, there was no shortage in supplies.

No matter what the Thunder Clan and the others needed, the processing machine can just make them. This caused Zhao Hai to dare say such things.

The Thunder Clan Patriarch and the others expressed their gratitude to Zhao Hai before taking their leave. The war left their clans with too many things to process. It was impossible for them to be with Zhao Hai for long. On the other hand, Bingya and the others stayed. Naturally, Bingya would have other subordinates process their action while he and the others stay and observe Zhao Hai. This was also for their people, they need to know how strong Zhao Hai was. Therefore, they would have to stay.

After seeing the group leave, Zhao Hai turned to the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King and said, “Your Majesty, Demon Dragon, you’ve been outside for some time, your people need to see you. I won’t be keeping you here for long”

The Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King observed Zhao Hai’s expression and knew that Zhao Hai had something to tell them and he didn’t want Bingya and the others to know. Because of this, the two didn’t say anything and just nodded, allowing Zhao Hai to send them back to the Space.

This wasn’t the first time that Bingya and the others had seen the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King entering the Space. However, they didn’t know that instead of the Demon Realm, the two were sent to the Demon Space. They were thinking that since Zhao Hai had a powerful Space Divergent Ability, he could send the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King back to the Demon Realm at any time.

To be honest, Zhao Hai was thinking of seizing this opportunity to make an offer to the Thunder Clan and the others. He would tell them about the Space and offer them their own background. But after Bingya told them about the other races, Zhao Hai knew that it was impossible. Everyone hated leaving their homeland. And now that there was hope of surviving, it was impossible for the Thunder Clan and the others to enter the Space. Therefore, Zhao Hai stopped himself from making a move.

Chapter 866: Devil Legion’s Mount

After the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King had left, Zhao Hai turned to Bingya and the others and said, “Everyone, I’ll be taking my rest as well. I hope you can fulfill the thing I’ve asked you.”

Bingya and the others bowed and said, “Mister can rest assured, we won’t disappoint you.” Zhao Hai nodded before he turned around and entered the cabin.

After seeing Zhao Hai leave, Bingya and the others also entered their cabins. Their rooms weren’t as good as Zhao Hai’s but it was still very nice.

Bingya entered his room. However, he didn’t immediately close it. Instead, he invited Ryder and Yehta over for some talks.

The Demons were very satisfied with their current state. The Royal Palace had been completed as their first building. At this time, Devil Legion soldiers were standing outside the castle. However, there were large quantities of Demons coming and looking at them.

The Devil Legion soldiers still had their indifferent posture, however, the death qi that was emitting out from them had vanished. Although people could still feel it, they weren’t as scared as before. This made the Demons puzzled. The Devil Legion used to be the most powerful unit of the Demon Race, they were essentially symbols of invincibility. What happened? Had the Devil Legion been weakened? This confused a lot of Demons.

The Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were also quite surprised after seeing these 100 thousand Devil Legion soldiers. They might look like ordinary Demons now, but the two of them understood that these Devil Legion soldiers had become more formidable than before.

In the past, having the Devil Legion felt like holding a double-edged sword. Anyone who saw them would immediately know that they were dangerous.

Now, although they weren’t as terrifying as before, the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King knew that these Devil Legion soldiers were at their most fearsome state, they had become sheathed blades. Everyone knew that a concealed weapon was more dangerous than an unsheathed sword. Hidden dangers were more scary in the battlefield.

At this moment, Zhao Hai entered the Space. After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King immediately went to meet him. After the three exchanged greetings, Zhao Hai looked at the Devil Legion soldiers and nodded, “Good, good. They look much better now. Right, it seems like it’s time to give them a mount.”

The Devil Legion was still primarily an infantry unit. In the past, because of necessity, they were given mounts by Zhao Hai. However, those mounts weren’t a match for them. But this time was different. Now, Zhao Hai managed to deal with the Taurus Continent while the Space had been upgraded by a few levels. At the same time, God-ranked magic beasts were beginning to be produced. A lot of these magic beasts can be used as mounts. The ones Zhao Hai prepared for the Devil Legion was actually being bred in the hell background.

Magic beasts that grew on other places might be strong, however, they were extremely wild and was hard to control. Giving such magic beasts to the Devil Legion would surely hinder their performance. Therefore, Zhao Hai specifically bred a lot of magic beasts in the hell background for the Devil Legion to use.

These magic beasts lived inside the hell background while the Devil Legion trained there. The purpose of this wasn’t only to train the Devil Legion. It was also to train the magic beasts. Once Zhao Hai equipped the Devil Legion with those magic beasts, their overall might would become stronger.

As for their wild nature, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid at all. The magic beasts weren’t as intelligent as the Devil Legion. Zhao Hai can even order the magic beasts to kill themselves, much less having them be mounts for the Demons.

The Great Demon King wasn’t aware of any of these. He looked at Zhao Hai blankly before he said, “Can Mister find a suitable magic beast for them?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s not a problem.” Then he released 100 thousand magic beasts. These magic beasts were black and were in the shape of horses. These horses had horns on their heads, but they had no hair, instead, they had thick leather armors. Their four hooves were on fire, the same was true for their tails, the tails looked like flaming whips as the horses moved.

These magic beasts were something that was produced by the Space, they’re called Nightmares. One shouldn’t underestimate them for being horses, they’re very ferocious beasts. Moreover, they eat meat and were essentially fire-type demons. With their God-rank strength, they were very frightening to behold.

Nightmares were also present in the Demon Realm. However, they weren’t so strong, at most they would reach 9th rank. These Nightmares had hairs on their bodies and didn’t look like fire-element beasts. At most, they had red hair, red tails and red hooves. Nightmares like what Zhao Hai released were unseen before.

Zhao Hai turned his head towards the Devil Legion and said, “Take them, they’ll be your mounts.” The Devil Legion soldiers nodded before they went and took a Nightmare for themselves.

However, matching weapons for the Devil Legion had yet to be found. At this time, they were currently equipped with full body armor, a spear, a sword, and some javelins.

These things were still quite good for the Devil Legion, however, Zhao Hai wasn’t satisfied. It’s a pity that he can’t make other weapons right now, they would need to wait for an opportunity later on.

After the Devil Legion took their Nightmares, Zhao Hai turned to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, you can arrange another batch of people to enter the Hell Space. As for the defenses in the spatial rift, let my undead take care of it. Have the rest of the Devil Legion take a rest inside the Space.”

The Great Demon King nodded as he left to take care of it. Demon Dragon remained by Zhao Hai as he said, “Mister, did the matter with Bingya and the others go bad? Or should we just leave them alone.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and smiled, “Don’t worry much about it. Besides, we still have another battle to fight. In the past month, the underworld’s dark mist had already drifted towards the Aksu Empire. Moreover, in one month, the people from the Atlanta Plane will bring their magic armors to the Ark Continent. Hehe, I want to see their expressions once they see the state of the Ark Continent.”

When he heard this, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but smile. The people from the Atlanta Plane wanted to attack the Ark Continent for resources and manpower. However, the Ark Continent has been completely turned to ruins. The various minerals of the continent had already been taken by Zhao Hai. Resources that remained were practically useless. At the same time, the population of the Ark Continent was gone. The people from the Atlanta Plane would surely lose greatly in this expedition.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Demon Dragon and said, “I don’t want to use the Devil Legion at the moment. Once we go to the immortal cultivation realm, that is where they will show their talent. My undead are simply more troublesome to upgrade. But first, we need to have the Devil Legion ascend to God-rank. This way, we would have some sort of foundation when we ascend.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, “Mister can rest assured, the Demons will not forget the humiliation brought to us by Lu Wei. Nor will we forget Mister’s great gift to us. I will also let Mister know that there are a lot of Demons who have your statue inside their homes.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think something like this would happen. He looked puzzled at Demon Dragon as he asked, “When did this happen? Why haven’t I heard of this? Did you force them?”

Demon Dragon smiled faintly and said, “We didn’t force them. They did it themselves to thank Mister. There’s no need for you to worry about it. And we also can’t force them to change their faith.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “It’s good as long they aren’t forced. If they treat me as a god, then that’s fine. Let’s just have this matter develop on its own.”

Faith Power would be useful for Zhao Hai, but he didn’t know how much nor was he able to feel it. Because of this, he wasn’t worried about it at this time. He didn’t have any intentions to force those who came to his Space. They were free to worship who they want.

Demon Dragon looked at Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but admire the young man. The Demons were aware of Faith Power, they were even planning to use it as a bargaining chip to allow them into the Space. However, they didn’t think that Zhao Hai wouldn’t open this topic. He just did what he said and invited all of them into the Space. He didn’t intervene with the Demons either. This made the Demon Dragon King admire him.

Chapter 867: Biggest Worry

After he came back out, Zhao Hai looked at the situation around the Thunder Clan and the others. Fortunately, nothing worth noting happened, everything was normal.

The fight this time was very hard. Although they managed to conquer Divine Will City, their ratio of casualties had reached about one to one. It can be said that if it wasn’t for Zhao Hai’s undead, the losses would have been much greater.

Although the three clans were prepared to have losses, the scale of their casualties was not what they expected. This wasn’t to say that Zhao Hai didn’t give an effort. In fact, if Zhao Hai wasn’t there, the battle would’ve dragged on for longer, causing more losses. It was because they had underestimated the might of the Divines who were fighting to the death.

Now, the three clans had their vitality injured. It would take some time before they recuperate their losses. It’s not just weeks or months, it might take years of perhaps decades.

What they lost this time was their elites. Elites of any race weren’t easily trained. Every soldier would need a long time and arduous training before becoming an elite. At the same time, the resources needed to nurture an elite was a lot. Armors, mounts, food, uniforms, everything required a lot of resources.

Behind every proud achievement of an elite unit was a mountain of resources invested. The three clans have been suppressed by the Divines for many years. Every year, they would pay the Divines a ton of tax, this caused their reserves to be small. Although the Divines were defeated, it was almost impossible for the three clans to train an elite unit in a short time, their foundation had been stretched thin.

Zhao Hai observed the three clans, they had returned to their own planes to relay the news to their people. Then they proceeded to construct defensive lines on their spatial cracks. This would allow them to defend their plane against attacks while only using a small amount of manpower.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the three clan’s actions. Instead, he was actually happy. In the past, when the three clans were moving together with him, he felt like his feet were being dragged. His special tactics simply couldn’t be used. Now that they left, Zhao Hai was able to breath. He was like someone who had let go of a heavy load.

Although Zhao Hai still had Bingya and the others inside the ship, their small number would have no influence on Zhao Hai’s actions.

The Taurus Continent was much bigger than the Ark Continent. In the past, Zhao Hai only had the Buddha Empire to deal with the Demons and the Divine Race. And now that he had the large Taurus Continent for himself, what else could he be afraid of? He can use the full might of the Space to make the Divine Race suffer here.

If Zhao Hai was confident in himself, then he was more confident in the Space. The incoming reinforcements might come from one continent, or several, but one thing was for sure; there will certainly be ultimate weapons coming over. Although ultimate weapons were strong, the Divines couldn’t use it lightly. It was just the same as the old man, he can use it but not for very long, otherwise his body will start breaking down.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai wasn’t weak. Currently, he has 40 Domain weapons, the Space’s transportation ability, and various other weapons. As long as he utilized them properly, the Divines would surely suffer.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but think about the Divine Realm. However, it’s a pity that the Space’s map only showed the Taurus Continent. At this point, he had no way of monitoring the Divine Race.

Besides this, Zhao Hai was also thinking about the Underworld and the Atlanta Plane. The underworld’s advancement was still going on while the Atlanta Plane was about to finish its preparations. As long as the people from the Atlanta Plane comes to the Ark Continent, another factor would be added to the current situation.

He wasn’t worried about any of these since he had the ample strength. Even if he dealt with multiple battles, he could still manage. The matter that Zhao Hai was most worried about was the laws rejecting him!

Zhao Hai can clearly feel that the repelling force on him was getting stronger, his time left was not much. He had never felt such a strong repelling force before. Even before the Divines had changed the laws of the Ark Continent, he hadn’t felt such a repelling force even if he was God-rank. However, he felt it here.

Although this made Zhao Hai puzzled, he can confirm that he may ascend soon. If he can’t solve everything when the time comes, then the Thunder Clan and the others would surely suffer under the Divine Race.

But as for the matter of how to solve everything, Zhao Hai was still clueless. Both Atlanta Plane and the Underworld couldn’t be easily dealt with. Even the Divines were hard to take care of. If the other Divines acted like the Taurus Divines, then the war would take a very long time. At that point, Zhao Hai was not sure if he would still be in this plane.

Zhao Hai also tried to see if the repulsion would disappear once the Hell King’s ship was stored in the Space. But the result left Zhao Hai disappointed. The repelling force was still there. Zhao Hai understood that this was because his strength had reached the threshold for ascension and not because of the Hell King’s ship.

However, Zhao Hai had found a temporary solution. When he hid inside the Space, the repelling force would get reduced. This was good news since it would extend his time. But in this case, his cultivation speed would be increased because of the benefits of the Space. Inside the Space, the Dao Lotus would have more energy to absorb. Zhao Hai was sure that if he stays in the Space for too long, then he would definitely ascend once he went out.

The Space can’t do everything, therefore Zhao Hai cannot stay here forever. It can be said that Zhao Hai was currently in a dilemma.

In order to reduce his cultivation speed, Zhao Hai had to reduce his time inside the Space. Since this was the case, Zhao Hai decided to deal with the minerals present in the Divine Realm in the meantime. He immediately sent large numbers of undead and iron armor beasts to mine the minerals in the Taurus Continent and had them sent to the Space.

Bingya and the others were confused regarding Zhao Hai’s actions. However, they didn’t ask about it. In the eyes of Bingya and the others, Zhao Hai had already seized the Taurus Continent, so why would he frantically mine all the minerals here? As long as he manages to repel the Divine Race, he can mine it whenever he wants.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t care to explain it to them. Every day, the undead scoured the continent for resources to mine. As long as something was present there, the undead proceeded to collect it.

There were plenty of high level Taurus Divine undead inside the Space. And these people were quite familiar with the  continent. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried about finding places to mine.

While he was mining, Zhao Hai also paid attention to the situation in the Divine Realm. Time passed quickly and before long a month had passed.

Now, the three clans had completed their defensive lines. And soon, the people of the Atlanta Plane would invade the Ark Continent. Information had also been sent by the foreign races. The allied armies of the Capricorn Continent, Scorpio Continent, Cancer Continent, Gemini Continent, and Leo Continent had left their continents and had proceeded to head towards the Taurus Continent.

When he heard this information, Zhao Hai didn’t worry. He was actually waiting for these people to arrive. To be honest, their departure was slower than Zhao Hai wanted it to be. Zhao Hai was now facing a two-way war. Once the Atlanta Plane invades the Ark Continent, it would be impossible for them to miss the spatial crack. After all, it was quite obvious.

As long as the Atlanta Plane’s people notice the spatial crack, they will certainly send people to investigate. When the times comes, Zhao Hai might face a battle on two sides.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t want to see this situation, he had no choice but to accept it. With the arrival of both the Divines and the Atlanta Plane, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to only fight one battle.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai had expected this kind of situation, so he wasn’t worried about it. The arrival of both parties wasn’t a bad thing for him. At most, it would just be mildly troublesome.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to divert the Atlanta Plane’s people to battle with the Underworld. But with speed of the underworld’s advance, it would take quite a long time before they become a problem for the Atlanta Plane. The Atlanta Plane would enter the southern part of the continent, it is for certain that they would meet Zhao Hai and the others first.

Zhao Hai thought and decided to leave the spatial crack’s defensive line open, allowing the people of the Atlanta Plane entry to the Divine Realm. He wanted to see how the Atlanta Plane and the Divine Race interact. He wanted to see which of them are more formidable.

Chapter 868: Gold Ben’s Plot

Gold Ben was sat on his bull. His face looked calm but his feelings deep inside was different. He had lost contact with his people one month ago. One can imagine that the situation back home wasn’t doing very well.

Upon thinking about this, his chest couldn’t help but tighten up as he lowered his head and coughed a couple of times. In the previous battle against Zhao Hai, Gold Ben had been injured forcing him to run away. This caused his body to not be as strong as before. And as he went about to convince the other continents to send reinforcements, his condition worsened. At this time, his vitality was damaged, his face wasn’t as rosy as before.

According to the estimate made by the Taurus Patriarch, with Zhao Hai’s strength, it would take about three to six months before the Taurus Continent gets captured. However, Gold Ben didn’t expect to lose contact with the Taurus Continent not long after he left. This made him restless.

Although he managed to invite five continents, the ultimate weapons only numbered two. With him, there were three ultimate weapons. To be honest, even he wasn’t convinced that these three ultimate weapons could defeat Zhao Hai. The reason why he decided to head back even if he was uncertain was because; one, he was worried about the the state of the Taurus Continent, two, he knew that it was close to impossible for the others to send him their ultimate weapons, the two ultimate weapons already costed him a lot. Third reason was because he chose to invite these people even if there was no sure way to defeat Zhao Hai. Even if they were defeated by Zhao Hai, this meant that Zhao Hai had just sown a seed of discord between him and the other continents. This would cause the other continents to formally declare war on Zhao Hai.

With these reasons, Gold Ben decided to specifically invite Capricorn, Scorpio, and Cancer Continents. Among other Divines, these people were the most probable to bear a grudge. As long as they fight with Zhao Hai, they wouldn’t be able to stop.

Moreover, these people were quite infamous in the Divine Realm. They were extremely militant, which caused them to become hotheaded and ruthless. They bore grudges and would seek revenge over the slightest problem. Most importantly, these people were greedy, even for a Divine. In fact, Gold Ben extremely disliked them.

But because of their character, Gold Ben was able to ask them for help. Gold Ben was good in using their greed and arrogance to draw them into this war.

After thinking about this, Gold Ben couldn’t help but look behind and gaze at the reinforcing army. Altogether, the five continents sent 100 million elite troops, there were also another 100 million troops from other races that were recruited. This resulted in an army numbering about 200 million troops. Additionally, they also had about 200 Domain Weapons as well as two ultimate weapons. It can be said that the five continents attached great vigilance towards Zhao Hai.

However, this didn’t mean that Gold Ben had his confidence in this army. He had seen Zhao Hai’s methods, he knew that if Zhao Hai wanted to attack a Divine Race city, then nobody would be able to stop him.

The military strength of the Taurus Continent wasn’t something to scoff at. But when these troops met Zhao Hai, they were all defeated. Although the Taurus already lost some troops and had the three clans rebel, for Gold Ben, this wasn’t the main reason. The main reason for this was because Zhao Hai was just too strong.

Although he managed to invite a 200 million strong army, he actually didn’t have the authority to command it. He had no way of directing their actions. These people still didn’t trust each other, so how could they show their full might? This caused Gold Ben’s confidence to go down.

However, he didn’t have any other choice but to believe in these people. He just hoped that the Taurus Divines were still in control. Otherwise, things would be even more troublesome.

The Taurus Continent began to show in the horizon. Upon seeing this, Gold Ben couldn’t help but get moved. But this agitation caused him to heavily cough once again. The Divines on his side couldn’t help but feel anxious.

As they slowly got closer and closer to the Taurus Continent, the more the Divines got anxious. All of them were paying close attention to their surroundings, afraid that they might run into Zhao Hai’s army.

Gold Ben didn’t hide any information about Zhao Hai to the five armies. He told them that Zhao Hai was very strong. After all, Zhao Hai was able to defeat him. Because of this, the five armies maintained their vigilance as they went on.

Before long, they arrived at the Taurus Continent’s coastline. Contrary to their expectation, they actually didn’t receive an attack. Their advance went smoothly. However, the Divines were soon able to discover an issue. They were already in the continent, but they were yet to see any Divine Race person. This caused their mood to sink.

Those who’ve been in the battlefield for a long time can understand what was going on. Before, they were looking down on the Taurus Divines for offering a huge price so that they could help. They thought that the Taurus Divines were too cowardly. But after seeing the state of the continent, they came to know that things weren’t as simple as they thought it would be.

The Taurus Continent was populous, and the place where Gold Ben decided to arrive at was in the rear of the Taurus Divines. If Zhao Hai hadn’t captured the Taurus Continent, then this place should be teeming with people. But now, they hadn’t seen even a single Divine. This caused their heartbeats to rise.

Gold Ben’s face was quite ugly. He also had an idea as to what this meant. Perhaps this meant that what he dreaded had already come true. However, he still wanted to try his luck, hoping that he was just mistaken.

In order to find answers as soon as possible, Gold Ben quickened his advance. He knew that a Taurus Divine City wasn’t too far away. If there’s no problem, then there should still be people in that city.

Those behind also followed suit and sped up. The desolate landscape had given them tremendous pressure. They also wanted answers as soon as possible.

Before long, the city in Gold Ben’s memory appeared in sight. But even before they arrived, Gold Ben’s expression got worse and worse. This was because he couldn’t see the magical shield surrounding the city nor any smoke coming out of the chimneys.

When Gold Ben and his entourage flew over the city, he couldn’t bear but despair, “No, this is impossible!!” Then blood spurted out from his mouth as he directly fainted mid-air.

The other Divines beside him immediately went and fetched his falling body. After that, they slowly descended into the city. Their eyes were full of tears, some were choked in sobs.

The city looked normal, the destruction inside wasn’t anything serious. However, it was completely deserted. The only thing they could see were bloodstains on the ground. These bloodstains had gone dark, it seems like it had been like this for some time.

All of these implicated that there was a fight. And since there were no Divine in sight, it meant that the Taurus Divines had been defeated.

These remaining Taurus Divines knew that this was their rear. If Zhao Hai managed to attack this city, then the other places had certainly fallen. Perhaps the Taurus Continent had already fallen into Zhao Hai’s hand.

The people from the other continents, after seeing the Taurus Divines, immediately understood what happened. They quickly issued an order to stop their armies’ advance and then sent people to clean the houses. Upon clearing everything, they proceeded to occupy the deserted city.

Naturally, Gold Ben and his people also lived inside the City. He was currently being treated by the others. After being nourished with healing magic for a long time, Gold Ben slowly opened his eyes.

Upon opening his eyes, Gold Ben saw the people around him. Gold Ben’s heart couldn’t help but pain. However, he steeled his heart as he slowly sat up. The Divines close to him were still in tears. He looked at them and said, “Don’t cry, it has already happened. What is most important right now is to take revenge. Where are the others?”

A Taurus Divine answered, “Supreme Elder, they stopped their advance and had occupied the City Lord’s Mansion.”

Gold Ben nodded as he took  a deep breath and closed his eyes. After some time, he opened his eyes once more, a new fire was lit inside his pupils. Then his body moved as he proceeded to stand up.

The Divines around him were immediately startled, a person quickly said, “Elder, take a proper rest. We need your healthy body for our revenge. If you fall, then the Taurus Divines will have surely ended.”

Gold Ben looked at the man and the others before saying, “We don’t have time to rest. Besides, I won’t die so soon. Stay here as I discuss matters with the others.”

After that, Gold Ben went out. Upon exiting the place, he found out that he was actually in a house right behind the mansion. He immediately found the direction and proceeded to head towards the Great Hall.

The people from the other continents were currently discussing the situation. A lot of the benefits that Gold Ben had promised was made in the assumption that the Taurus Divines were still standing. But now, it seems like the Taurus Divines were exterminated. Naturally, the advantages the Gold Ben promised had become impossible to attain. In this case, they were contemplating if they would want to offend a formidable enemy.

But after discussing for a long time, a decision had yet to be made. The hall had turned strangely quiet, everyone was calculating the pros and cons. They wanted to weigh if fighting this powerful enemy would be good or bad for them. If it was good, then they would think about the benefits. As for the bad, they were thinking about the price that they would pay.

After thinking for some time, a male Capricorn Divine said, “I think we shouldn’t participate in this war. The enemy that the Taurus Divines offended is too powerful. It would not be a good idea to offend him. And even if we beat him, our losses would surely be big. Moreover, there isn’t much benefit left for us.”

Chapter 869: Divine Race’s Huge Problem

“You short-sighted fool!”

A roar came from the hall’s door. The people in the room stared. The Capricorn Divine that just spoke wasn’t any ordinary person, he was the Capricorn Continent’s Supreme Elder, an ultimate weapon expert. It can be said that among those present, he held one of the highest status. Nobody dared to be impolite towards him.

But after they saw who came through the door, they shut up, it was Gold Ben. Gold Ben was also an ultimate weapon expert, him being the Supreme Elder of the Taurus Continent. He and the Capricorn Supreme Elder held equal status. Naturally there was no problem if he said those words.

However, the Capricorn Supreme Elder didn’t take take it lightly. He looked straight an Gold Ben and said, “Who do you think you are? You stray dog, why did you come here!”

Gold Ben looked at the Capricorn Supreme Elder and snorted, “Moroga, I’m scolding you for being a short sighted idiot. You decide to retreat after seeing the Taurus Divines being defeated? Where did your courage go? Are you still from the Divine Race? Have you ever thought about it, since Zhao Hai managed to conquer the Taurus Continent, what stops him from going over to your Capricorn Continent? Do you believe that you can deal with him alone? Even if you can defeat him, how much losses will your continent suffer? Think about this first!”

Moroga wanted to argue, but when he listened to Gold Ben, he said nothing. What Gold Ben said was true. Since Zhao Hai can destroy the Taurus Divines, why couldn’t he destroy the Capricorn Divines? If Zhao Hai decided to go to the Capricorn Continent, then their days would surely be the worst. After seeing that Moroga kept silent, Gold Ben said, “Zhao Hai isn’t someone that a single continent can handle. Moreover, he is a formidable Dark Mage, capable of turning everyone into undead. Most importantly, his undead will keep the strength that they had when they were alive. The more Divines he kills, the more God-rank undead he would acquire. At this point, I’m afraid he already had about 100 million God-rank undead. Even if it hadn’t reached 100 million, he should have at least 80 or 90 million. Think about it, 80 million God-rank undead killing their way to your continent. What kind of situation would you be in?”

A man next to Moroga suddenly opened his eyes. His eyes were very strange, it was entirely red. Although he only wore ordinary cotton garments, his aura was actually stronger than Gold Ben. This person was the Cancer Continent’s Supreme Elder, Jie Yu.

Jie Yu, with his red eyes, scanned the people in the room before saying, “We need to eliminate Zhao Hai. Just like Gold Ben said, if he gets more and more powerful, the Divines will not have any good days ahead. Moreover, since he just had eliminated the Taurus Divines, fighting here won’t affect ordinary people. If we wait, then the battle would be on our own homes. Uninvolved people would die.”

Jie Yu’s status in the hearts of the people was higher compared to Moroga and Gold Ben. This was because he had been a famous expert for many years. In the Divine Race, the amount of people he killed had made him well-known.

After listening to Jie Yu, the group couldn’t help but face the matter at hand. Gold Ben also added, “Elder Jie Yu is correct. Now that the Taurus Divines had been eliminated, we don’t need to worry about commoners being hurt. If one day Zhao Hai comes to your doorstep, then even if you defeat him, the battle would definitely hurt your people. I believe nobody wants to see this situation. And don’t say that there aren’t benefits in defeating Zhao Hai. Don’t forget, now that the Taurus Divines have been ended, the Taurus Continent is completely empty. Not only the Taurus Continent, there is also the our three vassal planes. Although they had rebelled, as long as we defeat Zhao Hai, subduing them would be an easy matter. Additionally, there is a spatial rift in the Taurus Continent that is connected to the Ark Continent. And inside the Ark Continent is a spatial rift to the Demon Realm. As long as we defeat Zhao Hai, not only would you gain the Taurus Continent, you also obtain the Thunder Plane, Barbarian, Plane, Winged Pegasus Plane, and Demon Realm. Isn’t this price enough? Think about what you will gain.”

Gold Ben thought that since the Taurus Divines had been eliminated, he might as well use these things to bait these people. This way, they would be more convinced to dealing with Zhao Hai and avenging the Taurus Divines.

Sure enough, when they heard Gold Ben, the people inside the hall couldn’t help but turn greedy. Moroga looked at Gold Ben and said “Gold Ben, are you telling the truth? Is there really a spatial rift to the Demon Realm in the Ark Continent? Don’t you dare lie to us”

Gold Ben coldly snorted and said, “Why would I use this to deceive you? It’s known that Zhao Hai and the Demons had allied to deal with us. You can even see Demons in Zhao Hai’s army. Moreover, the Demons being the first to arrive in the Ark Continent is something that every Taurus Divine knows.”

Moroga didn’t talk for a while, then he said, “Is Zhao Hai really that strong?”

Gold Ben snorted and said, “If he wasn’t, then the Taurus Divines shouldn’t have lost. The Taurus DIvines didn’t even last for two months. When I went to deal with him, I took 20 Domain Weapon experts with me. But when I faced him, he completely destroyed everyone except me. Now you tell me if he is strong or not.”

Moroga’s face turned ugly. At this time, it was Jie Yu who talked, “Why did you only tell us this right now?”

Gold Ben sneered and said, “If I said it before, will you come? Let me tell you the truth. We had already summoned the Deity twice. We asked him for help in destroying Zhao Hai. However, both attempts failed, which caused Zhao Hai to snatch two artifacts. The reason why Zhao Hai was so powerful was precisely because he has the Deity’s artifacts in his hands.”

After Gold Ben said this, a distinct sound of gasping can be heard in the room. To be honest, when they heard that Gold Ben had been defeated, they weren’t too surprised. In the thirteen clans of the Divine Race, Gold Ben wasn’t the strongest, he only ranked at about 7th or 8th strongest, both Moroga and Jie Yu can defeat him. Him being defeated by Zhao Hai only meant that Zhao Hai was stronger than him. And if Zhao Hai was against Jie Yu and Moroga? It was still hard to say.

However, upon hearing that Zhao Hai had defeated the Deity twice and even managing to rob his weapons, the Divines present couldn’t help but get startled.

The Deity was very strong. They had long known that the Deity uses his incarnations to fight. Although the incarnation might not be stronger than the Divines, his weapons were very strong.

Once the Deity’s incarnation gets destroyed, it was certain that the second one would be stronger. In the Divine Race, nobody can oppose the Deity, even Jie Yu can’t defeat him. But Zhao Hai actually managed to do it, acquiring two weapons in the process. This meant that Zhao Hai’s strength was beyond their expectations. At this point, he might even be stronger, with him having the Deity’s weapons.

Jie Yu was also frowning. As for why Gold Ben only said this now, his intention was very clear. Gold Ben wanted to drag all of them into the water. However, Gold Ben’s words gave them no choice, Zhao Hai was that big of a threat. He can threaten the entire Divine Race. They can’t do anything else but deal with Zhao Hai.

Nobody made any noise, everybody was frowning. On the other hand, Gold Ben was calm. He scanned the people in the room before he turned to Jie Yu, “Elder Jie Yu, we need to make proper arrangements. First, we should send messages to the other continents. We need at least two more ultimate weapons to be certain in dealing with Zhao Hai. Second, we need to be wary about the vassal races under your control. The Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus showed no signs before, but now they had rebelled. This is a lesson we need to learn from. We need to guarantee that your vassal races have no hidden plans. And third, we need to guard against the Foreign Races. Zhao Hai came from the Ark Continent where the Foreign Races also existed. Upon reaching the Divine Realm, it was almost certain that they contacted the Foreign God-ranks. Once they become aware of Zhao Hai’s strength, they would surely enter into an alliance. Don’t forget, we have been suppressing the Foreign Race all these years, they certainly won’t let this opportunity to retaliate go. If the other elders agree, then I want to propose an alliance of the ten continents. We need to work together in dealing with Zhao Hai. Of course, since the Taurus Continent has been destroyed, we just want our revenge. As long as someone kills Zhao Hai, I will give them my Taurus God Armor.”

Upon hearing Gold Ben, Moroga and Jie Yu stared. Then they quickly understood what Gold Ben meant. Gold Ben had nothing left, his family was killed, his body was injured. The only thing he had right now was his Taurus God Armor, nothing else. Therefore, he wants to use his Taurus God Armor as a bargaining chip to help him take his revenge. One couldn’t help but recognize how heavy this was. Almost all of them were tempted.

And there was nothing wrong with the other things that Gold Ben said. The Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus clan had long been vassals of the Taurus Divines. These three clans even participated in the fight against the Foreign Races. Their betrayal meant that other vassal races could also rebel. Additionally, with Zhao Hai being from the Ark Continent, a place that had a branch of the Foreign Races, he would definitely contact the Foreign God-ranks for cooperation upon arriving in the Divine Realm. The hatred between the Foreign Races and the Divine Race wasn’t small, it simply cannot be resolved easily. If the Foreign God-ranks didn’t use this opportunity, then they would be nothing more than fools.

These three points were enough to unite the ten continents against Zhao Hai. Not to mention Gold Ben narrating it properly as to fit his narrative.

After some hesitation, Jie Yu nodded and said, “Alright, we’ll do it according to what Gold Ben said. Moroga, Gold Ben, us three will collectively write the letters to be sent to the other continents. We’ll tell them about the situation here in the Taurus Continent, we’ll express your opinion as well. As for what we need to do at this time, I don’t want to rush an attack. Let’s build a base here and prepare to welcome the other armies. What do you think?” Moroga nodded and said, “I agree with Elder Jie Yu. but I think us three won’t be enough. How about we let everyone present here sign the letter. This way, it will be more convincing.”

Jie Yu nodded and said, “That would be best. While I write the letter, Gold Ben, are you familiar with the surrounding terrain? Go and draw a map, then select a place for us to build our base.” Gold Ben nodded and said, “I’ll take care of it. But I need to tell you that Zhao Hai has powerful magic cannons and javelins. Moreover, he obtained a ship from the Deity. This ship can ram the city and easily destroy its protective shield, it’s not affected by normal attacks either. I also heard about Zhao Hai’s actions back in the Ark Continent. He can use harassment tactics with his speedy cavalry to chip at our numbers while hindering us from going forward. I’m afraid Zhao Hai will use this method to deal with us. I want all of you to think about these matters as we establish our base.”

Jie Yu nodded, “Among all of us, only your people had fought with Zhao Hai. This matter shall be handed over to you. You need to build a proper base. If we can’t quell Zhao Hai here, then he would definitely be a disaster to the Divine Race.” Gold Ben nodded and said, “I’ll begin immediately.” Then he turned around and left.

After Gold Ben left, Moroga turned to Jie Yu and said, “Elder Jie Yu, do you think Gold Ben would really let go of his Taurus God Armor?”

Jie Yu replied, “He will. Gold Ben’s injury isn’t light. He can’t hide it. He also spat blood outside the city. At this point, he is surely using a secret method to delay time. However, it’s impossible for this method to last for a long time. Once his injury flares up, he will surely die. Therefore, he can dare to say that he’ll give us his Taurus God Armor.”

Moroga nodded, then he sighed and said, “This Zhao Hai is really fierce. I didn’t expect him to really eliminate the Taurus Divines. No wonder Gold Ben would want to take revenge. If Zhao Hai doesn’t get eliminated, he would surely be a huge trouble for the Divine Race.”

Jie Yu nodded, then he closed his eyes, nobody knew what he was thinking. After seeing Jie Yu like this, Moroga immediately prepared a pen and paper so that Jie Yu can proceed to write.

Chapter 870: Axe Island Shipyard

Axe was feeling great recently. His status in the family was now a step higher than before. Axe loved to adventure, which explained why he didn’t have the highest position in the family. And with the addition of having minimal contact with the family, Axe’s status of being the direct successor wasn’t very stable.

But this time, the information that Axe brought was too important of the O’neal family. After Axe came back, the family immediately prepared for their invasion of the Ark Continent.

With this, Axe’s status had become more and more stable. When the time comes, nobody could say anything if he were to succeed the family.

Because of this, Axe took care of the Ark Continent’s invasion very meticulously. In his mind, conquering the Ark Continent was a very good opportunity for him. As long as his family takes control of the Ark Continent, the position of Patriarch would certainly be his.

Axe was too enthusiastic with the preparations, there were matters he wasn’t involved with but he still chose to express his thoughts.

However, the O’Neal Clan’s Patriarch was Axe’s father. He became quite fond of his son, so when he saw Axe intervening on things he not only let it go, he even supported his son.

In the past, Axe didn’t pay much attention to the matters of the family, this worried his father. One could transfer one’s power to another person, but things were more complicated than that. If you can’t consolidate your power, then you would end up like a puppet in the end.

Axe was heading this direction, which worried his father. Therefore, after seeing Axe’s enthusiastic performance, the Patriarch encouraged him to intervene more.

In the Atlanta Plane, especially in the Magic Armor Continent, military operations were done large-scale, causing many things to be prepared.

Like the Divine Race, if they wanted to make an attack, they needed to carry out some preparations. They would need to assemble an army, amass supplies, provide weapons, and a lot more. These needed to be properly taken care of before making a move. If the military wasn’t prepared, then they would risk failure.

The thing the Atlanta Plane needed to take of the most were their magic armors. Both the offensive and defensive capabilities of the magic armors are formidable. However, magic armors had a weak point, it was power.

Magic armors weren’t like people, especially God-ranks. As long as people had enough food and rest, then they would be able to fight properly.

On the other hand, magic armors needed energy coming from a compressed energy source. The energy inside these sources came from extracting energy somewhere and compressing it.

This energy is the heart of each magic armor. Therefore, the Atlanta Continent  prepared a lot of these things. Otherwise, there would come a time where the magic armors would turn into useless pieces of junk.

It was precisely because of this that the preparation time for the Atlanta Continent was much longer compared to the Divine Race. The Divines would be able to finish their preparations in just one month while the Atlanta Plane would take at least two to three months.

Besides compressed energy, the Atlanta Plane also needed means of transportation before they can proceed to attack.

The magic armors of the Atlanta Plane were just like aircraft, but much more formidable. However, each magic armor can only carry so much energy source inside them. Once their source of power gets used up, then they could no longer fight.

But since the magic armors needed to be used for combat, they couldn’t just be allowed to fly by themselves. Because of this, if one wants to transport the magic armors, you would need a bigger vessel.

There were many means of transport in the Atlanta Plane. Some of these transport vehicles work in the sea while some work on land. But regardless of where they operate, one thing was for sure, these transport vehicles were very large.

Since these transportation vehicles were big and there weren’t any who can carry a lot of magic armors in one go, they needed to be taken care of as well before the Atlanta Plane can invade the Ark Continent.

In the Atlanta Continent where the spatial rift to the Ark Continent was located, was an island. It was quite a large island with no people in it. This wasn’t an issue since it could be regarded as a military base to be used as a jumping point for their invasion of the Ark Continent.

However, the island also presented a problem by itself. If they wanted to leave the island and proceed to the Ark Continent, then they would need a lot of transportation vehicles. There were a lot of transportation vehicles available in the Atlanta Plane, but how to bring them to the Ark Continent was a nuisance that needed to be taken care of.

Whether it be in the Ark Continent or the Atlanta plane, or even on Earth, constructing marine-worthy vehicles was much harder compared to land vehicles.

And this case was especially true for much larger vessels. Therefore, after hearing about the Ark Continent, the O’Neal family immediately constructed a shipyard on that island. Then they concentrated all of their shipbuilders there in order to make the ships.

The O’Neal family had no other way. The spatial crack was in a small mountain, there was simply no way for the family to send a large amount of ships directly to the Ark Continent.

However, for the Atlanta Plane who were constructing magic armors, making said ships only took a short time. In this case, a megaton-class ship can be made in just a month.

And because the O’Neal family was looking at this invasion with importance and had invested almost all manpower and funds into this project, they were able to make four megaton-class ships in two months.

These four huge ships aren’t just for transporting magic armors, they were also used to carry land transportation vehicles. These land-based vehicles were also a masterpiece of the Atlanta Plane. Each one can carry 20 magic armors. Moreover, it can go through all kinds of terrain. It also had a thick armor as well as weapons making it capable for combat.

The O’Neal family knew that to conquer the Ark Continent, they would need to rely on these land vehicles. Therefore, along with the ships, they also made a few of these vehicles.

The O’Neal family went all out on this gamble. As long as they conquer the Ark Continent, every investment would be worth it.

Axe was currently on the island with the spatial rift. This island was known to the family as Axe Island. After he came back home, it was named after him to commemorate his achievement. Axe took a liking to this island. He stayed on it as he supervised the shipbuilding efforts.

Today, it wasn’t only Axe who was present. His father, the O’Neal family Patriarch was also here along with other important figures of the family.

The reason they came to Axe Island was because the fourth ship was finally able to be launched.

In the O’Neal family, these four ships had been named, ‘Conquest’, ‘Victory’, ‘Glory’, and ‘Tyrant’. One can see from the names of these ships the ambition and expectations of the O’Neal family in conquering the Ark Continent.

The workers below were still busy. Axe was standing on the dock, a step behind his father. Axe’s father looked at the four big ships and couldn’t help but smile. He turned to Axe and said, “Axe, you did this quite magnificently. As long as the family occupies the Ark Continent, you will receive the highest honors.” Although Axe was feeling proud in his heart, his outside expression maintained its calm. He bowed to his father and replied, “It is my pleasure to benefit the family. Father, I want you to wait for a while. I’ll head to the Ark Continent and contact Zhao Hai. What do you think?”

Axe’s father smiled, but he shook his head and said, “Axe, there’s no need to be anxious. Wait until everyone is ready. When the time comes, it won’t be too late. Zhao Hai is very young and might be inexperienced, however, this doesn’t mean the same for the other people in the Ark Continent. If we aren’t prepared and you just brashly go there, you might alert them. This matter is crucial for the family, so we don’t want even a small mistake. Axe, don’t forget, you’re a young Patriarch, what you need to do is to overlook the entire situation and not to charge headfirst. That kind of thing is not befitting someone of your status, let others do it instead. Understood?”

Upon hearing his father, Axe didn’t talk back. Instead, he nodded and said, “Yes, father, I understand.”

Axe’s Father nodded, then he patted Axe’s shoulder and said, “Kid, I’ll be handing the future of the O’Neal family in your hands. You need to understand that there are things that even the Patriarch cannot help with. You can’t do everything by yourself, otherwise, what point is there for your position?” Axe remembered his father’s words. Although he didn’t have a thorough understanding about it, he also knew that this wasn’t the time to ask his father. He just nodded and stayed silent.

At this time, someone arrived by Axe’s father and kneeled down on one knee, “Reporting to the Patriarch. Everything has been prepared. We ask the Patriarch to give the honors!”

Axe’s father nodded. Then he went to the pier right by the Tyrant. On the bow of the ship was a bottle of wine tied by the rope. Axe’s father took the bottle and then swung it with all his strength towards the ship.

Chapter 871: Technomagic Civilization

However, what Axe and the others didn’t know was that everything that happened in Axe Island was completely known to Zhao Hai. These days, Zhao Hai had been constantly monitoring the state of the Atlanta Continent and the Underworld.

When the reinforcements from the Divines arrived, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately attack them. He wanted to see what those people decided to do.

Zhao Hai thought that the Taurus Divines would go to him in order to fight. But this time it seems like he had guessed wrong. The opposite party didn’t come looking for him, instead, they proceeded to build a base. Zhao Hai was quite surprised, but he soon calmed down when he understood that it was reasonable for the Divines to do so.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that the reason why this was the case was because the Divines weren’t fully confident in dealing with him. Every time the Divines met, they would use their magic formation to enclose the surrounding space, making Zhao Hai unable to listen in on their conversation.

However, Zhao Hai still understood why the Divines stayed put upon seeing their actions. But we wasn’t worried. He wanted to see how the Divines would want to deal with him.

Of course, Zhao Hai wouldn’t just let this pass. He had Bingya and the others send a letter back to the Foreign Races and had them see if there were any news about the vassal races of the Divine Race. However, this couldn’t be accomplished in a short time. Even if Zhao Hai provided them with messenger fishes, it was still impossible to send word.

Because of this, Zhao Hai’s attention was shifted towards Axe Island. The O’Neal family didn’t establish a formation on the island. Although the people from the Atlanta Plane were famous for their formations, in the O’Neal family’s minds, it was impossible for the Ark Continent to come to this island. Therefore, there was no need to build a formation.

Also, since they arranged magic armor guards on the island, they thought that magic formations would be redundant. For the O’Neal family, the time used to establish magic formations might as well be used for shipbuilding.

Since they didn’t have any magic formations, Zhao Hai can see every one of their actions quite clearly. Initially, Zhao Hai didn’t know what things the O’Neal family were busying themselves with. But soon, he understood the the O’Neal family were actually building a ship.

After seeing this situation, Zhao Hai guessed the situation of the Atlanta Plane. The Atlanta Plane was a Technomagic Civilization, a society much higher than the one back on Earth. However, they still haven’t managed to reach the cosmos like the Earth. At the very least, they had no way to build spaceships to transport people.

Zhao Hai didn’t make any attacks. He was afraid that the O’Neal family would be more vigilant once their island was threatened. He also wanted to see the expressions of the O’Neal family once they see the state of the Ark Continent.

Because of this, Zhao Hai observed Axe Island as it slowly built their four ships. To be honest, after seeing the O’Neal family’s efforts day and night, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pity them for their soon to be useless work. However, Zhao Hai reminded himself that they were enemies.

Under Zhao Hai’s gaze, four huge ships were constructed. After the last ship was built, Zhao Hai also saw Axe’s father doing the honors. As for what Axe and his father were talking about, Zhao Hai didn’t know.

The Atlanta Plane’s official language was different from the Ark Continent. Although they can also speak the language of the Ark Continent, they wouldn’t do so when they were talking amongst themselves, instead, they would talk in the words of the Atlanta Plane. This matter made Zhao Hai depressed.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried much about it. Now that the ships were made, it won’t be a long time before the O’Neal family invades the Ark Continent.

Currently, Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about time difference between the attacks of the Divines and the Atlanta Plane. At this point, it was impossible to estimate when things was going to happen. It seems like the Divines wanted to delay for some, the people of the Atlanta Plane were the same. In any case, Zhao Hai was prepared to fight a two-way battle.

At this time, Zhao Hai was enamoured by the construction of the megaton-class ships. This was especially true for the machines used in the process.

When the ships were beginning to be made, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get surprised. This was because the Atlanta Plane had achieved a degree of fully mechanized work.

Building a ship requires a lot of welding, cutting, and other processes. All of which were done by people who were inside magic armors. This astonished Zhao Hai.

These magic armors were different than transforming ones. They weren’t entirely humanoid. Some of them were car-shaped with mechanical arms, some were just mechanical arms.

Their shipbuilding was the most formidable one that Zhao Hai had even seen. Naturally, this was due to their magic machinery. It was the perk of being a technomagic civilization.

Technomagic civilization, this was the name Zhao Hai used to describe Magic-Machine civilizations. In the beginning, Zhao Hai thought that the Ark Continent was heading in this direction. This was because there were already people in the continent that used magic formations for stoves, refrigeration, and many other daily activities.

However, Zhao Hai was quick to discover that although the people of the Ark Continent were using magic formations, those who develop these formations weren’t looked at in a respectable way. People were only thinking about magic formations as something that can make their lives easier. They didn’t think about using it to make even greater things.

The Demon Realm, Divine Realm, and even the Thunder Plane and the others were almost on the side of a Magic Civilization. They knew so little about machines.

After being introduced to the Goblins, Zhao Hai felt that they were unfortunate. To Zhao Hai, Goblins were headed towards a technomagic civilization. It was a pity that they had been ruined.

The appearance of the Atlanta Plane made Zhao Hai aware that technomagic civilizations existed in this universe. Moreover, the Atlanta Plane seemed to have developed to a very advanced level.

After living on Earth for decades, Zhao Hai was clear about what technology can do to people’s lives. Therefore, Zhao Hai was hoping that the Ark Continent would steer that way. In Zhao Hai’s view, the Atlanta Plane have really developed the technomagic civilization to a high degree.

In addition to the machines used to make the ships, the ships themselves made Zhao Hai’s eyes shine.

The huge ship was a big hulking piece of metal. It was different to the Ark Continent’s iron ships. These big megaton-class ships can contend against the biggest freighter ships back on earth.

However, these big ships had magic formations all over their bodies. These magic formations made these four ships even more amazing in Zhao Hai’s eyes.

Zhao Hai didn’t understand the magic formations used in the Atlanta Plane. With their level of technology, no ordinary people could make sense of it.

Their magic formations were very strange. Although they looked the same, they actually do different things. After careful scrutiny, one could see a symbol or two being different. This small change could actually transform its function.

However, this wasn’t just a simple matter of changing a symbol. It took a lot of experimentation to find the right position, size, and even thickness of a certain symbol. All of these factors make magic formations very difficult to learn.

Zhao Hai already had a lot of Atlanta Plane magic formations in his hands. Some of them were copied by Cai’er from Axe’s mecha. At this time, Karen was researching these magic formations. Although the Goblins were innately skilled in this aspect, their civilization was mostly destroyed. Most Goblins would need several months of study in order to learn characters. At this point, they simply couldn’t help. Even if Zhao Hai had a lot of formations in his hands, he only knew a few of its uses.

Because of this, when Zhao Hai looked at the magic formations on the ships, he felt like he was reading a book that came from heaven. He simply couldn’t grasp the uses of the formations. Without knowing anything, it was impossible to put it to good use.

But this only made Zhao Hai even more curious about the ships. He now wanted to know what functions these ships had.

Aside from the magic formations, the design of the ships also made Zhao Hai’s eyes light up. The deck of the ship was divided into 30 layers. The upper layers were living quarters. The design of the rooms were very reasonable. The space on each one wasn’t very small. There were also some entertainment facilities inside.

The living quarters comprised of five floors. Starting from the sixth floor was where the magic armors were stored. The magic armors occupied a total of ten floors. After that were the garages, housing the land vehicles to be used. Zhao Hai already saw these vehicles, there were a lot of them in Axe Island.

Below the garage was the workshop. There were up to 50 stations in the workshop. All kinds of mechanical arms and devices were seen inside, all equipped for repairing magic armors.

On the lowest levels of the ship were components of magic armors along with energy sources. There were even equipment for compressing energy. One could say that the ship was fully equipped.

Seeing that the workers weren’t having trouble in building these four ships made Zhao Hai understand the level of technology the Atlanta Plane has reached.

Chapter 872: Everyone Is Busy

Zhao Hai was currently sitting in the Hell King’s ship along with Laura and the others. The layout of the room they were in was the same as the living room of the Space’s villa. Zhao Hai can’t stay inside the Space for a long time, so the only thing they could do was to make a room inside the ship.

The women didn’t object to Zhao Hai’s action. In their view, it was necessary for Zhao Hai to stay inside the ship, so they decided to accompany him. However, they were already used to the Space’s villa. It can be said that if they were to close their eyes, they could still manage to navigate the place. So if they change their environment, they may take a while to get used to it. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s decision also had them in mind.

At this point, the Hell King’s ship had become their home. Almost everything in the villa was moved to the ship, allowing Zhao Hai to stay inside it every day.

Bingya and the others had also been treating the ship as their home. Although they stayed with Zhao Hai in the ship all the time, they rarely went out, they were almost always inside their room. After seeing their actions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile.

Zhao Hai was currently watching the situation on Axe Island. The four ships were already launched. Moreover, their trial run had no problems. After the ships returned to the island and conducting a final inspection, they can then be allowed to set forth.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t actually concerned about this. What he was paying attention to were the armored land vehicles. Although Zhao Hai didn’t know the names of these vehicles, he wanted to call them armored transport vehicles. The armor on these vehicles were thick, and they were crawler-types. Their design was also angular, making them look quite mighty. Zhao Hai paid attention to the magic formations on those trucks. The formations looked like those used on the huge ships. With Zhao Hai’s current knowledge, he really can’t see anything different between the two formations.

But one thing made Zhao Hai feel strange. Although these vehicles were crawlers and were evidently heavy, their speed wasn’t slow, even if they were filled with magic armors. At the same time, their steering was also very smooth.

Laura was sitting right next to Zhao Hai, she had nothing to do at the time. She wasn’t as busy as Lizzy and Megan who were always busy with coming up with tactics. However, Zhao Hai had found out something about Laura other than her skill in logistics, she was interested in machinery.

It’s possible that she got it from Karen, but Laura had some sort of intuition after seeing magic formations and machines. It was just because Laura wasn’t paying attention to this aspect that her talent wasn’t discovered.

But now was different. Laura was looking at the Atlanta Plane’s magic armor and magic formations with deep focus. When the ships had made their testing voyage, Laura’s eyes were glued to the monitor. It reached a point where Zhao Hai was actually afraid that she would get fatigued, so he forced her to take a rest.

Laura was currently inspecting the armored vehicles at the screen. After some time she said, “Brother Hai, how about we modify the Hell King’s ship?” Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “Modify the ship? What changes would you like?”

Laura smiled and said, “Don’t you think that the attack of the ship is too limited? I want to make changes on this aspect.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “The Hell King’s ship is made according to the Space’s blueprints. I’m afraid it won’t be easy to modify. Make a blueprint first, if it looks good, I’ll try implementing it.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Brother Hai, I think you misunderstood. I don’t want to change the shape of the ship. Instead, I want to make modifications on its internal structure. There’s no need to remake the ship from scratch.”

After hearing this, Zhao Hai let out a sigh of relief before he said, “So it’s like that. Alright, but you still have to draw your plans. Otherwise, I won’t agree to it.” Laura nodded before she turned around and left.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura’s departing back and smiled bitterly, “I hope she doesn’t end up like father-in-law. That would be terrible.”

Meg, who was on Zhao Hai’s side, couldn’t help but chuckle as she said, “Just who made sister Laura stare at the monitor for too long? It’s too late to regret it now.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, “At that time, I just saw it as her being bored. So I allowed her to look at the monitor and relax. Who knew it would reach this point?”

Megan chuckled. Among Zhao Hai’s women, Meg talked the least and had the least presence. Even Ni’er’s presence can be felt more. Ni’er liked animals. Therefore, Zhao Hai had her stay in the Space at this time to look after them.

Ni’er was just too pure. Zhao Hai didn’t want to expose her to things she shouldn’t be in contact with. Having her stay with the animals was the best thing for her.

On the other hand, Meg usually had nothing to do. Her main job was to assist Zhao Hai along with Laura with the day to day activities. She would aid Laura while also arranging things for Zhao Hai and the others. At this point, Zhao Hai and the others were already used to Meg’s services. If Meg were to vanish one day, their lives would surely be turned into a mess. However, everyone knew that day won’t come.

Although Meg didn’t express herself more often, she still held Zhao Hai’s best feelings. Meg had been the longest person right beside Zhao Hai. This made Meg Zhao Hai’s favored wife.

Now, among Zhao Hai’s wives, there were only two of them who were inside the Space. One was Ruyen. Ruyen spent the least time with Zhao Hai. In addition to her previous status, it can be said if one were to rank Zhao Hai’s wives, Ruyen would place last.

Ruyen was currently inside the Space’s Wild Dragon Island. She was taking care of the island’s affairs, after all, it belonged to the Buda Clan.[1]

Naturally, she would stay by Zhao Hai’s side when evening came. She can just return to the Space during daytime. As long as the island was running well, she would have ample time.

Zhao Hai didn’t want Ruyen to get bored. And since Ruyen wanted to be useful, she asked to be the one to manage the island. In the end, Zhao Hai agreed to her proposal.

Another wife who wasn’t always by Zhao Hai was Berry. Berry was a Demon, and she wasn’t good in management. She also wasn’t good of taking care of Zhao Hai’s needs. What she was busying herself with right now was her clan.

Even before the Demons entered the Space, Zhao Hai already promised Berry to let her people in. After Zhao Hai allowed the Demons in, Berry came to Zhao Hai and asked him to give her people a place like Wild Dragon island so that the Succubi would be able to live in peace.

Naturally, Zhao Hai agreed to this request. However, he didn’t quite understand why Berry wanted to do this. Later when he asked Berry, Zhao Hai finally understood the state of the Succubus Race. In the Demon Realm, the Succubi were deemed to be the best choices to become wives. Therefore, almost every Demon wanted a Succubus for themselves. Because of this, a lot of Demons forced Succubi to submit. The Succubus Race hated this, therefore, it would be great if they could have their own island for them to live a quiet life.

However, Zhao Hai still felt strange. So he asked Berry about what how the Succubi would multiply if they isolate themselves from the others.

This point had already been thought about a long time ago. The Succubi wouldn’t always stay on the island. Every once in a while, an adult Succubus with enough strength would go to the mainland and train. At that time, they would have the opportunity to find a husband for their own. After that, they can choose to stay on the mainland or just borrow the male to impregnate them before they go back to the island. Everything would be up to that Succubus’ discretion.

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but be startled. He still couldn’t understand the decision made by the Succubus Race. However, he still agreed. It was because this wasn’t only Berry’s decision, the other Succubi wanted this as well.

Therefore, Berry would spend most of her time with her clan and then help whenever she was wanted.

Since Berry was Zhao Hai’s wife, her status was very special. Therefore, the Succubi were full of respect towards her, treating her as the leader of their clan. This caused Berry to be quite busy.

Zhao Hai didn’t oppose to Berry’s actions. Zhao Hai wasn’t possessive of his wives and he wouldn’t dare to treat them as his property. He hoped that his wives would find their own paths. Because of this, Zhao Hai was in full support to what Berry decided to do.

While his wives were busy, Zhao Hai, the man of the family, was relaxed. What he did every day was sitting on his room and staring at the monitor, watching the undead and iron armor beasts in the Demon Realm, the underworld’s advancement in the Ark Continent, the mining in the Taurus Continent, the Atlanta Plane’s progress in their conquest, and the Divine Race’s base construction.

These matters looked quite boring because of the repetition. However, Zhao Hai still needed to pay attention because these people were his enemies. As he observed their actions, he could analyze their future plans and find any weaknesses that they might have.

At the same time, Zhao Hai was also looking at the people inside the Space. The Goblins were living their usual lives. However, more and more Goblins had started to play with magic formations. This caused materials to be very much needed. Zhao Hai had Cai’er negotiate with the Goblins to do some tasks in exchange for supplies.

These tasks weren’t too difficult for the Goblins, and all of these were related to magic formations. The tasks were effective for the growth of the goblins. Every day, the Goblin race were becoming better and better.

Zhao Hai also paid attention to the Fishman Race once in a while. The one he paid most attention to was the Azure Dragon Snail.

The Azure Dragon Snail was a magic beast that Zhao Hai had received from the Fishmen. Its defensive capability was very formidable, making it an important weapon for the Fishman Race. The moment he received the Azure Dragon Snail, Zhao Hai immediately took care of it inside the Space.

Because of the Space’s ability to accelerate growth, the Azure Dragon Snail was now quite big. However, Zhao Hai didn’t go on and refine the snail. It was because he knew that the older the snail, the better it would be. Although there were a lot of Azure Dragon Snails in the seas, Zhao Hai didn’t make use of them.

Zhao Hai wanted to see the lifespan of these snails. After they die a natural death, only then would Zhao Hai take them for refining.

However, what happened next surprised Zhao Hai. The snails were living very well, none of them were on the verge of dying. At this time, the largest snail in the sea had reached a height of ten thousand meters. And even if it was quite large, it was still full of life, it seems like it could live for a longer time.

Zhao Hai did a test. He attacked the Azure Dragon Snail using a magic cannon made in the Ark continent. This magic cannon can threaten even God-rank experts. However, after hitting the snail, Zhao Hai saw that the snail seemed unflinched by the incoming attack. The snail just reached out with its dragon claw and met the beam of light. When the beam of light clashed with the claw, it vanished. It seemed like nothing even happened.

Zhao Hai was shocked upon witnessing this. He didn’t expect the snail to have this much defense. If he made them live for longer, who knows what they will turn into. It was because of this that Zhao Hai decided to just have the snails grow. He wanted to see how formidable they would be in the future.

At the same time, the Fishmen gained great benefits inside the Space. This was especially true for the Sea Dragons, the last of the Dragon Race. The place where they were in was still in the sea, but this sea was in the same background as Zhao Hai’s villa. The Sea Dragons stayed there for quite some time that Zhao Hai even forgot about them.

However, the growth of the Sea Dragons was beyond Zhao Hai’s expectation. Last time, Zhao Hai was able to see some God-ranks among them. Now, there were even more God-ranks. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be astonished by their growth..

* * *

Maybe the author meant Haven Island, I don’t know.

Chapter 873: The Atlanta Plane Invades

Time flew by quickly. At this moment, Zhao Hai was calmly standing on the Hell KIng’s ship as he gazed at a spatial rift. Naturally, there were no changes to the rift. However, Zhao Hai knew that something was happening on the other side.

Behind the spatial rift were the people of the Atlanta Plane. Their four ships had officially set forth as they rushed towards the Ark continent.

Zhao Hai thought that the most pressing matter for him right now was the Divine Race. However, he was left surprised when the Divines were still building their base a month after they arrived on the Taurus Continent. They were also using ships to gather resources and supplies in order to construct their fortress.

On the other hand, it was actually the people from the Atlanta Plane that needed to be looked after. After they finished making their four ships and amassing supplies, they immediately started to mobilize their soldiers. After a month, they set forth and proceeded towards the Ark Continent. They didn’t even send scouts in to see the situation.

This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised. These people from the Atlanta Plane didn’t look like amateurs. However, they didn’t send any forward scouts, they just went directly for the Ark Continent’s spatial rift.

The action made by the people from the Atlanta Continent appeared careless, Zhao Hai really didn’t know where their confidence came from. However, Zhao Hai cannot help but recognize how good a Technomagic civilization was. The four ships were fully equipped, they were like four cities that could move at sea.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai can see a lot of magic armors. These magic armors looked advanced, there were some magic armors that looked like the one Axe and his team used, the one with three transformations. And from what Zhao Hai can see, these magic armors had strength no lower than average God-ranks.

This time, the O’Neal family dispatched nearly a thousand advanced magic armors. And one could see that they were yet to go all out. There should be more of these magic armors inside the ships.

At this point, the four huge ships had already arrived at Blazing Island. The Tyrant stopped at Blazing Island and immediately released magic armors to kill all the magic beasts left there. After that, they took the magic cores inside the beasts.

Zhao Hai has been paying attention to the actions of the people from the Atlanta Plane. He wanted to know what they wanted to do. Fortunately, maybe because they didn’t sense any danger, the magic shield of the ship didn’t activate, allowing Zhao Hai to see what they were doing.

They took the magic cores to the small workshop at the bottom of the ship and compressed them to be turned into magic crystals.

Zhao Hai became surprised upon seeing all of this. He didn’t expect it to be like this.

Zhao Hai now knew what the magic armors need for energy, it was actually magic crystals.

This made Zhao Hai even more curious. He wanted to know how these magic armors would perform if they could use his crystals.

Although the people from the Atlanta Plane can turn energy into crystal stones, Zhao Hai can clearly see that the energy inside them couldn’t compare to his own crystals. In other words, the source used by the Atlanta Plane was inferior to Zhao Hai’s.

The magic cannons using normal crystals were not very good, but after using Zhao Hai’s crystals, they could kill God-rank experts. If those crystals were used on magic armors, how much stronger would they get?

Zhao Hai was now itching to get his hands on magic armors and then try them out. However, he also knew that this wouldn’t be easy.

Laura walked to Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Brother Hai, don’t worry, the Atlanta Plane can’t do anything. Didn’t you want them to reach the Ark Continent? The fight will begin soon.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I know. I’m not worried. I just can’t wait to see how the Hell King’s ship would develop with the magic armors. Its fighting potential would surely be even more amazing.”

Laura smiled and said, “What? The current Hell King’s ship is unable to satisfy you? How about my modifications?”

Zhao Hai smiled. Before, he wasn’t too enthusiastic about Laura’s modifications, he just went along with her ideas. However, he didn’t expect Laura to be earnest in her task. She carefully researched the ship and carried on a comprehensive modification to its interior. She even drew a very detailed blueprint. In Laura’s blueprint, the Hell King’s ship was divided into many regions. The uppermost layers would be the place where Zhao Hai and the others lived. The arrangement was the same as the one in the Space. There were even some greeneries inside, along with the Hot Spring and the others.

The following layers held the other residential parts of the ship. Altogether, it would be able to house ten thousand people. Moreover, each one of them would have their own rooms, the things inside each rooms were also quite good.

Under that was the warehouse. It can store a month’s worth of supplies for a hundred thousand people. Under that was the undead region where the undead stayed. It had an environment the same as the hell background, allowing the undead to cultivate inside.

On the bottom part of the ship was the Yin-Yang pond, the heart of the ship.

Actually, Laura didn’t have to spend such great effort on this. But since Zhao Hai cannot enter the Space at this time, the ship’s interior needed to be improved to make their lives more comfortable. The other living quarters and storage were something for outsiders to see, helping Zhao Hai to hide the secret of the Space.

In addition to these things, Laura also made changes to other places of the ship. The first one was the ram in front of the ship. In the past, the ram was integrated with the ship. Now, Laura separated it. This meant that it can be taken down. When the time comes, it can fly out of the ship and smash the enemy.

Then there was the ship’s pole. In the past, its only use was for hanging the flag. After the changes, it can now elongate itself and harden or soften at will, making it to swing on all sides. This allowed it to be used as a weapon whenever some enemies get close to the ship.

Besides these major things, Laura didn’t do any other changes. This was because if they changed the ship too much, then they might need the help of the processing machine.

In addition to these, Laura also selected the undead to be stored inside the ship. All of them were God-ranks and God-rank magic beasts. Although the builds of these beasts were quite huge, Zhao Hai’s undead can transform, allowing them to turn into humanoid forms. They would stay inside the ship in the humanoid form and just transform  back during battle.

Zhao Hai became very interested in these modifications. Although they looked minor, these changes actually improved the Hell King’s ship’s performance.

Zhao Hai was aware that he can only act like an overlord because nobody can contend with the ship in this plane. He seemed like a grown man playing with children, he was bullying them, basically.

But now that he was being repelled more and more, a day would come where he would ascend. When that time comes, the Hell King’s ship wouldn’t necessarily be the most powerful thing present. He would encounter more powerful enemies and even more powerful weapons.

At this time, nobody can approach and threaten the Hell King’s ship. But this wouldn’t be true in the Immortal Cultivation Realm. Laura’s modifications of the ships needed to be carried sooner or later.

When he heard Laura, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, “It’s good, very good. Right, what are the others doing?”

Laura smiled and said, “Not much. Lizzy and Megan are looking at the maps of the Taurus Continent and the Ark Continent in preparation for fighting the Divines and the people from the Atlanta Plane. Meg is currently researching new food. Ni’er is taking care of the animals in the Space. Ruyen is still busy on the island. I heard from Grandpa Green that Ruyen is planning to set up a Merchant Union in the Continent. Berry is with her clansmen, she’s now the busiest among all of us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “How about you? Why don’t you study blueprints in the next few days? Aren’t you interested in those magic armors? You can have Cai’er provide you with a three dimensional figure of the armors.”

Laura smiled and said, “I’m quite interested. I’ve tried to make blueprints to make them, but I discovered that the metals used to make them aren’t common ones. It should be a special type of alloy. If those magic armors are made with common metals, they would disintegrate in no time.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Who knows how long the Atlanta Plane researched those metals. Making magic armors surely wouldn’t be simple. Go and look at the magic armor made by the Goblins. Their magic armor shouldn’t be that complex. Not to mention the magic formations used are much simpler. Don’t be anxious and take it slowly. Wait for me to grab a few magic armors and then you can study them.”

Chapter 874: Plan of Research

Laura smiled and said, “It seems like if we want to make magic armors, we would need to ask the Dwarves for help. Right, the Elves as well, they’re quite good at engraving magic formations.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Don’t tell them yet. After we get the magic armors, let’s have the Space analyze the magic armors first.This way, we’ll know what alloy to use when we make them.”

Laura nodded, “Alright, but I hope that we can involve the Dwarves and Elves with this. This way, they won’t be too idle. You should know that both the Dwarves and the Elves have their own innate skills. Dwarves are especially sensitive to metals, leagues more compared to the Humans. At the same time, the Elves are good at carving magic formations. If we have them help, we would gain more benefits while making magic armors.”

Zhao Hai thought about it and nodded. He hadn’t thought about it before. He was too focused on having the Goblins research magic formations to prepare making magic armors. He didn’t think that he could allocate different jobs to different people.

At this point, Zhao Hai had a certain understanding when it came to magic formations. He knew that researching magic formations couldn’t be done in a day. Besides selecting the metal, one would need to be skilled in engraving the formation itself. Once a small problem occurred during engraving the formation, the entire thing would have to be scrapped.

The most skilled when it came to engraving formations were the Elves, it’s their innate skill. Moreover, they’re quite dedicated to this craft.

On the other hand, the Dwarves were also dedicated to everything concerning metals. Humans couldn’t compare to their expertise. If the Elves and the Dwarves join hands, then they would certainly be helpful in making magic formations and magic armors.

Zhao Hai only thought about it now because he wasn’t thinking along this line before. To be honest, although he also took the Goblins into the Space, Zhao Hai still regarded the Ark Continent’s people as more important.

In his heart, the people from the Ark Continent were his family and friends. This was where he had lived for a long time, therefore, the people from the Ark Continent could already be considered as his own kin.

The next were the Demons. Although the Demons had been their enemies in the past, Zhao Hai didn’t actually hate them. Moreover, the Demons didn’t hate him as well, they even voluntarily entered the Space. Because of this, the Demons also held a high status inside Zhao Hai’s heart.

Then there were the Goblins. It can be said that Zhao Hai didn’t have any connection with the Goblins. He just wanted to free them and borrow their skill in magic formations. Because of this, he had them live inside the Space.

Then finally there were the Divines. The discord between Zhao Hai and the Divines couldn’t be resolved. But since he didn’t want to bother himself too much with the Divines and also didn’t want to wantonly massacre the innocent, he could only come up with imprisoning them in the Space as a solution.

Because of this hierarchy in these people’s status, Zhao Hai had the Goblins research the magic formations while leaving the Dwarves and the Elves alone. Zhao Hai wasn’t the type of person to seek for repayment. If Zhao Hai were to ask them for help, then it would be akin to him asking them to return the favor.

This wasn’t the case for the Goblins since he didn’t have any connection to them. It was appropriate for the Goblins to help him with these things.

Now, after being reminded by Laura, Zhao Hai managed to think it through. He would try asking them if they would want to help in this project, he wouldn’t force them. In any case, they liked to do these things.

Laura understood what Zhao Hai was thinking about, so when she saw Zhao Hai nod, she smiled and said, “Brother Hai, don’t think about it too much. We can ask the Dwarves and the Elves in Wild Dragon Island for help first. Then we’ll have the more intelligent Goblins come and mingle with them. This way, they can be familiar with each other. When the time comes, the Goblins wouldn’t be afraid of the Dwarves and the Elves. At the same time, the Dwarves and the Elves could also accept the Goblins. This way, they could smoothly research magic armors together.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, it’ll be good for the Goblins to have contact with the other races.” Zhao Hai understood the reason why Laura wanted the Goblins to mingle with the other races. In the past, the Goblins suffered under the persecution of the Divine Race. Not only was their civilization ruined, their spirits were shattered as well. Zhao Hai discovered that the Goblins held a strong vigilance towards other races. Because of their fear, they turn dull upon meeting other people. Therefore, Laura wanted the more intelligent Goblins get used to the other races to remedy this problem.

However, this matter couldn’t be done in a short time. The Goblins had just managed to touch magic formations. Even if they want to help, they couldn’t provide that much. They still need time.

At this time, Bingya walked out from his room. Bingya and the other had been following Zhao Hai’s side for quite some time. However, they still don’t know what Zhao Hai was thinking about. They only thought that Zhao Hai wanted to occupy the Taurus Continent. They would never guess that Zhao Hai was only staying here because he was waiting for the Divine Race’s ultimate armor as well as the Atlanta Plane’s magic armors.

However, Wolf Tribe Bingya was still very thankful towards Zhao Hai. The Taurus Divines were arch enemies of the Foreign Races, especially the Beastmen. Because of this, not only did Bingya not blame Zhao Hai for destroying the Taurus Divines, he even thought that he did great.

After seeing Zhao Hai and Laura standing at the ship’s bow, Bingya couldn’t help but hesitate. He was afraid of disturbing Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai had also noted Bingya’s presence, he smiled faintly before turning his head to Bingya and said, “Bingya, what’s wrong? Is there a problem?” The time they spent together wasn’t short, so Zhao Hai had become comfortable in calling him Bingya.

Bingya went towards Zhao Hai and bowed, “Mister, I just received word from the clan. It seems like the Divines had intensified their surveillance towards their vassal races. As long as they discover something wrong, they would immediately send troops to deal with it.”

Zhao Hai stared, but then he nodded and said, “No wonder the Divines had been motionless for a long time. So they were doing this. They want to stabilize their rear first before trying to deal with us. Hehe, interesting.”

Bingya looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, what should we do?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Is it really that bad? The Divines are used to these kinds of things. And they also know that the reason why the Taurus Continent fell was due to the rebellion of the three clans. Therefore, they need to increase their vigilance towards their vassals. They may even quell some numbers off of their vassals. But the more they do this, the more hatred those races would have towards them. If they can’t crush the rebels quickly enough, then the Divine Race’s backyard would get more and more chaotic. This is good for us.”

Bingya stared, then he nodded. He couldn’t help but agree to what Zhao Hai said. The foreign races had been fighting against the Divine Race for a long time, so Bingya understood how tyrannical the Divines were. Upon knowing that their vassals can perform a rebellion, they would certainly become more ruthless. Quelling numbers was only one of the more simple methods.

Bingya also knew that the already discontented vassal races would be more angry when the Divines suppress them even more. This would only speed up the planned rebellions. As long as races revolt together, the Divines would have to split their troops. When the time comes, Zhao Hai could then annihilate the Divines one by one.

After thinking this through, Bingya nodded and said, “Alright, we’ll be depending on Mister. I’ll tell the clan what mister said. But Mister, we should take action against the Divines. If they successfully make their base, then we would be at a disadvantage.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and smiled, “Don’t worry about it. Just let them be. It would be impossible for them to be in their base forever. As long as they go out and make an attack, I can deal with them then.”

Bingya didn’t say anything about this anymore. He just nodded and said, “I’ll be reporting to the clan now.” Then he turned around and went to his cabin.

Laura looked at Bingya and then turned her head to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, the Foreign Races didn’t make Bingya and the others go back. Do they want to monitor you? How can we just leave them be? We already have enough strength to deal with the Divine Race ourselves.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If you don’t pull them into the water, then how could you expect them to fight with the Divines? As long as the Foreign Races gets weakened, then the more chances we can have to get their ultimate weapons. Of course, it would be better if we can have them migrate to the Space.”

When Laura heard this, she couldn’t help but laugh. She now understood what Zhao Hai had in mind. This was actually the same plan that Zhao Hai had on the three clans. Pulling the Thunder Clan and the others along would not only help fight the Divines, but they would also get weakened. At that time, when Zhao Hai directs the Underworld and the Atlanta Plane into the Divine Realm, those three clans would surely allow themselves to be taken into the Space.

The sooner those people enter the Space, the sooner they could worship Zhao Hai. When the time comes, Zhao Hai would have more Faith Power.

Although this method wasn’t clever, it was actually the most effective. If Zhao Hai goes on and force them, then he would be wasting time. And time wasn’t exactly on Zhao Hai’s side right now.

Chapter 875: The O’Neal Family’s Turning Point

The reason why Zhao Hai always wanted to add people inside the Space was primarily due to its emptiness. There were too little people inside, and it would be a waste if the massive Space remains uninhabited.

Second, because of Faith Power. Although Zhao Hai wasn’t too clear about what Faith Power can do to cultivation, he knows how hard it was to collect. Therefore, it should be quite a valuable resource.

When Zhao Hai ascends to the cultivation world one day, wanting to collect faith power wouldn’t be so easy. Lu Wei needed to be assigned to this place in order to collect faith power. One could see how rare faith power was in the Immortal Cultivation Realm.

If the people in the Immortal Cultivation Realm were very strong, then it would be almost impossible for Zhao Hai to collect faith power there.

Moreover, in the Immortal Cultivation Realm, planes already had allocations. Every available resource should have already been claimed by the major powers. If Zhao Hai went to the Immortal Cultivation Realm and collect faith power, then he might risk offending these people. Zhao Hai already offended Lu Wei, it wouldn’t be wise for him to gain even more enemies.

Lu Wei’s incarnation was already powerful, this meant that his true body would be even stronger. However, Lu Wei wasn’t the strongest person in the Immortal Cultivation Realm. It’s certain that there were more people stronger than him. Zhao Hai didn’t want to go to the Immortal Cultivation Realm just to get chased around, that won’t be very fun.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai was afraid that there would be people in the Immortal Cultivation Realm capable of invading the Space. If a person like that exists, then Zhao Hai would be in a major trouble.

Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to make ample preparation before he gets kicked out and ascends to the Immortal Cultivation Realm. He wanted people inside the Space so that he won’t need to look for them once he went to the Immortal Cultivation Realm. In the meantime, he also wanted to analyze the magic armors and the ultimate weapons. This way, he would have more means of self-preservation.

——————————————————————-

Axe was currently standing on the Tyrant’s bow. He liked the name ‘Tyrant’. Everytime he heard the name, he always felt his passion burning inside him.

It had been a few days since they had arrived on Blazing Island. No changes happened to the island since he first came here. As for the magic beasts, Axe wasn’t polite with them as he sent his people to directly eliminate them all. They gained some magic crystals along the way. But even if they weren’t a lot, Axe was still feeling happy. He liked this feeling of conquest.

After that, they began to head northbound. Based from what he heard from Zhao Hai, the Ark Continent should be this way.

The Tyrant wasn’t the flagship of the fleet. The ship at the head of the fleet was the Glory, Axe’s father was on this ship. Axe made the request to stay on the Tyrant.

Axe disliked staying under his father’s gaze. Although he can learn a lot of things being by his side, Axe felt uncomfortable being there every day. Therefore, he took the initiative to leave the ship. The reason he gave was that he wants to study on how to command a ship.

This reason was quite reasonable, so Axe’s father immediately agreed to let Axe take command of the Tyrant. At the same time, he also arranged an experienced first mate to guide his son.

Before this, he really didn’t care about taking command of the ship. However, Axe came to discover how great the taste of authority was. It was like an expensive glass of wine, not many people were able to taste it.

It had been a few days, but although they had been sending scouts ahead, they were yet to find land nor did they see any ships. This made Axe confused.

Their ships weren’t slow. This was a powered ship, not any old sailing vessel. But their ship was yet to find the continent even after several days of travelling. It seems like Blazing Island was farther to the continent than Axe first thought.

Another thing made Axe puzzled. From what he comprehended during his talk with Zhao Hai, the Ark Continent didn’t have machines. Therefore, the Ark Continent should be using sailing ships. With how slow sailing ships were, how come Zhao Hai arrived at Blazing Island? And why was his timing so appropriate? There shouldn’t be something wrong, is there?

After thinking about this, Axe shook his head, eliminating these thoughts. He didn’t dare to think about it since he was afraid that it would be true. If it was, then this expedition would be a huge blow to the family.

Time passed by, after two days, Axe couldn’t calm himself down. Most of his time every day was spent on the deck looking for signs in the horizon. He did this even if he knew that a scout would come if the continent was spotted.

Axe stayed on the deck since he was unable to settle himself while being inside his room. At this time, black spots appeared on the skies. Axe’s mind couldn’t help but shake, the scouts had come back.

Before long, a magic armor flew towards the Tyrant. This magic armor was in its aircraft mode. Among all of its form, the aircraft mode was the fastest.

The magic armor transformed into its humanoid shape before it set foot on the ship. Then the hatch opened as a person jumped out. Then the person went towards Axe before he bowed and said, “Young Lord, we’ve discovered the Ark Continent. It is definitely the Ark Continent, not just a boat. It’s in the east, our direction has been a bit off.”

Axe excitedly nodded and said, “Good, good, fantastic. Has this information been related to father?”

The person nodded and said, “Someone went to report to the Patriarch. The Young Lord can rest assured. However, …” After the person spoke up to here, he had a hesitant expression.

Axe’s heart couldn’t help but sink. He immediately asked, “What happened? Tell me. Speak!”

The person looked at Axe and said, “Although we weren’t too close to the Ark Continent, something felt strange to us. There are no smoke coming from the land, there aren’t any ships on the seas as well as the shore. It’s quite strange.”

Axe’s heart sank deeper. He immediately said, “Did you relay this to father as well? What did father say?”

The person shook his head and said, “I don’t know whether the Patriarch has been informed or not. We scouts separated as we came here.”

Axe nodded, then he turned to his men and said, “Prepare my magic armor. I need to go to the Glory.” The servant behind him immediately nodded before he turned around and left.

Before long people came and towed Axe’s magic armor out. Axe didn’t say anything as he immediately rode his magic armor and then flew towards the Glory.

Axe’s position wasn’t too far from the Glory. The four ships advanced in a straight line. The first was the Victory, which acted as the vanguard. Then the Glory, then the Conquest, and finally the Tyrant.

It didn’t take a long time before Axe arrived at the Glory. After his magic armor landed, he immediately jumped down and hurried towards his father’s room.

Upon arriving outside the room, the two guards immediately bowed to him as one of them said, “Young Lord, the Patriarch already told us that if you arrive you should see him immediately.”

Axe nodded before pushing the door open and entering the room. Then Axe stared, it was because he wasn’t the only visitor inside. There were famed commanders of the family present. This time, they joined in to command the battle against the Ark Continent’s ships.

After seeing Axe arrive, the Patriarch nodded and said, “Axe, it’s good that you came. Take a seat.” Axe gave everyone inside a salute before sitting down.

When Axe sat down, his father said, “We’ve already discovered the Ark Continent on our east side. But a strange phenomenon sprang out. There aren’t any ships on the shoreline. This is very strange. I’ve already sent the scouts once more to approach the continent. We need to know whether something happened.”

The people inside the room nodded. Then one commander frowned and said, “Patriarch, what do we do if we find nobody in that continent?”

Axe’s father paused for a moment before he said, “Don’t worry. If there are no people in the continent, it could only mean one of two things. First, it means that we haven’t found the right place, it’s not the Ark Continent but a deserted one. The possibility of this happening is small. The second possibility is that something happened to the continent, the people simply left. This is good for us since we won’t need to use force. In any case, what we want here are the materials and the minerals. The people won’t matter too much.”

The group nodded. At this time, Axe stood up and said, “Father I apologize. I’ve been neglectful in my earlier scouting.”

Axe’s father waved his hand and said, “I can’t blame you for this. If you went to the Ark Continent at that time, then you might alert them. Maybe there really are no people in the continent. Let’s us go along with the plan. You can go and see Zhao Hai while we wait and see.”

Axe nodded, then his father turned to the others and said, “Whether there are people in the continent or not, we still need to prepare. The ships had already fixed their heading and are now going towards the continent. We need to build a base there in the shortest time possible and anticipate the arrival of the continent’s troops. It seems like the Ark Continent is larger than we imagined. This is good news for the O’Neal family. A bigger place means there are more things for us to get. This will be a turning point for our family.”

As soon as the group heard this, their spirit couldn’t help but shake. Right, the Ark Continent being bigger was good news. If the Ark Continent was big, then there would be a lot of magic beasts there. Magic beasts bring forth magic crystals. The more magic beasts there were, the more crystals the O’Neal family would gain. There were also the minerals. With such a huge continent, it would be impossible for it to not have minerals. These minerals were also important for the family.

After many years of mining, the Atlanta Continent’s ore deposits had gone very low. And without these deposits, there would be no way to make more magic armors. Without magic armors, their family would be weakened. It would be a negative chain reaction.

Axe’s father looked into the eyes of those present and said, “Although the Atlanta Plane is big, we share it with the Warriors and the Mages. Dealing with those two would take a long time. However, the Ark Continent would only belong to us, the O’Neal family.  It’s not even that smaller than the Atlanta Plane. Think about it, we have a place like the Atlanta Plane as our base, how exciting would that be.”

The eyes of those present were shining. They couldn’t help but dream about the scenario that Axe’s father described. If the O’Neal family were to have a place as big as the Atlanta Plane as their base, then who could contend against them in the Atlanta Plane?

Axe’s father looked at the group and gave a satisfied nod, “Alright, I’ll speak up to here. You go back to your stations and prepare. We will take the Ark Continent. Kill all those who dare block us! O’Neal Family, Victory!!!”

The group stood up as well as Axe, all of them loudly shouted, “Victory!!” Just as Axe was about to leave, he was stopped by his father.

Once all the other commanders had left, Axe’s father sat him down and said, “When you met Zhao Hai, did you find anything peculiar?”

Axe stared, but he understood his father’s question. His father still wasn’t too comfortable about the state of the Ark Continent. But since Axe didn’t see anything peculiar, he shook his head and said, “There isn’t anything special. When he saw the magic armors for the first time, he had a scared and curious expression. I can affirm from this that there are no magic armors in the Ark Continent. At that time, he was dressed like a Mage. He also had a magic staff on his hand. He can fly which meant that he should be 9th rank. I can’t feel any God-rank aura around him.”

Axe’s father nodded and said, “So it seems like our speculations are true. It’s quite possible that there are no God-ranks in the Ark Continent. This is good. However, I’m quite worried about something. Why would Zhao Hai be by the spatial rift? He had no reason to be there.”

Axe knitted his brows, he was thinking the same thing.

Chapter 876: Turbid Waters Are Good For Catching Fish By Hand

Axe wasn’t a fool. He understood what his father was thinking about. He was also confused about what was happening in the Ark Continent.

After seeing Axe’s expression, Axe’s father nodded secretly inside. He felt that Axe had matured in the recent days, this was what he wanted to see.

At this time, a report suddenly came in from outside, “Reporting to the Patriarch, the scout has come back.”

Axe’s father stared for a moment before a smile appeared on his face, then he immediately said, “Let him in.” Then the guards complied and then opened the door to let the person in.

The scout was a middle aged person, likely over 30 years old. However, he looked spirited in his tight suit. This suit was also necessary for those who drove magic armors.

The man arrived in front of Axe’ father and then gave a salute, “i have seen the Patriarch.”

Axe’s father nodded and said, “Lev, tell me the situation.” Naturally, it was impossible for Axe’s father to know about every magic armor user in the family. However, Lev was an exception. He was a God-rank magic armor driver. Moreover, he ranked among the best God-rank magic armor drivers in the family. The magic armor he drove specialized in stealth. Since it’s important that they know the situation regarding the Ark Continent, Axe’s father decided to send Lev out. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have sent him for common errands.

Lev’s deep voice answered, “It’s highly probable that we’ve spotted the Ark Continent. But the strange thing about it is there is nobody present in their cities by the shore. There’s no sign of any battle either, it looks like people just moved by themselves. All the houses are empty. And from the way the dust had settled, the place had been empty for over three months.”

Axe’s father stared. Meanwhile, Axe’s expression changed as he looked at Lev and said, “Over three months? Then does this mean that when I met Zhao Hai, the Ark Continent was already like this? Lev, did you only look a at the cities? How about the other parts of the continent?”

Lev replied, “I looked through two cities and some villages. Same thing, everybody had moved out. Everything that can be of use has also been taken away. Moreover, it seems like they weren’t hurried upon leaving. The place was cleanly left behind.”

Axe’s face turned difficult as he turned to his father. Axe’s father looked at Axe and then smiled, after that, he comforted his son, “Axe, it’s fine. Don’t think about it too much. It seems like Zhao Hai has deceived you. When you met him, they were already moving away. But no matter where they moved, the Ark Continent is still here. They can’t take the Ark Continent with them. It’s fine as long as we get the continent for ourselves. Lev, you go take a good rest.” After giving a salute to the two, Lev turned and left. After Lev went out, Axe’s father frowned and said, “Things are more complicated than we thought. Why did the people from the Ark Continent move out? And where did they move? The appearance of our spatial crack shouldn’t be the reason why they moved away. It seems like we need to check much further into what happened.”

Axe calmed down as he sat on one side of the room. He’s really angry at Zhao Hai’s deception. He thought that he had cheated Zhao Hai, as it turns out, he was the one being cheated.

After thinking about this, Axe couldn’t help but clench his jaw. The feeling of being played wasn’t very good.

Axe’s father looked at Axe and smiled, “Axe, don’t be mad, its fine. You’ll get to meet more of these kinds of things later on. Go return to your ship, manage it well.”

Axe took  a deep breath, he nodded before giving his father a salute and leaving. Looking at Axe’s departing back, his father smiled. He didn’t say anything else. In his mind, these were things that young men need to experience.

What Axe’s father didn’t know was that Zhao Hai was observing them. After Axe went out of the room, Zhao Hai sighed and said, “It’s a pity, I thought we’d have much more things to get out of this. But I didn’t expect Axe’s father to be this insightful. The O’Neal family is really extraordinary.”

Laura gave a nod, then she turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, did you manage to translate it properly? To be honest, I’m quite surprised that you’ve managed to learn the Atlanta Plane’s language in such a short time.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “There’s nothing surprising about it. I’ve been watching Axe Island for a while. Although the people were very busy, they always talked with each other. After watching them for a long time and doing some analyses and calculations, it’s natural that I managed to learn their language. There shouldn’t be anything wrong with the translation.”

Laura nodded, “If that’s true, then the O’Neal Patriarch is really quite the character. The issues he just said are key reasons for our departure from the Ark Continent.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “He’s quite a character indeed. He’s the Patriarch, so how could he be simple. But it’s not time to deal with them right now, we’ll keep monitoring them and wait until they discover the spatial rift. I really didn’t expect them to have gone straight to the Rosen Empire. It’s interesting to think which one they will discover first, us or the Underworld.”

This time, it was Lizzy who opened her mouth as she said, “I didn’t expect their route to deviate like that. Moreover, their ships are quite fast, they actually went straight towards the Rosen Empire. With how the Underworld has progressed, I reckon they’d find the undead first.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s highly probable. Right, there’s no need to pay much attention to them right now. It’s fine as long as we take a look at them from time to time. Cai’er, don’t forget to collect more data about their equipment, the more the better.” Cai’er gave him a nod.

After that, Zhao Hai adjusted the monitor to show the Divines in the Taurus Continent. They’ve been quite patient, completely out of Zhao Hai’s expectations. Zhao Hai didn’t think that those people would take this much time just to make a base. Moreover, their base looked more formidable than any city.

Their entire base took up an entire mountain range, almost just like how Zhao Hai made his base on the Accra Mountains. They had hollowed out the inside of the mountain.

Although the Divines didn’t have iron armor beasts to dig, one shouldn’t forget that these people were powerful, and they also had magic to help them. Earth magic was easy for people to use, this allowed them to build their base. This way, they had less burden when building their base compared to Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai didn’t have a lot of mages in the past, he had to rely on the Dwarves to excavate the Accra Mountains.

What surprised Zhao Hai the most was the walls of the base, they were covered with magic formations. The construction of these walls took most of the time. It seems like the Divines were eager to turn their base into a solid fortress.

Zhao Hai can understand the approach made by the Divines. It was their exact approach to conquering the Ark Continent. They would build a base and then slowly advance towards the Taurus Continent, pushing Zhao Hai back bit by bit.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect it to do so well because this was the Divine Realm. Back in the Radiant Empire, after the Divines conquered it, the reason they had a continuous stream of supplies was because of the spatial rift. At that time, Zhao Hai was unable to enter the rift, therefore, he wasn’t able to disrupt their supply chain.

But this time, they were in the Divine Realm, and the base of the Divines was constructed by the seaside. The seas weren’t necessarily part of the Divine Race’s domain, their supply chain wouldn’t be that well protected. As long as Zhao Hai’s cuts their supplies off, then that base would just be as good as decoration. It would practically be useless.

Besides the base, Zhao Hai also saw that the Divines weren’t too trusting towards the vassal races that they’ve brought. During the construction of the base, they left the vassal races out. Moreover, they forbade the vassal races from entering the fortress, completely excluding them from everything.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think about attacking them right now. He wanted to wait until the Divine Realm became more chaotic. At that time, he would cut the Divines off from the other continents and then deal with the fortress.

These days, Bingya provided Zhao Hai with more information. The Divines were getting more and more ruthless regarding their suppression towards their vassal races. Their rules got more and more strict as well. A curfew was imposed, and besides the curfew, no more than ten people from the vassal races could equip themselves with weapons, the vassal races were even forbidden from cultivation.

One could say that the Divines had completely lost their trust in the vassal races. In turn, this made the relationship between the two parties worse and worse. A massive battle was starting to come up.

It was precisely because of this news that Zhao Hai wanted to wait until the vassal races finally rebel. If he made a move right now, then the Divines might focus all of their power towards him. At that time, the pressure towards the other races would decrease, making them think twice whether they should rebel or not.

Zhao Hai didn’t want such a thing to happen. He wanted those vassal races to participate in the war. After all, in turbid waters, it was easier to catch fish by hand.

Chapter 877: Huge Rebellion by the Vassal Races

The vassal races didn’t let Zhao Hai wait for a long time. The key to the matter was all the Divines moving at once. The suppression got more and more unreasonable, there even came to a point where a Divine captured and killed a vassal just for being unpleasant to the eyes. When this news came about, the vassal races finally exploded.

They cannot wait, they couldn’t. Any more than this and their race would practically be exterminated. Therefore, rebellions began to crop up everywhere in the Divine Race. The scale of the operation was very huge.

Zhao Hao got this information from Bingya ten days after the people from the Atlanta Continent arrived.

Majority of Zhao Hai’s attention was now pointed at the people from the Atlanta Continent. Although the O’Neal family knew that something strange was going on, they still didn’t care much. They continued to lead their ship towards the continent. Before long, they had arrived by a port city, Rising Water City.

This place was originally an important port city of the Rosen Empire, governed by a Rosen Empire’s Prince. Now, not a single person can be seen on its streets.

However, this doesn’t have any relationship with the O’Neal family. They weren’t far from the city, so they decided to use it as a landing site.

This was good for them since Rising Water City’s harbor was a deepwater port. Otherwise, there would be no way for their four ships to dock. Since the O’Neal family didn’t know anything, they sent their scouts to see if there were any danger. After which they landed on the city.

Upon arriving at the shore, the O’Neal family didn’t immediately rush to expand towards the Ark Continent. Instead, they sent small troops as reconnaissance while those who were left behind began to renovate the city.

Although Rising Water City was a famous port of the Rosen Empire, it was insufficient for the O’Neal family. The family mostly used their magic armors and war tanks, both of which were massive. This was especially true for the war tank, each on of them were able to carry 20 magic armors, making it much larger than magic armors themselves.

Even if Rising Water city wasn’t a small city, its structures were made according to normal standards. Although their roads were quite wide, they still couldn’t accommodate the war tanks.

Additionally, when magic armors weren’t in battle, they would need a place to be stored in for maintenance. Because of this, the O’Neal family needed a large warehouse. However, Rising Water City’s warehouses were just too small, the O’Neal family would need to build the warehouses themselves. In order for them to survive for a long time, they would need to do this. They couldn’t just deliver the magic armors back to the ships since the four ships wouldn’t be staying here forever. The ships would need to return to Axe Island and bring commodities back.

In the past few days, aside from sending scouts and renovating Rising Water City, the O’Neal Family didn’t really have too much trouble. Their scope of reconnaissance didn’t exceed the Rosen Empire’s territory. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s desire of having them clash with the Underworld fell through.

At this time, Bingya sent information to Zhao Hai about the revolt happening in the Divine Realm. Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. As long as they started, Zhao Hai could also start to act.

This didn’t mean that Zhao Hai was a warfreak. These days, Zhao Hai was forced to just look, unable to make a move. This state made him feel uncomfortable. But this time, he can now deal with the Divines.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t say much in front of Bingya. He just nodded and said, “Alright, thanks.” Then he nodded once more before returning to his room.

Upon entering the room, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Laura and the others and said, “Prepare to set off. We’ll deal with the Divines here first.” Laura and the other nodded. To be honest, they were already bored of waiting around all day.

However, they also knew that it wouldn’t be good to prematurely dispatch troops. Because of this, they endured. Now that they can make their move, their moods naturally improved.

After looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Let’s set off. Break their supply line first. Then we’ll take care of their base.”

Laura and the others nodded. There’s no need to say anything else right now. When they left, Zhao Hao sent word to the Thunder Clan and the others, informing them about the situation.

Bingya was still quite confused with Zhao Hai’s reaction. He still didn’t know what Zhao Hai plans to do. Upon hearing about the rebellion, Zhao Hai’s reaction was quite light.

However, Bingya soon found himself wrong. Zhao Hai was already in action. The Hell King’s ship suddenly changed direction and flew straight towards the outskirts of the Taurus Continent.

Bingya stood on the deck of the ship, looking outwards as the ship unceasingly went through the clouds. His heart couldn’t help but calm down, he knew that Zhao Hai had started to make his move.

Bingya didn’t have any doubts regarding Zhao Hai’s strength. He had seen how strong Zhao Hai was with his own two eyes. As long as Zhao Hai made a move, the Divines would surely suffer greatly.

Although the ship was quick, no wind can be felt by those standing inside it. With the ship’s shields, all of the gale winds were kept out. Moreover, the ship flew steadily. If Bingya wasn’t standing on the deck, he wouldn’t have known that the ship had moved.

At this time, Zhao Hai appeared behind Bingya as he said, “What’s wrong? You’ve been staring for quite some time.”

Bingya turned to look at Zhao Hai, he bowed and then said, “Mister, I’ve been thinking about my uncles, father, and brothers. All of them were killed by the Divine Race. The thing I wanted the most right now  is to kill the Divines and avenge my family.”

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya and sighed, he patted the Wolf Beastman’s shoulder and said, “Death is inevitable, especially during wars. Don’t think about it too much, go take a rest.”

Bingya actually shook his head and said, “I’ll be unfair to mister, but I cannot fall asleep. Mister, can you defeat the Divines?”

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya’s eyes and smiled, “Yes, I can. You can rest assured.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Bingya’s expression turned calm. He didn’t know why, but he found himself believing Zhao Hai’s words.

At this time, Yehta and Ryder also arrived on the deck. They silently looked at the Hell King’s ship’s heading. They were aware about the rebellion, Zhao Hai’s response was within their expectations.

The Hell King’s ship was very fast, After two hours, they had already arrived at sea. Zhao Hai didn’t stop as he flew for another two hours before stopping. Then he had the ship fly parallel to the shore, mapping everything he came across.

If the Divines had satellites, they would discover that the Hell King’s ship’s course went in a semicircle, going around the Divine Race fortress in the Taurus Continent.

When he felt like he had covered the supply line, Zhao Hai stopped. Bingya and the others looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “Don’t worry, we’ll wait here for some time. When the Divines send supplies to the Taurus Continent, we’ll rob them. You go and take a rest.”

Bingya and the others looked at each other, but nobody moved. They were already aware of Zhao Hai’s mystical methods, but they still believed that if the ship remained here, the supplies would still be delivered.

Zhao Hai didn’t explain it to them as he turned and returned to his room. Since Bingya and the other didn’t have anything else to do, they chose to return to their cabins as well.

Bingya and the others also understood that if Zhao Hai wanted to block the supply line, then the Divines in the Taurus Continent certainly wouldn’t have a good time. There were about 100 million Divines in the Taurus Continent right now. In addition to the Divine Race army, there were also 100 million vassal soldiers. These vassal soldiers were unaware that they had already launched a revolt, therefore they still listened to the orders of the Divines.

Although these people were very strong, one shouldn’t forget that they also needed to be fed. 100 million people meant 100 million mouths to feed. And if they add the vassal soldiers, then that would be 200 million mouths. And this didn’t include the fodder for their mounts. All of these added up to an astronomical figure. The Divines needed new supplies every day. People would bring them spatial bags filled with food, otherwise they would starve.

Not only was Zhao Hai planning to cut the supply line of the Divines, he also asked Bingya and the others to think of a way to inform the vassal soldiers about what has been happening. They needed to be informed that the rebellion had already started.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the 100 million vassals to pose any threat to the Divines. However, there was no downside to recruiting these 100 million soldiers. Even if they can’t help, they could at least cause some headaches, or even waste the Divine Race’s energy.

Time passed by as evening was slowly creeping in. Bingya couldn’t stay inside his room for so long, so he decided to go into the deck and look to see if some Divines could be spotted.

Upon arriving outside, Bingya couldn’t help but stare. This was because he saw the ship moving. Bingya stared for a moment before he looked down from the ship and then he smiled. This was because a Divine Race fleet was on the sea not far away.

At this time, Zhao Hai also walked out. He looked at Bingya and smiled, “Are you worried that I won’t be able to stop the fleet?”

Bingya scratched his head and bowed, “Mister’s methods are extraordinary, this Bingya is just blindly worrying.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, if I said that I’ll deal with the Divines, then I will certainly be able to take care of them. I’ve placed undead on the places we passed through earlier. As long as the Divines come, they would immediately be spotted by my undead.”

Chapter 878: Fighting another Ultimate Weapon!

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t speaking the truth. If he didn’t make it up, then he wouldn’t have any other way of explaining why he knew about the Divine Race fleet here.

Sure enough, when Zhao Hai said this, an understanding expression appeared on the faces of Bingya and the others. They really thought that Zhao Hai arranged his undead on the sea.

Bingya and the others had already seen how strong Zhao Hai’s undead were. Therefore, they didn’t suspect Zhao Hai’s words at all.

Zhao Hai didn’t think of hiding himself, therefore, the Divines were quick to discover his ship. The fleet slowed down before Divine Race soldiers began to fly out. Among these Divines were more than 20 Domain Weapon experts.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t rush to attack. He only commanded the Hell King’s ship to slow down and stop in front of the soldiers. Then Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “There’s no point in hiding. Since a Supreme Elder had come, then let this Zhao Hai introduce himself.”

Nobody made any noise, the Divines were honestly standing there, they didn’t respond to Zhao Hai. Bingya and the others were confused at Zhao Hai. They thought that Zhao Hai was playing with the other party.

At this moment, Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Since the Elder wants to hide, then I would have to be impolite.” After that, the Hell King’s ship’s flag pole suddenly swung towards Zhao Hai. Bingya and the others were startled, they were unable to react as the pole pierced forwards above Zhao Hai.

Originally, that place was empty. But a clashing sound can suddenly be heard. Along with this sound appeared a humanoid shape. The figure was flying about 30 meters away from Zhao Hai.

The figure showed a man riding a huge scorpion. The Hell King’s ship’s pole was currently blocked by the scorpion’s tail.

Upon seeing this, Bingya and the others knew that a person using an ultimate weapon was planning a sneak attack on Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai discovered it and managed to block it with the ship’s flag pole.

Zhao Hai looked at the man and coldly said, “And who are you? Care to introduce yourself?”

The man looked at Zhao Hai and replied, “There’s no need to know since you’ll die anyway.” After that, two big pincers went out from the scorpion and went towards Zhao Hai. At the same time, the tail went forward and suppressed the flagpole.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. Then with an intention, the ship’s ram suddenly flew out, heading towards the figure, ignoring the two pincers.

The person was startled, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually go for mutual attacks. He refused to get hurt and immediately directed the scorpion to go down. Naturally, the two pincers returned.

As the scorpion went down, the ship’s cannons suddenly adjusted themselves and fired towards the man. The man had the two pincers block the attack while the tail went to strike the ship’s hull.

Just as the tail was about to hit the hull, the waves beneath the ship suddenly rolled. The waves turned into a vortex, blocking the tail of the giant scorpion.

Zhao Hai suddenly waved his hand, taking his magic staff out. Then he waved his staff and transformed it into a huge hammer which proceeded to smash towards the person.

The man didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this move. He had to retrieve his tail and go back. But at this moment, he suddenly felt a breeze by his side.The Hell King’s ship’s ram just flew beside him, it caused him to have a cold sweat.

The man dodged the ram strike, but what he didn’t expect was the flag pole softening itself and turning into a whip, targeting his head. He couldn’t help but retrieve the scorpion tail. However, he wasn’t able to use his full strength as he was dragged down by the pole.

Zhao Hai didn’t pursue, instead, he retrieved the pole and the ram back into the ship. His magic staff also returned to its original appearance.

Following the exchange was a flash of golden light. Then a person flew up from below. His giant scorpion had disappeared, but his body was now covered in a magnificent golden body armor. In place of knuckles, the armor had pincers instead. One could see the lethality of the pincers by the cold light that it gave out. At the same time, the armor had a swaying scorpion tail in place of a belt.

The man’s blood red eyes looked at Zhao Hai before he suddenly laughed and said, “Good, good, no wonder Old Ox managed to suffer a loss against you. Unfortunately for you, you met me today. That Old Ox is already aged, he’s useless. Now that I’m here, you’re dead.”

After that, he punched forward. His fist was quite interesting, he didn’t hold a fist like a normal person would do. Instead, he had his index finger hooked. Along with his movement, a huge shadow appeared behind him. The shadow was a huge tail that was currently going towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at this and smiled as he waved his hand. Then the ship’s battering ram separated from the hull and met with the approaching scorpion tail.

A bang resounded in the surroundings. Upon clashing, the scorpion tail disappeared while the ram returned to the ship. Not waiting for the man to make another attack, Zhao Hai quickly extended his staff, making it longer as it attacked the other party.

The man’s response came quickly as well. He extended his left hand as a giant pincer appeared. The pincers went on to block the staff. However, the man didn’t wait for Zhao Hai to retrieve his staff as his right hand extended and captured it. The man sneered before exerting force, pinching Zhao Hai’s magic staff in half.

The man laughed and said, “Kid, your weapon is a bit interesting, but it’s too weak.”

Zhao Hai looked at the person and then smiled, “Really? Why didn’t I know that?” Then the magic staff slowly returned to its original form. The section that was pinched shrunk as the entire staff went back to Zhao Hai. Then the staff merged back together, one couldn’t see any signs of it being broken.

Zhao Hai looked at the man and sneered, “I just want to match your movements, but you took it too seriously. Hahaha, interesting, interesting.”

The man rushed roared before he rushed towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai looked at the man and sneered, “You should look at your current appearance. Since you want to kill me, then I would have to be impolite.” After he said that, the Hell King’s ship shrunk and then proceeded to smash towards the man.

It only took a blink of an eye before the ship was about to collide with the man. Upon seeing this, the man couldn’t help but get surprised. He crossed both of his arms in order to block Zhao Hai’s blow. However, something suddenly pulled at his arms, he didn’t even manage to make a cross in front of him before the ship’s ram crashed straight into his body.

The ram’s attack hit no other place than the least defensible place in any armor, the throat. The man’s head was immediately cut off.

The man was dead, his expression filled with disbelief. What he just saw was his two hands being tied up by the waves beneath the Hell King’s shp. It was due to these waves that he had failed to block the approaching collision.

When the man died, the armor immediately separated from his body and automatically returned to being a large scorpion before it fell into the ground.

But how could Zhao Hai let it fall. He waved his hand as a spatial rift appeared, the giant scorpion disappeared in mid-air.

Upon seeing the man die, the Divines behind him immediately turned chaotic. Naturally, these Divines were aware of the man’s status. Now that the man had died, the Divines had lost all means of defending, their morale sharply fell.

Zhao Hai didn’t let go of this opportunity and directly bombarded the Divines. The Divines died one chunk at a time. It must be known that the might of the Hell King’s ship’s cannons was very huge.

The Divines were immediately flustered, they didn’t even think about resisting as all of them scampered to escape. However, they were soon to discover that Undead were blocking their exit. Not only from behind, above, below, on their left, their right, all avenues for escape were closed off. They were totally trapped inside a huge undead-made basket.

What they failed to notice were more undead charging from underwater. Before long, these undead emerged and began to fight the Divines on the ships. The Divines were slowly killed until Zhao Hai had finally taken control of the fleet.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about this as he commanded his undead to kill the trapped Divines. The Domain Weapon experts tried to resist but their efforts were ultimately useless. Zhao Hai also released undead Domain Weapon experts. Since the undead experts outnumbered the Divines, they too were soon killed off.

The battle ended very quickly. For an army with no morale at all, it was practically a one sided slaughter. In less than two hours, the whole fleet was under Zhao Hai’s hand.

Naturally, there were Divines who weren’t killed off. There were those who lost their morale and immediately surrendered. Ever since Zhao Hai fought against the Divines, this was the first time that people actually surrendered.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to manage them right now. He immediately threw them to the Space along with the ships they were using.

There were a lot of provisions inside those ships. And among the Divines who died, there were people who had space equipments with them. Inside were also supplies. The biggest space equipment that Zhao Hai gained belonged to the Supreme Elder. Inside weren’t supplies, instead, they were magic crystals.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these. What he wanted to do right now was to investigate the giant scorpion. This was the first ultimate weapon that he obtained.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t make the Space analyze it right now, he just stored it inside the warehouse.

Bingya and the others were also able to see the fight. When Zhao Hai was battling the Supreme Elder, Bingya and the others were nervous. Fortunately, Zhao Hai won in the end.

However, this battle reminded them about Zhao Hai’s terrifying strength. Within a short period of time, Zhao Hai actually managed to kill the Supreme Elder. Zhao Hai was too strong.

At this time, Zhao Hai turned to the three and asked, “Do you know that person?”

Bingya and the others recovered, but they shook their head. Bingya opened his mouth and said, “Mister, although I don’t know who that was, but I heard about various ultimate weapons. From what I just saw, that man should have been the Scorpio Continent’s Supreme Elder.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I guessed the same. Alright, I’ll head to my room and take a rest. You take care of yourselves.” After that, Zhao Hai returned to his room. Zhao Hai didn’t rush to examine the giant scorpion inside the warehouse. Instead, he waved his hand and summoned an undead. This undead was the Supreme Elder that Zhao Hai just fought.

The reason Zhao Hai asked Bingya and the others about this person was to cover himself. That would make Bingya and the others believe that he had no way of gaining news from the Divines. After all, his relationship with the Foreign Races wasn’t that good to begin with.

Although the man was beheaded by Zhao Hai, his body didn’t suffer any destructive injuries. Therefore, the man was able to be raised as an undead.

Zhao Hai looked at the man and said, “What is your name? Why are you with the fleet?”

The person immediately bowed and said, “Answering to the Master. I’m called Yan Jian, Scorpio Clan’s Supreme Elder. In the past, the Taurus Continent told us about Master’s strength and the fact that Master might attack us. Therefore, he proposed for a Supreme Elder to accompany each shipment of supplies. This time, it was my turn.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Tell me about how long the fleet arrives. Right, you used more than a thousand ships to transport supplies. In addition to the ships, you also brought space equipments along. You transported quite a lot of grain.”

The man quickly replied, “Replying to Master. The food generally arrives after one month. These supplies cannot feed 200 million people. Because of this, the vassal races could only receive limited amounts of food. This is to make sure that they don’t get full. This would make it easier for the Divines to suppress them once they decide to revolt.”

Chapter 879: Planting an Ultimate Weapon?

Zhao Hai didn’t sneer at the Divine Race’s methods. He thought that it was appropriate for the Divines to do this. The Divines had decided to distance themselves from the vassal races. Naturally, because of this, they wouldn’t treat those people right. If the Divines provided them with proper nourishment, then the Divines would be the ones to suffer in the end.

He nodded and said, “How many continents decided to participate in this action?”

Yan Jian nodded and said, “Replying to Master. This time, all ten continents decided to participate. We decided that this matter is enough to shake the entire Divine Realm. We need to quell this as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he asked once more, “In the Taurus Continent, how many ultimate weapon experts are there?”

Yan Jian immediately replied, “Currently, there are four Supreme Elders in the Taurus Continent. Gold Ben from the Taurus Clan, he’s the one that master defeated. There’s the Capricorn Clan’s Moroga, Cancer Clan’s Jie Yu, and Sagittarius Clan’s Zither Karna. Including me, these are the only Supreme Elders that the Divine Race can spare. The others are needed to deal with the vassal races as well as the Foreign Races.”

Zhao Hai nodded, the Divine Race’s arrangement was quite good. Without knowing Zhao Hai’s true strength, five Supreme Elders should be a safe choice. Even if it was impossible to kill Zhao Hai, their number could still allow them to protect each other.

At the same time, leaving five Supreme Elders behind was just the right number to contend with the Foreign Race’s three ultimate weapons. This way, the Foreign Race would find it hard to attack.

Zhao Hai looked at Yan Jian and said, “Will the other continents send more reinforcements to the Taurus Continent? How would the Divines deal with the rebellion?”

Yan Jian said on word, “Kill!”

Although Yan Jian only said a simple word, Zhao Hai can feel the bloodlust behind it.

The Divines on each continent had vassal races with a large population. Because of this, the Divines would only have one way of dealing with them, and that was to kill! It seems like the Divines were getting serious this time.

Zhao Hai nodded and then waved his hand, “Alright, you go back down.” Yan Jian bowed to Zhao Hai before he turned around and left. Zhao Hai wanted him to return down to the layer where the undead were supposed to be.

After Yan Jian left, Laura and the others came over. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, the Divines have become more ruthless. But this time, we managed to gain an ultimate weapon. Right, take it out, let us have a look. Then have the Space analyze it.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he nodded. With an intention, the ultimate weapon appeared inside the Space. Just as the ultimate weapon appeared, a prompt was heard, “High-grade Combat Suit detected. Establishing seed database, seed added: 12 Constellation Combat Suit, Scorpio crystal seed. Seed can only be planted on fertile land. Seed can only be harvested once. Host can choose who to bestow the Combat Suit. If the person is disloyal to the Host, then the Host can choose to take the Combat Suit away or have the suit attack the person. Current Combat Suit can be transformed into a crystal ball and merged with the Host’s staff. Since the Host has a better crystallization ability, it is advised that the host doesn’t use this Combat Suit. Once merged with the staff, the Combat Suit cannot be damaged. Suit will gain little consciousness and will only awaken when called out. Combat suit can help the Host in battle. Asking the host to proceed with the fusion.”

With this much information, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to comprehend them all. But after asking Cai’er, Zhao Hai finally understood. The Space had recognized the Divine Race’s ultimate weapon as a type of combat suit. This combat suit would be important in aiding its owner in battle. And because of this combat suit, the Space had made a special seed page in the store. There were several entries to this page, but the only one unlocked was the scorpio seed. This seed would need a whole season to grow. After it matures, it would produce a crystal ball. Sealed within this ball was a same armor as the Scorpio Clan’s ultimate weapon. Zhao Hai can give these armor to his people. And if the person was unfaithful, Zhao Hai can use the suit to kill the person or he could just confiscate the suit. On the other hand, the current Scorpio Combat Suit has been turned into a crystal ball. This crystal ball can combine with Zhao Hai’s staff. At this time, the Scorpio combat suit looks like something made from a special type of metal. Once combined with Zhao Hai’s staff, it would become one with it. However, since Zhao Hai’s crystallization ability was more defensively powerful, there was no need for Zhao Hai to wear this suit at all. He can just use the suit as a weapon like Yan Jian’s summoned beast.

This information was a very good thing for Zhao Hai. This combat suit was deemed as an ultimate weapon by the Divine Race. Although it wasn’t as powerful as the Hell King’s ship, it still couldn’t be underestimated. Zhao Hai was now planning to plant a batch of them. Once a war starts, then Zhao Hai would have an army of people wearing such suits. At that time, how much would the troops be strengthened?

Zhao Hai was just worrying about how to improve the combat power of the Devil Legion. What the Devil Legion lacked right now were good armors and weapons. If they wear these suits, then both matters would be solved.

Although Laura and the others managed to hear the prompt, their understanding was much less compared to Zhao Hai. Upon hearing Cai’er’s explanation, they finally understood. They couldn’t help but cheer. This was an absolute surprise for them, a huge pleasant surprise.

They can plant ultimate weapons? Other than the Space, no other place in the world was able to do this.

Zhao Hai was similarly happy, he quickly said, “Start immediately!’

Just as Zhao Hai said that, the combat armor in the Space was suddenly covered in a white light. Before long, the light condensed into a blood red crystal ball. This ball wasn’t very big, probably about the size of a dragon’s eye. Zhao Hai turned his hand as the crystal ball appeared. Zhao Hai inspected the ball and discovered the astrological symbol of Scorpio inside.

Then Zhao Hai took his staff closer to the ball, dissolving the crystal ball in no time and merging to the staff. Before long, the scorpio symbol appeared on the staff, nothing else.

Zhao Hai began to wield the staff and waved it gently. Then a huge scorpion tail made out of red crystal appeared inside the cabin. This scorpion tail looked like the one from the Scorpio suit, but it also wasn’t quite like it. It looked more powerful and more robust than the one before.

Zhao Hai looked at the scorpion tail and nodded. Then he said, “Tail needle!” The scorpion tail obediently moved itself. Zhao Hai discovered that the tip of the scorpion tail looked different compared to normal scorpions. Generally, a scorpion tail would be oriented to attack the front. However, this tail was made into something that can attack in all directions, similar to a whip.

Zhao Hai gave a satisfying nod before he gave another command, “Attack left!” The scorpion tail obediently waved leftwards before separating itself and proceeded to attack.

After that, Zhao Hai tried to attack the right side. Zhao Hai gave a nod and then said, “Transform!” Zhao Hai wanted to see how the combat suit could protect him during a fight.

Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the scorpio combat suit slowly transformed into a humanoid form. However, the suit didn’t cover Zhao Hai’s body, instead, it just formed into a full body armor. The whole body was made out of blood red crystals, it was very beautiful. Even the joints were made from crystal, they looked soft, perfectly able to handle human movements.

Zhao Hai can see the that the helmet had the same form as the one worn by Yan Jian before. However, this suit right here didn’t need someone to wear it, the suit can move on its own.

Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “Receive!” Then the armor turned back into a crystal ball and then fused with Zhao Hai’s staff.

Laura and the others saw everything from start to finish. Upon seeing how the scorpion tail performed, all of them couldn’t help but smile.

After taking the scorpio armor in, Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, make some adjustments in the Space. Make some space on fertile soils and plant some combat suits there.”[1]

Cai’er nodded. At this time, fertile black soil was used for herb production. These herbs were going to be used to make God-rank potions. What Zhao Hai wanted to do was make way for some combat suits while minimizing the impact on the God-rank potion production. For Cai’er, this was a very simple matter.

Naturally, no matter what she decided to do, the herbs would certainly be affected. What Cai’er needed to do was make sure the effect was as low as possible.

After talking to Cai’er, Zhao Hai looked at Laura and the others and said, “I didn’t expect the Ultimate Weapons to have this much use. It seems like collecting all 13 would certainly be useful for us, what do you think?”

Laura smiled and said, “It’ll certainly be helpful. Brother Hai, will the Divines know that we plundered their supplies?”

* * *

Fertile meant that those special plots that can accelerate growth.

Chapter 880: Don’t Worry

Zhao Hai coldly smiled and said, “They’ll find out for sure. But they won’t be able to immediately, maybe tomorrow or the day after that. After all, they don’t have things like messenger fishes for communication. Let’s return to the Ark Continent for now. If the Divines come looking for their fleet, then we can use that opportunity to deal with their base.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “I know you’ll say that. But I think we should tell Bingya about our plan. The vassal soldiers in the Taurus Continent have no idea that the rebellion has already started. If we deal with the base, then they might be used as cannon fodder by the Divines.”

Lizzy gave a nod and said, “Brother Hai, we aren’t friendly with the other vassal races. If we became enemies with them, then our future actions would be met with more troubles. It would be best if Bingya were to contact these vassal races before we proceed to attack the base. In any case, we aren’t in much of a hurry. Even if we robbed the Divines of their grain and ships, it’ll be fine as long as we don’t let them know. While the Divines are looking for their ship, Bingya and the others can contact those vassal soldiers, what do you think?” Zhao Hai thought about it for a moment before he nodded. He understood that this wasn’t a war that can be finished in a short time. And if he wanted to detain the Ultimate Weapons, he would need to work very hard. Today, he was only able to slay the Scorpio Supreme Elder because the elder had been looking down on him, at the same time, it was also because of the recent upgrades made to the Hell King’s ship. From this point on, detaining the Supreme Elders wouldn’t be easy. If the Supreme Elders wanted to flee with all their might, then there was only little that Zhao Hai could do.

Now that the Divines had eaten a defeat, they will definitely strengthen their defenses. The next batch of grain might be delivered by two elders. Although Zhao Hai was confident in dealing with two elders, it wasn’t easy to catch them if they decided to escape.

Zhao Hai cannot ignore the Supreme Elders. It would be impossible for this war to end if they were kept free.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai thought of something. The Divine Realm had 13 continents, 12 of which were named after the 12 constellations, the last one was not. If the Ultimate Weapons went according to the 12 constellations, then what would the 13th ultimate weapon be? Zhao Hai frowned upon thinking about this. But in the end, he shook his head and stopped thinking about it, he would find out later on.

Lizzy saw Zhao Hai nod, then frown and then shake his head. She became confused, so she asked, “Brother Hai, what’s the problem? Did I say something wrong?” Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy and smield, “You didn’t say anything wrong. I was just thinking of too many things. Let’s go see Bingya and tell them to contact the vassal races.” Then he stood up and went outside.

Bingya and the others were currently outside. They were there since the fight, they still haven’t returned to their room.

The fight was just too big of a blow to their minds. A Divine Race Supreme Elder was just killed off by Zhao Hai, it was completely out of their expectation.

Moreover, they didn’t have the capacity to help in the battle, it made them feel uncomfortable. In their minds, they were just garbage in front of Zhao Hai’s might. Knowing that you were useless would leave one with a bitter taste in their mouths.

However, they had no choice but to recognize Zhao Hai’s prowess. In the battle between Zhao Hai and the Divines, they didn’t even need to move. Although they were strong figures back in their clans, they were nothing compared to Zhao Hai.

But even if they were given a duty, it wasn’t in battle. This made them quite depressed.

Ryder looked at Bingya’s face and said, “Old Bingya, are you waiting for Mister Zhao Hai’s command? Aren’t you just waiting for nothing?” Bingya forced a smile and said, “At the very least we don’t have much to do right now. And with our strength, do you think we could participate in Mister’s Battles? Aren’t we just courting death?” Yehta smiled as well. She couldn’t help but recall how she had been arrogant in front of Zhao Hai. This thought made her embarrassed. Perhaps at that time Zhao Hai was looking at them as though they were idiots.

Ryder looked at their expressions and smiled. Bingya and Yehta looked at him in confusion. They didn’t know why he was smiling.

Ryder smiled faintly and said, “I just want to say that following Mister had really expanded our horizons. In the past, would we believe it if people told us that Supreme Elders could be killed?” When Bingya and Yehta heard this, they couldn’t help but laugh. Right, before, if they were told that a Supreme Elder could be defeated or killed, then they would definitely regard it as a joke. But now, with how much they had seen, they would definitely believe it.

As the group chatted, Zhao Hai suddenly opened the door and headed outside. After seeing him, the three immediately stood up and gave Zhao Hai a salute. Zhao Hai waved his hand and looked at the three people before saying, “What were you talking about?”

Bingya smiled and said, “Just chatting about normal matters. Didn’t mister need to take a rest?” Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It was useless. Right, Bingya, I just want to ask. When can you tell the vassal soldiers in the Taurus Continent that their people had already started the rebellion?” Bingya thought for a moment before he replied, “That wouldn’t be easy. At this point, the Divines had monitored the vassal races very closely. Contacting them wouldn’t be very easy. I guess it should take about half a month.” Zhao Hai knit his brows, he didn’t say anything for a while before he nodded and said, “Try to do it as soon as possible. Don’t wait for the Divines to be the ones to tell them. The sooner we contact them, the sooner we could conquer the base. In turn, the fewer losses there would be to the vassal races.”

Bingya replied with a serious voice, “Mister, rest assured, we will certainly make best use of the time.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Talk to your people as well, tell them to refrain from being too anxious to move. Take it slowly and wait for a while before attacking.” Bingya nodded and said, “Alright, we will certainly relay Mister’s words properly.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head towards the Taurus Continent and said, “Since this battle started, I couldn’t count how many lives had been lost. Perhaps this is a destiny of someone from a lower realm. For those in the upper realms, we’re but ants that are struggling for survival. Only they don’t know that we ants have feelings as well.”

Bingya and the others didn’t understand what Zhao Hai was talking about. As they were looking at Zhao Hai in confusion, Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled bitterly, “The actions made by the Divines all this time has been orchestrated by a person. Add a little bit of ambition, and we have today’s current state. If we defeat the Divines, then that person would have to change the way he operates. In the end, nothing would matter. Right, I should stop talking. No matter what this person is planning to do, I still need to defeat the Divine Race. This way, maybe I’ll get to meet the person controlling all of these.” Bingya and the others stayed silent, they still couldn’t understand Zhao Hai’s words. Zhao Hai looked at the three of them and said, “After we arrive at the Taurus Continent, you shall disembark and arrange ways to meet the vassal soldiers. I can give you some spatial equipment with food inside. We need them to be healthy in both body and mind so that they can help in dealing with the Divines. Now that we have plundered the Divine Race’s supplies, the Divines would surely deduct more from their food. It wouldn’t be good for us if they are starving.”

Bingya and the others weren’t fools, so they immediately understood what Zhao Hai was saying, so the three nodded. The Divines certainly knew about the rebellion that was currently happening, but the vassal soldiers were still kept in the dark. Because of this, the Divine Race’s method of starving them had gone successfully.

Zhao Hai looked at the three of them before turning his hand over, taking out spatial equipments. These spatial equipment were the ones taken from the Divine Race fleet. Inside each of them were provisions for the army. Zhao Hai gave these items to Bingya and the others and said, “In here are grains taken from the Divine Race fleet. Give these to the soldiers and make sure that the Divines don’t find out. If the Divines knew about it, then we would have to prematurely begin our attack.”

The three nodded. At this time, the Hell King’s ship had already arrived on the Taurus Continent. Zhao Hai turned his head to the three and said, “You can go down. After the matter gets settled, look for me in a safe place. I’ll be waiting for you there.”

Bingya and the others nodded before they jumped down from the ship and dived towards the Divine Race fortress. After the three figures had vanished, Zhao Hai returned to his room.

After going inside, Zhao Hai immediately called Cai’er, “Cai’er, what happened? Why did you call me?” Cai’er did indeed call Zhao Hai, however, Bingya and the others couldn’t hear it. Cai’er nodded and said, “Young Master, the O’Neal family has started to investigate and they are heading towards the Aksu Empire. It’s possible that they would meet the undead soon.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately became curious. He turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Oh, good good. Let’s take a look. I want to see the O’Neal family’s response once they meet the undead.” Then he sat on the sofa as Cai’er opened the monitor.

Chapter 881: Demon Realm’s Currency Issue

On the monitor was a small team of magic armors. This team composed of three armored tanks with a total of 50 magic armors inside. Overall, these armored tanks can carry 60 magic armors, however, they freed ten spaces so that they could bring living materials and energy sources along.

The three tanks had entered Aksu Empire’s Lifeline Canyon. Their speed wasn’t any slower than any automobile back on Earth. However, this was Zhao Hai’s first time seeing a vehicle as fast as this given its size. Zhao Hai calculated that the tanks had reached the speed of  about 200 kilometers per hour.

Upon reaching this calculation, Zhao Hai couldn’t believe that it was true. There weren’t a lot of cars back on Earth that can reach 200 kilometers per hour. One shouldn’t forget that these tanks contained 20 magic armors, reaching a weight of over 100 tons. And with wind resistance, how could these things reach this speed? It was impossible!

However, after recalculations from the Space, Zhao Hai was finally convinced. Those bulky things actually had this kind of outrageous speed.

Zhao Hai didn’t understand how it could be possible. Why would these things be this fast? But when he thought about the ships, Zhao Hai thought that it might be possible

The big ships of the Atlanta Plane weren’t slow even though they displaced a million tons. .This was strange in and of itself but since the ships were sailing on water, Zhao Hai had no point of reference to notice it.

However, when he remembered the time the four ships had encountered a little bit of storm, Zhao Hai noticed that the although the wind and rain looked normal, the waves caused by the collision to the ship’s bow flew higher than one would expect. There was only one explanation for this, the ship was very quick. Upon making measurements, Zhao Hai discovered that these ships had infinitely more speed than the other ships back on Earth.

At the thought of this, Zhao Hai understood that no matter the tanks or the ships, both of them were using magic formations. Its possible that the Atlanta Plane were using their formations to reduce the weight of their tanks and ships. This would allow them to go quickly.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel excited about the magic formations and magic armors of the Atlanta Plane. Their Techno-magic civilization had reached a very high degree. Whether it be the Ark Continent or the Divine Realm, both need to look up to the Atlanta Plane when it comes to magic armors or magic formations.

Zhao Hai also came to discover that the Atlanta Plane’s war tanks were divided into several types. One of them was a turtle-shaped tank. This turtle-shaped chariot was the slowest, but it can carry the most. Moreover, its defenses were the best. There was also a tiger-shaped war tank. This tank was the most commonly used war tank in the Atlanta Plane. It’s firepower and speed were much better than the turtle-shaped tanks. Its weapons made it the most commonly used tank in the Atlanta Plane.

The third type of war tank was the leopard-shaped tank. This was the fastest tank among the three. However, because of its speed, it can’t carry a lot of cargo. Its firepower was also inferior compared to the tiger-shaped tanks. This type of tank was more specifically used to transmit information.

However, the war tanks that Zhao Hai could see were actually modified tiger-shaped tanks. Not only can its speed compare to the leopard tanks, it can also leap forward just like the other tiger-shaped tanks. But making these tanks was also more troublesome compared to making any other tiger-shaped tank. Because of this, there are only a few of these tanks present in the Atlanta Plane.

After passing through Lifeline canyon, the tanks were now inside the Aksu Empire. Although the Aksu Empire had experienced war in the past, its mountains weren’t like the Accra Mountains where Zhao Hai killed every magic beast. Because of this, one could see several magic beasts here.

There were plenty of magic beasts inside Aksu Empire. Although Zhao Hai had moved the people of the Ark Continent, he didn’t have much time to take care of the magic beasts. Even if there were no such things as beast tides in the Akse Empire, there were still quite a lot of magic beasts.

Now that the people from the Aksu Empire have migrated, the place naturally became a paradise for magic beasts. All kinds of magic beasts ran into the Akse Empire and settled themselves.

However, the three Atlanta Plane tanks didn’t care much about those beasts. They would only kill magic beasts that came to disturb them. Other times they would just plow forward.

Zhao Hai didn’t understand what these tanks were doing. If they wanted to scout, then they should’ve stopped and looked around them. Why would they plow on forward like this? It wasn’t something that scouts would do.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t know that the three tanks were indeed sent to scout. They were heading north of the Ark Continent in order to look for people, or even find traces as to why they left. The O’Neal family actually sent people to the south as well. However, these people would only stroll around the Lyon Empire. They couldn’t reach the Buddha Empire since their provisions were limited.

Because of this, Zhao Hai only came to notice the team heading north. After some calculations, the team heading north would meet the underworld’s creatures soon.

Although the speed of the tanks were quite high, the Ark Continent was quite large. If they wanted to explore the entirety of it, then it wouldn’t take one or two days. Because of this, the team camped on a medium Aksu Empire city when darkness came.

After seeing that the team had gone to take a rest, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “It seems like they would be in the Ark Continent for a while, there’s no need to worry. I just don’t know if the people from the Atlanta Plane would fight the Underworld’s creatures when the time comes.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “That might not be the case. They could stop their advance to the North and focus on the southern part of the continent. It’s possible that they would be interested with the spatial rift first.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s quite possible as well. In any case, we won’t have to worry. We’re not afraid of them, conversely, I’m waiting for them to come. I just don’t know if they can come in half a month. At that time, we would be starting our fight against the Divine Race.”

Laura forced a smile and said, “When that time comes, then we would be fighting on two sides. Right, Brother Hai, tell this matter to the Thunder Clan and the others as well. Have them prepare themselves.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, we’ll tell them. You go arrange this matter while I go and see Bingya and the others.”

Laura nodded, then along with Lizzy and the others, they turned around and left. On the other hand, Zhao Hai changed the monitor’s image to Bingya’s group.

Bingya and the others had already arrived at the vicinity of the Divine Race’s fortress. They didn’t advance rashly, instead, they camped inside a forest and rested well.

When Zhao Hai saw that nothing was about to happen, he closed the monitor and then took a bath. After relaxing himself, his body flashed as he went to visit the Demons.

The Demons had already sent the third batch of Devil Legion soldiers into the hell background at this time. Meanwhile, the Demons inside the Demon Space were also looked after by Zhao Hai, their current state wasn’t worse off compared to the Ark Continent. Although the Ark Continent had received more care from Zhao Hai, the Demons were given ample attention as well. Most importantly, the Demons liked their environment more.

Besides feeling that the air was much better here, the Ark Continent’s people didn’t think too much about their new place. After all, the Ark Continent and the Ark Space was quite similar. On the other hand, the state of the Demons was different. Compared to the Demon Realm, the Demon Space was infinitely better. The Demons treasured this gift. In their minds, it would be the best if they could thrive in such an environment. Because of this, every Demon was giving 200% of their effort in order to develop their land. This caused their society to improve smoothly.

When Zhao Hai came to the Demon Space before, he already told the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King about the current state of the war with the Divine Race.

Currently, the days of the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were doing very well. The Demons were busily developing their own lands. And since the Space was quite big, and each race had their own Domain, no conflict had occurred. The matters that the two needed to take care of was quite little.

Back in the Demon Realm, each race and clan would fight for land because of food. Each conflict that happened would need the Great Demon King’s attention. At the same time, cities in the Demon Realm were also susceptible to attacks made by magic beasts and natural disasters. All of these needed the Great Demon King’s help.

However, these things didn’t occur in the Space. The Space was very big, so each race would have ample land of their own, erasing the conflicts caused by land. At the same time, magic beasts in the Demon Space were weak, and there were also a lot of Bread Fruits inside. With the addition of bamboo rice, other grains, and vegetables, the problem with food was also taken care of.

In the Space, there was also the church to exchange things from. As long as one place something of equal value, then the Space would make a trade. This reduced the conflicts for resources even more. Because of these things, the Great Demon King was very relaxed. The Demons had almost reached a state of high standard for a society where law and order prevailed and crime was at an all-time low.

Zhao Hai came to the Demon Space this time in order to discuss the matter of the Demon Race’s currency.

In the past, the Demon Realm didn’t have any form of currency. Everyone traded for what they want. It was just like the Beastmen, where they would use their argali to trade for living supplies. For the Demons, supplies were more precious than gold.

However, things were different in the Space. The Space wasn’t lacking in supplies, the Demon Space was completely self-sufficient. In this case, a form of currency was much needed. Otherwise, it would be impossible to place values on traded commodities. This might even cause conflict among the people.

In order for the Demons to develop further, they would need a form of monetization. Zhao Hai had already thought about this a long time ago. Having currency would also be very beneficial during transactions with the other Spaces. This meant that Zhao Hai was planning to have the various Spaces trade with each other in the future.

Zhao Hai already opened this matter with the Great Demon King. Being the wise leader that he was, the Great Demon King immediately agreed. However, the means of currency had become quite of a problem.

Each of the Space’s backgrounds can produce gold ores. However, the Demons have reached an extreme state of environmental protection. Even if they built their house, they would make sure that they would make the least amount of damage to the surroundings as possible. With this mentality, how could they stomach mining their mountains for gold ore? The Demons would surely disagree.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh upon thinking about the Demon Race’s conduct. He was left wondering what else to do. He can’t mine for gold and he can’t use paper currency as well because it would need cutting of trees to produce paper. Moreover, making forgery-proof paper wasn’t possible. If counterfeit money appeared later on, then the Demon Space’s currency would be in turmoil. The Demon Race might go into war because of this and Zhao Hai didn’t want this to happen.

Zhao Hai went to the Demon Space because he wanted to discuss a solution. And since this wasn’t his strength, he took Laura and Ruyen along with him.

When the three appeared in the Demon Space, the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King were having their meals. The things the two ate were simple. This was a habit they developed back in the Demon Realm.

Zhao Hai’s group of three appeared in front of the Palace. The Devil Legion guards immediately discovered them upon arriving. The guards didn’t block the three, instead, they gave a salute and sent one person to inform the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King of their arrival.

Upon hearing that Zhao Hai had come, the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King immediately went out and welcomed them to the dining room. After that they had people arrange tablewares and food once more.

After everything was taken care of, the Great Demon King turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are you here to discuss the matter of our currency? Did you come up with some solutions?” The last couple of days, the Great Demon King had a headache while thinking on this matter. However, he was still left with no good solution.

best joke ever

Chapter 882: Crystal Card and Selfishness

Zhao Hai had thought about various methods before, but these methods wouldn’t work. This was until a while ago when he was scanning through the Space. He remembered about these things from the Ark Continent, crystal cards!

Zhao Hai had obtained a lot of crystal cards from the Ark Continent before. However, crystal cards were useless for the Space. But then, after further upgrades, the Space can now turn crystal cards to gold coins and gold coins into crystal cards. Because of this, banks were already prevalent in the Ark Space and crystal cards had become more necessary for the people from the Ark Continent.

Back on Earth, your bank card can be used to buy things. However, if you use it to spend abroad, then you would have certain problems. Moreover, if it was lost, stolen, or hacked, then you would have huge problems. However, these things wouldn’t happen in the Space.

In the Ark Space, crystal cards were divided into two types. The first type was the regular crystal card. This crystal card was just like any ordinary money to be used in spending. The other type was a personal crystal card. This card can only be used by its owner. The owner’s appearance, fingerprint, blood-type, energy-attribute, and other qualities were used to personalize these cards. No other person can use it besides its owner.

Such protective measure might be impossible back on Earth, but in the Ark Continent, it can be achieved. Moreover, Zhao Hai tied each person’s ID to their personal crystal cards. This way, the card would have its owner’s information, making it convenient for the people to use.

At this point, these crystal cards were widely used in the Ark Space. This time, Zhao Hai wanted to implement this system into the Demon society.

Because of this, when the Great Demon King asked Zhao Hai for any ideas, he immediately told him about the crystal cards. Upon hearing the explanation, the Great Demon King nodded and said, “These crystal cards are very good. Mister, let me see this card that you described.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then took a card out. Since this card was the same one used by the people from the Ark Continent, Zhao Hai also had one. This was also effective in promoting the use of the card.

Upon receiving the card and inspecting it, the Great Demon King nodded and said, “Good, Mister, this is quite useful. When could we start using this card?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then said, “I’ll prepare some banks in your cities first, with the purpose of releasing personalized cards. At the same time, I’ll be providing you with transfer devices. These transfer devices aren’t that big, they’re as big as a piece of jade. As long as two parties reached an agreement on the price, they can insert their cards on this transfer device and make the transaction. It’s quite convenient to use.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “So Mister has already thought this through. Alright, I have no problems with it. We’ll go according to Mister’s plan.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “Good, then it’s settled. You need to discuss this matter with your people first. When you reach an agreement, then you can call me over and I’ll immediately build the banks.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll have to ask mister to wait. Right, Mister, how’s the outside situation doing? Do you need us to send troops?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “At this time, there’s no need. We’ve just plundered a Divine Race supply fleet. This will delay their plans since they would need to find food for themselves. There’s is also the people from the Atlanta Plane arriving at the Ark Continent. Those guys wouldn’t be a threat for some time. It’ll be a while before a fight happens, you don’t have to worry about going out for some time.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “I’m not really anxious about it. The more we drag time, the better it would be. I just want to send some Devil Legion soldiers out for a test.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Just take it slowly, there’s no need to rush. Right, in the future, I might be able to bestow special armors to the Devil Legion soldiers. When the time comes, I will inform you.”

The Great Demon King stared, “Did Mister manage to find the appropriate equipment?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Yes, didn’t the Divine Race have some ultimate weapons? If we snatch those ultimate weapons and make combat armors, then wouldn’t that be great?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King couldn’t help but get shocked. He never expected Zhao Hai would actually have this idea. Snatching ultimate weapons? Only Zhao Hai would think about it.

The Great Demon King had seen how strong ultimate weapons were. To be honest, although he had a Domain Weapon, after seeing the Divine Race’s ultimate weapon, he couldn’t help but feel a blow to his mind. The Divines were indeed worthy of their name.

Although the ultimate weapons looked simple, the Great Demon King knew that they were extremely strong, much much better compared to domain weapons.

Before the Demons met Zhao Hai, only one Demon held a domain weapon. Because of this, the Great Demon King was aware of how hard it was to manufacture weapons of this calibre. This was especially true when it comes to ultimate weapons.

Now, Zhao Hai actually wanted to make ultimate weapons. No wonder the Great Demon King was surprised. Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and smiled, “Don’t worry about it, I’ve already gained one ultimate weapon. I’m just currently waiting to get the others. I believe that we would have another great harvest soon. However, since these things are special, there are certain difficulties when it comes to mass production. I could only supply the Devil Legion in batches.”

The Great Demon King stood up and then looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, if you really managed to make ultimate weapons, please give me one.”

ZhaoHai stared, he was confused at the Great Demon King as he asked, “Your Majesty, you’re the King of the Demon Realm. Having your Devil’s War Chariot is already good. Why would you want an ultimate weapon? Do you want to enter the battlefield in the future?”

The Great Demon King stared, then he smiled bitterly and said, “Right. Even if I’m a King, I still think about these things every day.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and then smiled, “You’re really a fighting maniac. Rest assured, ultimate weapons wouldn’t be a problem. If conditions allow me to make Hell King’s ships, then I will give you one as well.”

Zhao Hai can now understand why the Great Demon King would want an ultimate weapon for himself. Ultimate weapons were extremely important for warriors. If Zhao Hai equips the entire Devil Legion with ultimate armors, then they might change their loyalty and devotion to Zhao Hai. Because of this, the Great Demon King couldn’t help but worry.

Although the Devil Legion had become strong, they still regarded the Great Demon King as their leader. If Zhao Hai bestows them with ultimate weapons, then their mentality might change.

Even if the Great Demon King’s thoughts about Zhao Hai had been influenced by the Space, it still hadn’t reached a state similar to Shue and the others. The Great Demon King still had his own thoughts and this was understandable. After all, every leader would need a steel heart in order to prosper. It would be harder to change their minds compared to ordinary people.

Zhao Hai realized this point, therefore he promised the Great Demon King that he would give him an ultimate weapon. At the same time, if permitted, the would also give the Great Demon King a Hell King’s ship.

When he heard Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King couldn’t help but stare. His heart couldn’t help but jump as he bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, thanks!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t be too polite. You’ll have to settle matters here as soon as possible so that the banks can be made.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Mister can rest assured. I’ll take care of it as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded before leading Laura and Ruyen to leave the Demon Space and return to the Hell King’s ship. Upon returning, Laura immediately turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, the Great Demon King seems to have some reservations. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have asked for an ultimate weapon.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s understandable, don’t worry about it. Let’s just let matters go on its own. I’m not afraid of his reservations, as long as he doesn’t want to rebel, then that’s fine. In the end, the Divines are still our enemies. Since the Demons are already inside the Space, then there’s no need to be anxious about it.”

Laura nodded. At this time, Lizzy came over and said, “Brother Hai, how was it?” After that, Laura relayed everything that happened back in the Demon Space.

After Lizzy finished listening, her eyes couldn’t help but blaze up as she said, “Brother Hai, the Great Demon King seems to be unable to tell good from bad. How about we teach him a lesson?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need. The Great Demon King’s position in the Demon Race is quite high. If we deal with him, then there might be a negative influence on the Demons. In any case, the Great Demon King only has this small reservation. There’s nothing bad about this.”

Lizzy was still a bit indignant, she coldly snorted and said, “We’ve been good to the Demons, yet he still had some doubts. Those kind of people needed to be taught a lesson.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’re mistaken. Who told you that good deeds are always returned? Remember, being good to others doesn’t necessarily mean that the others would be good to you. Minds of people are the most mysterious things in the world. Do you know why the Space is formidable? It’s because it can influence the minds of people, even for a little bit.”

Lizzy nodded, although she was still quite mad, she knew that Zhao Hai was correct. In this world, there were a lot of people that would bite the hand that fed them. If you think that your good deeds would be reciprocated, then you’re too naive. It won’t be long until you would end up dead.

Laura didn’t want such a serious topic to continue, so she turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you go and take a rest. A major battle wouldn’t happen in the following days.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, pay attention to Bingya and the others. If there’s any problem, then go and help them. At this time, they’re quite useful to us.”

Cai’er nodded. After that, Zhao Hai turn around to take his rest.

Chapter 883: Two Geniuses

While sitting inside a tiger-shaped tank, Theo looked outside through the tempered glass. He can see that the land here was quite fertile, no worse than any land in the Atlanta Plane. Although there weren’t any crops on these fields, one could see how fertile they were judging by how healthy the weeds on these plots were.

But this was where Theo was confused. Theo knew that no ordinary person would move out with such a land in their hands. However, the Ark Continent’s people actually moved out. There could only be two explanations to this, either they found a better place to move to, or they were forced to move out.

And the latter reason was the one he wanted to prove. This wasn’t only because of his curiosity, it was also tied to the O’Neal family’s future.

They have been on the road for three days and have encountered cities both big and small. From what they had seen so far, they can be certain that the Ark Continent’s population was very large. Who knows how much larger they were compared to the O’Neal family. However, the more their population estimate became, the more uneasy Theo was.

It wasn’t an easy task to relocate an entire continent. Even if they wanted to move, then where could they move to? Not to say about a continent this big, even an entire city moving would have many things that needed to be done. The relocation of the Ark Continent was just too sudden and strange.

While Theo was thinking about these things, the person next to him suddenly said, “Theo, what are you thinking about?”

Theo turned his head and looked at the war tank’s driver, Lewis. Theo wasn’t a war tank driver, instead, he was a magic armor pilot, a position much higher compared to a war tank driver. However, Theo didn’t underestimate Lewis. In the past, Lewis was an outstanding magic armor pilot. However, he was injured and lost his capabilities to pilot a magic armor. This caused him to drive war tanks instead. However, his status was much higher compared to any other war tank driver. Among the O’Neal family’s war tank drivers, Lewis was the most famous one.

Theo didn’t ignore Lewis, instead he replied, “Big Brother Lewis, I’m getting more and more restless. You can see how fertile the Ark Continent is. If there’s nothing bad going on, then people wouldn’t have moved out. From the cities and villages that we’ve passed through, we can be certain that the continent’s population was not less than tens of millions. These many people would need an extremely important reason to move out. I’m quite certain that they’ve come across something unordinary. We need to be careful when going forward.”

Lewis turned his head and looked at Theo, he can see the evident restlessness on the young man’s face. Theo looked at Lewis and said, “Big Brother Lewis, what’s wrong? Did I say anything bad?”

Lewis shook his head and said, “No, there’s nothing wrong about what you said. I just didn’t think that you would think up to this point. You’re correct, the Ark Continent’s migration is too suspicious. This matter involves the future of the O’Neal family, we do need to be careful.”

Theo nodded, then he turned to Lewis and said, “Big Brother, I seem to remember something about your injuries. I heard that they came from a someone in the Warrior Continent. Are those people really strong?”

These years, the Atlanta Plane was quite peaceful. Theo had yet to participate in a battle against either the Mage Continent or the Warrior Continent Because of this, he had no idea about to their strength. Since he has the opportunity, then he decided to ask.

When Lewis heard Theo’s question, his expression couldn’t help but change. Then with a low-spirited nod, he said, “Yes, very strong. I was already a God-rank magic armor at that time. When I was still in my 20s, I’m quite famous in the O’Neal family. Because of my fame, my arrogance had reached the skies. I wasn’t afraid of anybody. Then, news suddenly arrived that there was a magic silver mine on a deserted island between the warrior continent and the magic armor continent. Although its reserves weren’t a lot, it can still supply us for a period of time. When I heard this news, I immediately drove to the deserted island with my own magic armor.”

This was Theo’s first time hearing about Lewis’ matter. Because of this, he listened to it earnestly. To be honest, when Theo heard Lewis say that there was a magic silver mine on a deserted island between the Warrior Continent and the Magic Armor Continent, even his heart was moved.

Magic silver was an ore essential to the construction of a special alloy used for making magic armors. Anyone from the magic armor continent would not pass the opportunity of acquiring some.

Although Lewis shifted his gaze forward, his mouth kept moving. He continued on with his tale, “I was young and frivolous, so I wanted to claim the magic silver mine on my own. However, I wasn’t aware that this was a trap arranged by the Warrior Continent. It was only afterwards that I became aware of an unwritten custom of the Atlanta Plane. No matter which continent, when a young talent becomes famous, the other two continents would surely make plots to extinguish that talent. Also, there would always be people following that young talent to protect them. But at that time, I didn’t let my protectors follow me. In the end, I suffered a big loss and was seriously injured by a someone from the warrior continent. If it wasn’t for that expert from the family, I wouldn’t have been able to come back. The people from the warrior continent were quite strong in martial arts. They specialized in physical cultivation and were capable of fighting in the air. Because of their practice, their lifespans are much longer than the people from the magic armor continent. An important thing to note about them is their ability to sustain a fight for a long time unlike our magic armors. If we leave our magic armors, our strengths would be greatly reduced. It’s impossible for us to contend with them with our physical bodies, especially against their God-ranks. Even if their attacks couldn’t compare to our magic armors and they weren’t as fast, dealing with them isn’t easy. The longer the fight takes, the more disadvantage we would be in.”

Theo blankly listened to Lewis’ words. Lewis said a lot of things that he didn’t know. If one were to think about it, Theo was also considered to be a genius in the O’Neal family. And even he didn’t know about these things.

Lewis turned to look at Theo and whispered, “This matter isn’t something that the three continents would tell people. They will only protect the geniuses secretly. Maybe there are even experts protecting you right now.”

Theo gawked, then he forced a smile and said, “Big Brother Lewis, don’t joke with me. I’m not that talented. The family wouldn’t send people to guard me. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have sent me on this duty.” Lewis smiled faintly and said, “You don’t know that. You should know that those who came to be famous people didn’t only go through a single battle. Without undergoing a life and death trial, it would be impossible for them to become an expert.” Theo stared blankly, then he nodded as he looked out the window and said, “I will definitely become an expert. I will.” Lewis looked at Theo and smiled. He couldn’t help but think about the younger him, he had the same look as Theo. At that time he was so arrogant and was surrounded by praise. When he was injured and became unable to pilot a magic armor, people began to look at him in disappointment. Fortunately, Lewis didn’t ruin himself and turn into a good for nothing drunkard. After a period of depression, Lewis stood up again and began to drive war tanks for the O’Neal family. In the end, he became the family’s best war tank driver.

Although he was an excellent tank driver, his status is still not higher compared to magic armor pilots. However, this didn’t necessarily mean that he was lower than ordinary magic armor pilots. If one wanted to man a hundred ton vehicle, one would need nimble hands, and not everyone had this. Although this ability didn’t look much, it actually allowed a war tank driver to perform specialized tasks.

After some time of silence, Lewis suddenly stopped. This caused Theo to awaken from his thoughts as he looked at Lewis in confusion.

From Lewis’ expression, it seems like he had seen a ghost. Theo followed Lewis’ gaze and became similarly shocked. On the horizon in front of them was a sky covered by a dark mist.

It was still noon, about time for people to take their lunch, the middle of the day. However, in front of them was actually a dark sky. The heavens and the earth was covered by a dark mist! This caused everyone who saw this to stare blankly for a moment.

Theo’s face changed as he said, “Big Brother Lewis, what’s that?” Lewis recovered from his shock, his expression changed as he turned to Theo and said, “Tell everyone to prepare for a fight. I don’t feel good about this dark fog. I have killed a Dark Mage from the Mage Continent before. Among his dark magics was the dark mist. However, it wasn’t this large. Even God-rank Dark Mages would find it impossible to produce a dark mist this massive. Maybe this is the reason for the Ark continent’s migration.”

Theo didn’t dare to ignore Lewis’s words. He immediately turned and went into the interior part of the tank. There, the resting place for the staff was located. Theo went towards the magic armor pilots and then sounded an alarm. Red lights lit up from the walls as a blaring sound spread.

It didn’t take long before the alarm was heard all throughout Lewis’ war tank. The tank immediately burst into action.

Like any other war tanks similar to the one Lewis drove, each one of them had 40 people inside. 20 of them were magic armor pilots, five were war tank drivers, another five were war tank technicians, then lastly there were 10 war tank weapon operators. Since war tanks weren’t as big as the ships, their living quarters weren’t as big. However, since war tanks were expected to travel over long distances, the living quarters were still made quite ample.

Chapter 884: Yin Fire?

Theo quickly put on his own magic armor. He was a God-ranked magic armor pilot, so his armor was bigger than the one Axe had. Not only can it transform, its speed, power, and defense was also much better.

As the war tank’s roof opened up, Theo immediately drove his magic armor to fly towards the dark mist.

This was also how they usually fight in the Atlanta Plane. After an abnormality was discovered, the war tank would stop and immediately release magic armors. After all, the war tanks were simply used as a transport, the magic armors were the real firepower.

Theo carefully controlled his magic armor. He liked staying inside his mecha, he thought that the most comfortable place in the world was inside it.

He liked the feeling of being a pilot. Because of this, he was focused on the task at hand. Theo carefully looked out front to where the dark mist was located.

Upon seeing what was before him, Theo couldn’t help but clench his fist. This also made his magic armor clench its fist. Magic armors were the greatest inventions of the Atlanta Plane, it was because magic armors that the magic armor continent managed to grow to its own size.

There was one type of magic formation known as Spirit Projection Formation. The main function of this formation was to synchronize one’s own mind to an external object. Moreover, this would allow the object to be controlled as if it was one’s own limb.

This formation made magic armors formidable. Every action made by a magic armor pilot would be mimicked by the magic armor itself.

However, this magic formation also had its weak point. If one wanted to use this formation, then one would need a formidable spiritual force. Moreover, this spiritual force was different compared to the spiritual force that mages needed.

Mages used their spiritual force to control the elements. They can use incantations and with their own control of the elements they could produce their spells.

On the other hand, the spiritual force that magic armor pilots used were the purest type of spiritual force. This kind of spiritual force cannot be used to kill an enemy, instead, they were used to control things. It was important for magic armor pilots to study this kind of spiritual force. The stronger the pilot, the stronger their spiritual force was.

It was because they spend most of their time studying this spiritual force that the magic armor pilots only have stronger bodies than average mages but was way worse compared to warriors.

Inside his magic armor, Theo looked at the dark mist. Because of the formation on the magic armor, Theo can see the situation very clearly. Under the strengthening effects on the magic armor, his eyesight had also improved.

The dark mist was extremely black, he could barely see anything inside. Theo turned his head towards the others beside him and said, “What do you guys think?” His voice was also amplified by the magic armor.

Another person gave a reply, “I think we should send people inside to scout. The others will wait outside to provide support.”

Theo nodded and said, “Alright. Spirit Snake, Poison Serpent, Mad Dog, Lunatic, and Lone Wolf, you five go in and have a look. There’s no need to be thorough. Go in and when you spot something wrong, immediately retreat.”

The five magic armors complied and immediately flew towards the Dark Mist while Theo and the others remained outside. They were in high alert, ready to provide aid at any time.

The five magic armors proceeded to enter the dark mist. Due to the Dark Mist’s nature, the visibility inside was horrendous. However, the five didn’t feel anything after flying inside, the place was spiritless, it made them very alert.

The five people advanced in a 2-3 formation following a trapezoid shape. As they carefully advanced, someone’s voice was suddenly heard, “Stop, i can hear something.” The person who talked was the one named Mad Dog. After hearing him, the others stared as they immediately stopped.

Mad Dog then said, “Let’s go down. I can hear something below.” Then just as he was done talking, a bone spear suddenly flew from below stabbing towards him.

Mad Dog stared, his consciousness immediately became alert. Because of this, upon seeing the approaching bone spear, his hand immediately moved and went on to capture the projectile.

At this time, more bone spears came from below. However, due to their skill, the people from the Atlanta Plane remained unscathed.

After the group defended against the bone spears, groups of fireball suddenly came flying. These fireballs had very peculiar characteristics. Most fireballs would have a shade of red, however, this one was actually grey!

When Mad Dog saw these fireballs, his expression couldn’t help but change as he said, “Retreat immediately! This place is too strange.” The group complied as they immediately went towards the edge of the dark mist.

However, before they retreated, they first released beams of energy from their hands striking the incoming fireballs. They expected the fireballs to disappear upon being hit by the beams of energy. But contrary to what they thought, the fireballs became bigger instead. It seems like the beams of energy were consumed by the fireballs.

Mad Dog and the others became surprised upon seeing this, they immediately hastened to exit the place. Fortunately, they haven’t penetrated too deep into the Dark Mist. Before long, they exited the place. But then, another strange matter occured. The fireballs that were coming towards them stopped once they reached the edge of the dark mist, they didn’t go out even for one step.

Theo’s group were constantly paying attention to the Dark Mist, but they didn’t think that the group that just went in would actually withdraw this quickly. Moreover, they looked very distressed. Theo’s group immediately went forwards to meet the scouting team, preparing to give them aid.

However, what surprised them was the absence of any pursuing parties. Theo turned his head and asked, “Mad Dog, what happened? How come you came out this quickly?”

Mad Dog immediately replied, “Theo, what’s inside is very strange. The visibility is very low so we cannot see anything. In the beginning, we were attacked by bone spears, then after that, by several groups of fireballs. Moreover, those fireballs were unaffected by our energy beams. Instead, once the energy beams collided with the fireballs, the fireballs began to grow bigger. Because of this, we decided to retreat. Theo, ask Brother Lewis. He has experience, he might know about this matter.”

Theo gawked, then he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go. Someone stay here and guard the place. Send a report if something peculiar happens.” After that, he lead people to leave the place, keeping ten people behind to stand guard.

When Theo’s group returned to the war tank, he immediately left his magic armor. Just as he jumped down, Lewis opened the door and walked out from the driver’s chamber. Theo quickly went towards Lewis and said, “Brother Lewis, I just had Mad Dog and the others go into that Dark Mist. At first they were attacked by some bone spears. But after that, they were met with a group of fireballs. These fireballs seem to be able to consume our energy beams. Instead of being extinguished, they became even stronger. Do you know something about this?”

Lewis became stunned, “Yin attacks? Could this place be an innate Yin Domain?”

Theo looked confused at Lewis as he asked, “Brother Lewis, what’s an innate Yin Domain?”

Lewis’ tone became serious as he answered, “Innate Yin Domain is just one of its descriptions. Basically, it is a place full of Yin Qi. Such a place is able to produce undead and allow them to evolve. The fireballs that you’ve met are called innate Yin Fire. This fire extremely poisonous. Aside from sources of Yang Qi, no other thing can extinguish this fire. As long as a lick of this fire gets into your body, you will definitely be consumed. No other place can produce this Yin Fire aside from Innate Yin Domains. Innate Yin Domains also have its own special conditions. Innate Yin Domains cannot have any light coming from the sun, the Yang energy of the sun makes the existence of Yin Fires impossible. Because of this, the Sun is the natural nemesis of anything inside an Innate Yin Domain!”

After hearing Lewis say this, Theo couldn’t help but look at the Sun. It was now that he could understand why Lewis was surprised about why an Innate Yin Domain would exist here. The Sun was blatantly up in the sky, however, an Innate Yin Domain actually existed right under it. This really can’t be explained.

Lewis turned his head to a man that looked around 30 years old and had a fierce aura about him, “Mad Dog, did the fire stay inside the Dark Mist?”

Mad Dog nodded and said, “It did. Not long after we went in, we were immediately met with that fire. Since we were unable to suppress it, we decided to retreat. In the end, the fire didn’t follow us.”

Lewis nodded and said, “Nobody got caught by the fire?” Mad Dog shook his head.

Lewis then relaxed himself and said, “That’s good. Anything touched by that Yin fire would get destroyed immediately, this includes magic armors. It’s just strange. In a place where an Innate Yin Domain couldn’t possibly exist, Yin Fire can actually manifest.”

Theo didn’t like where things was going. He regained his composure and looked at Lewis, “Brother Lewis, what do we do now? Do we go in once more?”

Lewis shook his head and said, “You can’t. This Yin Fire can only be dealt with by a strong cannon and presently we don’t have one. Going in once more would just be courting death. Let’s leave two war tanks here and monitor the Dark Mist as well as see how large it is. The last war tank will be sent back to send the report. I can now probably understand why the people from the Ark Continent moved. If this place could really produce Yin Fire, then some changes should have happened in the Ark Continent. And when the night comes, the undead creatures may come out from the Dark Mist. With the calibre of the undead, the Ark Continent shouldn’t be able to stop them. Go prepare a war tank immediately. Equip it with ten magic armors and have it go back to report.”

Theo didn’t dare to be slow and immediately complied. On the other hand, Lewis didn’t leave. He knew that he couldn’t leave this place. Although he couldn’t pilot magic armors anymore, he had gone to a lot of places before. Compared to Theo and the others, Lewis’ experience was richer. He needed to remain here to guide the group.

The War tank was quickly prepared. Theo didn’t go with the war tank, instead, he selected ten magic armor pilots to go along with the returning war tank. After taking care of this, Theo went back to convene with Mad Dog and the others.

After the war tank had gone back, Lewis looked around and said, “Let’s go back to the city we stayed in last night. Don’t get too close to the Dark Mist, otherwise we may be attacked at night.” Theo nodded and sent people to contact those who were observing the Dark Mist.[1]

However, what they didn’t know was their every action and every word was being observed by someone.

At this time, Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “Innate Yin domain? Are there Underworld areas in the Atlanta Plane? Otherwise, it would’ve been impossible for them to know that. Also, is this Yin Fire strong? It seems like I need to take a look.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura smiled and said, “I knew you would like to go and see. I’m also very curious about this Yin Fire. Brother Hai, the Hell King’s ship also has the Yin attribute. Can we go and see if it’ll be good for it?”

After hearing this, Zhao Hai turned to look at the others. Seeing the anticipation in their eyes, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “Look at you, you look like children waiting to see new toys. Alright, let’s go have a look.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as the Hell King’s ship went through the space and then instantly appeared inside the Dark Mist. However, the ship’s build this time had gotten smaller.

Actually, whether the Hell King’s ship was smaller of bigger, the space inside it remains the same. This was because the ship wasn’t relying on its outward size to decide the amount that can be loaded inside it. It completely relied on its spatial abilities in this aspect. Even if Zhao Hai made the ship into a very huge vessel, he still couldn’t place more things inside it.

When the ship arrived, Zhao Hai and the others immediately walked out from their cabins. All of them curiously looked at the Dark Mist. In the past, Zhao Hai just went inside the Dark Mist in order to snatch some undead for himself.

Now that he had returned inside the Dark Mist, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get curious. However, he soon felt that there was nothing else to see here. Everywhere was just dark mist, tumbling around and obscuring visibility.

At this time, several bone spears began to fly towards the ship, aiming for Zhao Hai and the others. But Zhao Hai didn’t even spare a look at these bone spears. He knew that this kind of attack was not a threat to him.

Sure enough, just as the bone spears flew towards the Hell King’s ship’s periphery, they were immediately wiped out using the spray coming out from the waters under the ship. The bone spears weren’t even able to make a scratch on the ship’s hull.

Upon seeing that the bone spears were useless, the enemy immediately sent out groups of fireballs. Unexpectedly, they were using the same tactic that they used against Mad Dog and the others. When Zhao Hai saw these clumps of fireballs, his eyes turned bright. He knew that these were the things he was looking for. When the group of fireballs reached the Hell King’s ship, instead of having the ship extinguish it, Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift and took the fireballs in.

* * *

I’m quite baffled why they have all this tech and yet they still don’t have long range communication.

Chapter 885: A Lich’s Anger

When the grey fireballs entered the Space, Zhao Hai immediately heard a prompt, “Toxic Yin substance detected. Substance classified as Yin Flame. Extracting properties, extraction is completed. Host can now use this flame for crafting. Increasing the hell Space’s strength. Yin Flame can be added to the Hell King’s ship. The Hell King’s ship’s surface will have Yin Flames surrounding it. Yin Flame may be used for both attack and defense. Yin Flame can increase the ship’s power system as well as improve the ship’s cannons. Yin Fire Crystals can now be mined in the Hell Space. Asking host to approve all the improvements.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the grey fireballs to have this much benefits. The flame can even be used for crafting. It’s quite good.

Zhao Hai couldn’t stop himself from laughing. This was truly a pleasant surprise. “Immediately start the upgrades!”

Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, a gray radiance suddenly covered the Hell King’s ship. After the grey light vanished, grey flames started to go about and around the Hell King’s ship.

The flames seem to go in and out of the ship, looking like it was burning the insides of the vessel. However, for those standing inside the ship like Zhao Hai and the others, they can’t feel anything different at all.

Upon seeing this, Laura and the others couldn’t help but feel curious. They stretched their hands and reached out towards the flames. However, like phantoms, the flames just went through, seemingly unaffected by the hands that stretched out towards it.

At this time, another batch of bone spears came out of the Dark Mist. Zhao Hai stopped the ship’s waters from blocking the spears. Instead, Zhao Hai just allowed them to strike the ship.

Just as the bone spears were about to hit the ship, a flame wall suddenly solidified itself, blocking the bone spears from going further. As the bone spears pass through the flaming wall, one could see the spears disintegrate into nothingness.

Laura and the others couldn’t help but call out in alarm. They didn’t expect these phantom-like flames to be this powerful.

At this time, a scream was heard inside the Dark Mist. Zhao Hai looked towards the direction of the scream and said, “Who is that? Come out?!”

The Dark Mist suddenly parted, revealing the people behind them, no, they shouldn’t be called people. These ‘people’ didn’t have a corporeal form, they looked like spectres floating in mid-air.

Zhao Hai looked at these beings and couldn’t help but stare blankly. Then he immediately understood, these people were unique beings of the Underworld, the Lich.

To put it simply, the Lich Race was part of the Ghost Races.They were Darkness beings that evolved their souls to the maximum, they almost had complete immunity against physical attacks. In the Underworld, they were one of the most difficult race to deal with.

Zhao Hai didn’t think that he would meet members of the Lich Race here inside the Dark Mist. It seems like more creatures from the Underworld had come up into the Ark Continent.

After the group of Lich saw Zhao Hai, one of them said with a deep voice, “Who are you? And why are you here?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and then smiled, “This is the Ark Continent, It’s natural that I’m here. Are you from the Underworld’s Lich Race? Why would you come to the Ark Continent and cause trouble?”

Upon hearing this, the Lich seemed to turn blank. One of them turned its head to Zhao Hai and said, “Don’t talk nonsense, how could this be the Ark Continent. The Ark Continent’s laws prohibit the existence of God-ranks. We’ve been here for some time, however, we didn’t feel any change of laws. Also, from looking at your God-rank strength, how could this be the Ark Continent?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the Lich would actually know about these matters. In fact, what Zhao Hai didn’t know was that these Lich were old ghosts that lived for who knows how long. As long as they weren’t killed in battle, the Lich were basically immortal. Because of this, they were aware of many things, they’re basically living historical records..

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and then said, “This is really the Ark Continent. Because of a giant accident, the laws of the plane has been changed. This accident also opened the rift to the underworld and the Ark Continent.”

The Lich looked at each other, clearly astonished by what they heard. Zhao Hai said that the laws had been changed. In the past, they didn’t understand how a spatial barrier could get punctured, producing a spatial rift. So it turns out to be this reason. However, what puzzled them was what kind of power would have the capability of changing the laws of a plane.

A Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Nonsense, changing the laws of the plane isn’t easy. How could people possibly achieve it?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he answered, “Changing the laws of a plane certainly isn’t easy. However, some people actually used an entire country’s worth of people to perform a Blood Sacrifice to achieve it.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the expression on the Lich changed. Although they were now members of the Lich race, they were originally transformed souls, they could still recall some memories. They didn’t expect that people would have the audacity to use an entire country to carry out a blood sacrifice.

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and then said, “Although you’ve become part of the Lich Race, you seem to have retained some humanistic natures. I’m not afraid to tell you that the one who did this to the Ark Continent was the Divine Race. The Divines and the Demons invaded the Ark Continent at the same time. The Divines used an entire country to carry their blood sacrifice to break the plane’s barrier as well as change the laws. And with the appearance of the Underworld, I had no choice but to move everyone out of the continent.”

Just as Zhao Hai said this, a Lich suddenly asked, “Mister, might I know which country was used as a blood sacrifice?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Of course, the country used for the blood sacrifice was the Ocean Waves Dynasty!”

When Zhao Hai said this, the Lich couldn’t help but pause. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Did you say Ocean Waves Dynasty? Is it really the Ocean Waves Dynasty?” Zhao Hai was confused by the Lich’s response, he nodded and said, “Right, it’s the Ocean Waves Dynasty, there’s no need for me to lie about this matter.”

Upon hearing this, the Lich suddenly screamed. Then Zhao Hai saw the flames of the ship suddenly forming a wall. It seems like this scream’s power was quite huge, otherwise, the ship wouldn’t have been compelled to produce this fire wall.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. He was confused at the Lich’s reaction. He knew that the Lich didn’t intend to attack. It seems like the Lich was impacted by something. The other Lich even went forward to comfort that Lich.

Moreover, Zhao Hai can see that the Lich that attacked had the lowest strength compared to the other Lich. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he thought that the Lich might be a person. Can it be that this Lich had a relationship with the Ocean Waves Dynasty?

It took some time before the Lich calmed down. At this moment, a more elderly Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please don’t get offended. He didn’t attack intend to attack you. It’s just because he was a member of the Ocean Waves Dynasty’s Imperial family before he died. He couldn’t help but get affected by your information.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I can understand. But has this gentleman not been in the Ocean Waves Dynasty for many years?”

The Lich that screamed paused for a moment before he nodded and said, “Mister guessed correctly. It has been more than a thousand years ago when I passed away. Since then, I’ve received no news about the Ocean Waves Dynasty.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I couldn’t blame mister. The Ocean Waves Dynasty has been the base of the Radiant Church in the past hundred years. It was said that the Radiant Church’s influence was more powerful than the Dynasty’s nobles. And most of those Nobles had become fanatical followers of the church. However, the Radiant Church was a chess piece of the Divine Race. After we discovered the Radiant Church’s schemes and dealt with them, we didn’t expect them to retreat to the Ocean Waves Dynasty. After that, the Ocean Waves Dynasty’s King relinquished the throne to the Radiant Church’s Pope, changing the nation’s name to Radiant Empire. Because of what happened, the Divines chose to sacrifice the entire country for their plans.”

The group of Lich gawked, then the Lich from the Ocean Waves Dynasty sighed and said, “Alright, it has been a thousand years. For the Dynasty to turn this way doesn’t have anything to do with me. And with my current state, there’s no way for me to take revenge against the Divines.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Actually, I have news regarding mister’s enmity. The one who invaded the Ark Continent are the Taurus Divines. At this point, the Taurus Divines have basically been extinguished by me. We’re currently battling for the Taurus Continent. The Ark Continent will be left behind for the Underworld.”

The group of Lich looked blankly at Zhao Hai. They couldn’t believe what Zhao Hai just said. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “I only came here because I heard from someone that a strange flame exists. Therefore, I came to witness it for myself. I don’t have any other plans.”

The Lich looked at each other before one of them said, “Are those Iron Men your people?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s impossible for me to have subordinates like those. Due to the changes made by the Divines to the Ark Continent’s laws, spatial rifts started to appear in the Ark Continent. In addition to the Underworld, there’s also another plane that managed to connect to the continent. That plane is called the Atlanta Plane. Those Iron Men that you say came from that place. Those suits are called magic armors, the people from the Atlanta Plane are inside. They’re quite strong, and are also intruders to the Ark Continent.”

Chapter 886: Establishing the Laboratory

The Lich didn’t know what to say. They didn’t think that the Continent would have this much change. It seems like they were reading from a story book.

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and said, “Everyone, I won’t be staying here anymore. You will definitely meet the people from the Atlanta Plane once again, please be careful.” Then he turned back into the ship with the intention of leaving.

But at this time, one of the Lich suddenly said, “Mister, please wait.” Zhao Hai immediately stopped, he turned around and then said, “Do you need something?”

Among them, an elderly Lich gave Zhao Hai a salute. This salute was just like one made by Nobles, but was also different. Laura looked at the old man’s actions and her eyes shone as she whispered to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, this is a salute made by ancient Nobles. They use this whenever they have a request.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the Lich and said, “Is there something wrong?” The Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “From what we can see, Mister should be someone with an extraordinary status. Our group had long been tired of the Underworld. We want to go to all places with Mister. I don’t know if Mister can agree? We can become Mister’s slaves, we’ll follow your every bidding.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect the Lich to have this request. He looked puzzled at the LIch before he asked, “You have God-rank strength. And since you seem to the the leader of your group, then you should have an overlord-class position in the Underworld. Are you really willing to follow me and be my slaves?”

The Elder Lich smiled and said, “Correct. Just like mister said, we’re honored and famed characters in the Underworld. However, the Underworld is different compared to other places. In the Underworld almost everyone has an immortal body. So there’ll be no problem even if one doesn’t struggle to live. People would just play around and then go elsewhere. Most of us just do nothing for countless years. I don’t know how many years I have lived, but I’ve grown bored of the Underworld. If you weren’t asleep, then you would spend your waking hours doing nothing. We want to go with mister to see the world. We don’t mind being slaves”

Then Zhao Hai turned to the other Lich and said, “Do all of you share the same thoughts?”

The other Lich nodded. It’s true, they spend all day doing nothing, being in a daze the whole time. It wasn’t something people could endure, it was akin to punishment.

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and then smiled, “I can take you with me. You can bring your subordinates as well. And instead of being slaves, I’ll treat you as my friends instead.”

The Lich looked at Zhao Hai blankly. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this willing to accept them, even going so far as to treat them as friends.

The Elder Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we are from the Lich Race. Won’t our existence bring trouble to you?” Zhao Hai laughed, “That won’t be a problem. I myself am a Dark Mage, the most powerful one in the Ark Continent. The undead under my control has reached tens of millions. What can a few Lich do to affect my reputation?”

The group of Lich stared, then their expressions lit up. The Elder Lich then asked, “Might we ask how many undead can Mister’s ship hold? Our subordinates are quite a lot.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “The number’s not a problem. I can just store them in my Space. The more people the better.”

The Lich paused then he said, “Alright, then we’ll be impolite to Mister. However, most of our people cannot fly. We’ll have to ask Mister to lower his ship.”

Zhao Hai smiled before he slowly lowered the Hell King ship’s altitude. At the same time, the Elder Lich made a sound before leading the other Lich towards the ship. Before long,  a large number of undead creatures came walking from all directions.

Zhao Hai thought that the Elder Lich’s subordinates were other Lich. However, he soon found out that he was wrong. Among the undead that came from all directions, most of them were skeletons and zombies. The Lich actually numbered the least among them. It was a bit strange but Zhao Hai still took all of them into the ship.

Under the stunned gaze of the Lich, the undead went into the Hell King’s ship in droves. The ship’s size was basically ignored, it was just like a bottomless pit as it swallowed every undead.

After the last undead went into Zhao Hai’s ship, Zhao Hai turned his head and said, “Alright. Everyone, let’s go to the Divine Realm.” The Lich nodded and in the next moment the ship vanished from the Dark Mist before reappearing in the Divine Realm.

The Lich couldn’t help but get stunned upon seeing the instant change to the scenery. The Elder Lich looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I didn’t expect Mister to hold a Spatial Divergent Ability. No wonder mister can defeat the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s not just my ability that allowed me to defeat the Divines. Since you have prestigious status in the Underworld, then you should know about the Demons, right?” The Lich didn’t understand what Zhao Hai was saying. Zhao Hai just said that the Divines and the Demons invaded the Ark continent at the same time. So why would he use the Demons to explain why he defeated the Divines?

The Elder Lich still wondered, however, he nodded and said, “Yes we are. We’ve had several battles against the Demon Realm. The Demons have good fighting prowess. Even if they are dominated by the undead, they still managed to fight back. They’re the most intimidating enemies we have seen.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Lich and smiled, “The reason why I dared to deal with the Divine Race is because I managed to bring the Demons to my side. The Demons are now my subordinates. Because of this, I didn’t have any other worries and managed to focus on dealing with the Divine Race.”

Upon hearing this, the other Lich gawked. After that, the way the see Zhao Hai changed. The Lich race lived extremely long lives, so they also participated in the battles against the Demons. They didn’t expect that those terrifying Demons would actually be subdued by Zhao Hai. This was just too shocking.[1]

After seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Come with me, let’s go visit the Demon Realm.” Then with an intention, the Hell King’s ship appeared inside the Demon Space.

Upon reaching the Demon Space, the Lich were shocked yet again. They had gone to the Demon Realm before, so they could safely affirm that this place wasn’t the Demon Realm.

What made them feel even more strange was the fact that although this place wasn’t the Demon Realm, Demons actually lived inside it. They had battled with Demons many times, therefore, they knew what the Demons looked like.

Just as the Lich were confused, a prompt was suddenly heard, “Robots not belonging to the Space discovered. Proceeding to modify their program. Program modification completed. Host can now command the robots.”

Before Zhao Hai could comprehend the announcement, the group of Lich suddenly bowed and said, “We have seen the Master.”

Zhao Hai was stunned, then a wave of happiness washed over him. The Lich were wise beings, so Zhao Hai thought that the Space wouldn’t be able to do anything to them. But now, it seems that this wasn’t the case. No matter what, the Lich were still undead. To the Space, they were just another type of robots. Naturally, the Space couldn’t allow disobedient robots to exist inside it, so it immediately subdued the Lich. This was great for Zhao Hai.

After comprehending what just happened, Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “No need to be too polite. Just call me Young Master. I’ll be sending you to the Space, to Wild Dragon Island. Go and help by father-in-law research magic formations. If you want to come out and see the world outside, then don’t hesitate to tell me.”

The Lich nodded. They now regarded Zhao Hai as their master, so they respected his words.

The Lich were different compared to those beings invited by Zhao Hai to the Space. Those who were invited in could only be influenced by the Space little by little. On the other hand, the Lich were immediately subdued by the Space.

Zhao Hai also took the Lich to see the Great Demon King. But since the Great Demon King was still busy with the crystal cards, Zhao Hai didn’t stay too long.

In the meantime, Zhao Hai just threw the Lich’s subordinates to the Space. Majority of their subordinates were just ordinary undead, they didn’t even reach 9th rank. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to use them in the near future.

When he was done dealing with the undead, Zhao Hai returned to the Divine Realm after handing the Lich over to Cai’er. Cai’er would introduce the Space to the Lich and then take them to Wild Dragon Island.

The Lich have lived a long life, so even if they weren’t that intelligent, they can still make up for it with their experience. Besides sleeping, the Lich also managed to record history and some even started to research interesting things.

However, it’s just a pity that technology was completely nonexistent in the Underworld. The Undead were basically brainless beings with nothing but instinct. In this case, having the undead research was basically useless.

Now that Zhao Hai had sent them to the Space, the Lich might find something good to do. And since magic formations were profound, then they might come to love researching it.

Zhao Hai had already asked Ruyen to make a laboratory in Wild Dragon Island. Gathered in this laboratory were many types of people. There were mages, elves, dwarves, and now Lich. Zhao Hai was also preparing to bring Goblins to the laboratory in the near future.

Zhao Hai knew how good laboratories could be. Back on earth, these laboratories were key to humanity’s scientific and technological advances. Therefore, Zhao Hai was making a laboratory for himself in order to prepare for the future.

* * *

I don’t know what the plural term for ‘Lich’ is, so I just used assumed to be the same

Chapter 887: The O’Neal Family’s Response

Theo and Lewis were currently standing on top of the city lord’s mansion, looking at the Dark Mist in the distance. The people who were sent to survey the situation had found out that the dark mist had already covered the entire northern part of the Ark Continent and has been slowly creeping further. This report made Theo and Lewis’ faces ugly. Mad Dog and the others left to  send word back to the family. At this time, Theo and Lewis were inside a small city with 30 magic armors and two war tanks.

Theo looked at the Dark Mist and couldn’t help but clench his fist as he said, “I didn’t expect that the Dark Mist is still expanding. No wonder the people from the Ark Continent left. What should we  do? The family had already exerted great effort for this expedition.”

Lewis was very clear about this point. Both of them were already branded with the O’Neal family’s mark. It can be said that their fate was intertwined with the family. Lewis knew that the O’Neal family had made great efforts in order to enter the Ark Continent. If they fail this expedition, then the O’Neal family might not be able to recover. Their future would be bleak.

However, this Dark Mist wasn’t very easy to deal with. It’s certain that underneath this dark cloak was a ton of undead. Lewis can confirm this because only Undead and Dark Mages could use bone spears as an attack. And after he saw that Yin Fire, Lewis was absolutely sure that there were undead. This was because it would be impossible for Dark Mages to get in contact with Yin Fire without causing damage to themselves.

But even so, Lewis cannot display his restlessness at this time. He turned to Theo and smiled faintly, “Don’t worry, the Family will surely find a way to deal with this. There are powerful cannons on the Family’s ships.”

Theo nodded, he was still young after all. Without Lewis here, the Undead would have already caused havoc to their team. Because of Lewis, Theo was able to keep a calm mind amidst the recent developments.

Then Theo turned to Lewis and said, “Brother Lewis, will the messengers come back soon?” Lewis shook his head and said, “I’m not sure. However, I’m certain that the family would make the proper arrangements. There’s a good chance that they would send a warship here to support us. After all, warships have more firepower and can carry more troops. It can also save more energy.”

Theo stared for a moment before he gave a nod, then he said, “Brother Lewis, since the undead would only come out at night, how about we do something else during the day?”

Lewis looked at Theo and said, “Do something? What do you want to do?”

Theo smiled faintly and said, “Now that the Ark Continent’s people have migrated, the magic beasts began to thrive. Those magic beasts would be able to provide us with magic crystals. If we send our people to kill those magic beasts during the day, then we can make crystals for our own use. At the same time, we could also use this time to scout for minerals in the Ark Continent.”

Lewis thought about it for a moment before he gave a nod, “Alright, let’s go do that. We can spare ten people for that task. However, we cannot use our war tanks.”

Theo happily complied as he turned around and went to manage it. Looking at Theo’s departing back, Lewis couldn’t help but smile. After that, he returned to looking at the Dark Mist. His brow wrinkled, he was worried about the current situation. The area covered by the Dark Mist was too big. Moreover, with the rate of its expansion, who knows what kinds of undead were lurking inside. Was it worth it for the O’Neal family to fight the undead?

While Lewis was worried about these matters, Mad Dog and his team arrived at the O’Neal family’s camp located in the Rosen Empire. The O’Neal family had already occupied the entire Rosen Empire with the Patriarch moving to the Rosen Empire’s Imperial Palace.

Although Zhao Hai had relocated the entire Rosen Empire’s population, he didn’t destroy the Imperial Palace. And even if the interior decorations had been taken away, the structure was still as elegant and magnificent as before. Therefore, it’s understandable for the O’Neal Patriarch to settle there.

When Mad Dog’s group appeared outside the palace, they were stopped by two magic armors. These two magic armors were God-ranks, therefore, Mad Dog didn’t dare to be unreasonable, otherwise he would be killed on the spot. He jumped down from the war tank and then gave a bow, “Lion Squad’s Mad Dog from the Scout Team. I seek an audience with the Patriarch, I have matters to report.”

The two magic armors turned their head as they gave an announcement, “Lion Squad’s Mad Dog bears news. He asks for an audience with the Patriarch.”

Another magic armor not far away passed the message. Before long, the word got into the Imperial Palace and into the Patriarch’s living quarters. A servant then knocked on the Patriarch’s door and said, “Patriarch, Scout Team’s Lion Squad has arrived for a report. They’re asking for an audience with you.”

The O’Neal Family’s Patriarch was currently working. But when he heard the servant, he immediately send, “Send him in.” The servant complied and then turned to a distant place and gave word to a magic armor, “Send him in!” The magic armor then passed the message over until it reached the Palace’s entrance. After that, the servant led Mad Dog to the Patriarch’s room.

The Patriarch looked at Mad Dog and said, “George, you brat. What happened? Did you discover something?”

George didn’t expect the Patriarch to actually recognize him. His mood couldn’t help but get lifted as he gave a bow to the Patriarch and said, “Patriarch, it’s been ten days since we left here and headed north. However, after travelling for ten days, we actually met trouble. There is a place covered with Dark Mist. When I entered the Dark Mist to investigate, I was attacked by bone spears and after that grey fireballs. That fireball wasn’t affected by our energy beams, instead, it actually strengthened it. After we came out and consulted Big Brother Lewis, he said that we’ve come to meet an Innate Yin Domain and those fireballs are possibly Yin Fire. Because of this, he decided to send us back to give a report while they remained to take watch over the Dark Mist.”

The Patriarch stared, then he knit his brows. Naturally, he knew what innate Yin Domains were. He looked at George and said, “Has it been confirmed to be an innate Yin Domain?”

George shook his head and said, “Brother Lewis said that it had the characteristics of an innate Yin Domain. However, Innate Yin Domains don’t exist under the sun yet this one did. But even so, Brother Lewis still believes that it should be an innate Yin Domain.”

The Patriarch nodded and said, “Lewis’ assessments are always safe. Since he said so, then it seems that it is an innate Yin Domain. If that is the case, then that would be troublesome. But I don’t want to have Lewis going into the Dark Mist. You go take a rest first.” George nodded before going away.

After George left, the Patriarch turned his head and said, “Call the Generals for a meeting.” Then the servant at the door gave a sound of affirmation before leaving.

Before long, the Generals arrived at the Patriarch’s room, Axe was also present. After the group had sat down, the Patriarch said, “George from the Lion Squad just arrived. He said that after travelling north for ten days, they were met with a Dark Mist. Lewis suspects it to be an innate Yin Domain. What do you think about this?”

The people in the room turned silent. Everyone here had fought many battles. Even Axe was experienced due to his love for exploration. All present knew what an innate Yin Domain was, therefore, they couldn’t help but turn silent upon hearing the news.

After some time,  a tall general stood up and gave a bow before saying, “Patriarch, we should send more troops there. A distance of ten days isn’t far. If something happens there, then it would definitely a threat to us. Moreover, the O’Neal family already went all out in this conquest. Retreating will result in huge losses.”

The Patriarch nodded. Then another general stood up and said, “Patriarch, I think the Ark Continent’s migration has to do with this innate Yin Domain. We need to guard the boundary. From what I can see, we should send a battleship over for support. At the same time, we should request some strong cannons from the family as soon as possible.”

The Patriarch gave another nod. Then another general stood up and said, “Patriarch, I think we should also quicken our southern survey. The south is too close to the Family. If a threat appears there, then the Family might be threatened.”

The Patriarch hesitated for a moment before he nodded, “That’s rational. We need to focus on the south as well. Axe, do you have anything to say?”

Axe stood up, gave the Patriarch a bow, and said, “Father, we’ve already occupied the Ark Continent. It’s not clear why the people of the continent really left. And now, there’s the innate Yin Domain. I think we should ask for more firepower from the family. We also need to adjust some magic armors in order to look for the resources of the Ark Continent and then mine them. This would fund the Family’s operations, we need to recoup our expenses as soon as possible.”

The Patriarch looked at Axe and gave a satisfied nod as he said, “My son has really grown up. That is a good idea. The dangers of the Ark Continent is still unknown to us, we must be ready to retreat at a moment’s notice. However, if we retreat, that would be a huge loss to the family. The best thing we could do right now is to scour the continent for any mineral resource and mine it.”

The generals agreed. In fact, the main reason they attacked the Ark Continent was to get commodities and minerals. If they didn’t get any minerals here because they were busy finding out why the Ark Continent’s people migrated, then that would just be putting the cart before the horse.

Even if the Ark Continent had turned dangerous and they needed to retreat, they still need to mine for minerals as much as possible. This would minimize the losses to the family.

After seeing that everybody agreed, the Patriarch nodded and said, “Pass this order. The Victory and the Glory would immediately return to the family to be restocked with 1000 strong cannons and an additional 10 thousand magic armors  as soon as possible. At the same time, the Tyrant will carry a thousand magic armors and 50 war tanks in order to support the Lion Squad.”

Those present stood up and immediately went on to execute the command. After they left, the Patriarch lightly frowned and said, “Interesting. There’s actually an innate Yin Domain here. The Ark Continent is getting more and more peculiar. Who knows what else we could find.”

Zhao Hai was also  listening to the meeting. After the generals left, he turned to Laura and said, “It looks like the O’Neal family had started to become careful. I’m afraid their southern scouts would quickly discover the spatial rifts to the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm. I want to see how they react after seeing those two places.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “If I was the O’Neal family’s Patriarch, in addition to sending people to monitor the Underworld and mining the Ark Continent, I would also send people to investigate the Demon Realm. At the same time, I would send people to attack us in the Divine Realm, just to see how strong we are.”

Zhao Hai smiled as well and said, “They have a lot of things to do. I just don’t know if they have enough manpower to do it.”

Laura chuckled and said, “Well, they surely have enough troops. From what we just heard, they wouldn’t use too much magic armors when mining for ores. And since there’s no danger in the Ark Continent, those magic armors should be enough. It’s the same with the Demon Realm. In this case, their troops can only be divided into two; the ones guarding the Dark Mist, and the other half can be allocated to us. However, I’m not sure about how much they’ll send for the attack.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I think they shouldn’t send too much to attack us. What we need them to do is to enter the Divine Realm and then we’ll  toss them to the Divines. Meanwhile, after they finish mining, we could just steal it off of their hands. Wouldn’t that be better?”

Laura and the others chuckled. Then Lizzy said, “Recently, I’ve been sensing that Brother Hai really wants to steal. You really want to snatch everything. Brother Hai, if you see a girl in the future, will you snatch her as well?”

Zhao Hai pretended to lower his head as if he was thinking. After some time, he nodded and said, “That’s a good idea. I haven’t had a new wife for some time. It seems like now’s a great chance.” Then after he said that, he proceeded to run away.

After hearing Zhao Hai say this, Laura and the others immediately chased Zhao Hai. Naturally, they knew that Zhao Hai was just messing around. They just wanted to play along with their husband’s antics.

After some time, Zhao Hai stopped. He just sensed a call coming from a messenger fish. Zhao Hai took the messenger fish and saw that it was the one that belonged to Bingya. Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the other and then smiled, “It looks like we have something to do.” Then he spoke to the messenger fish, “Bingya, it’s Zhao Hai.”

Chapter 888: Unprecedented Crisis

Bingya’s voice was then heard, “Mister, the work is done. You can make your move at any time.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Don’t leave the area. Only move when I give the signal. Don’t let the Divines discover your actions, we need to make a surprise attack.”

Bingya replied, “Yes. Mister can rest assured, the Divines have centralized the vassal soldiers in one area, we aren’t so easily found.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “How are the Divines solving the food problem?”

Bingya smiled faintly and said, “The Divines are strictly monitoring the grain distribution. At the same time, they are also sending a lot of soldiers out in order to hunt magic beasts. The grains that the vassal soldiers were receiving have become less and less. However, the Divines didn’t stop the vassals from hunting for themselves.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he replied, “The Divines didn’t want the vassal soldiers to have suspicions. Tell the vassal races to not worry and not to show any hostility to the Divines. Wait until I arrive, then we can deal with the Divines.” Bingya gave an agreeing sound.

Zhao Hai smiled and then stored the messenger fish. After that, he turned to Laura and said, “It’s time to move.” Laura smiled faintly and said, “Do we make a move on their supply ships? If we do, then the Divines would surely starve.”

Zhao Hai replied, “I know they’ll send more food soon. And in addition to food, they might send more manpower and Supreme Elders this way. At this point, they should have already suspected that the Scorpio Supreme Elder had met an unfortunate end..” Laura nodded, then she looked at Zhao Hai and frowned, “So Brother Hai, what do we do? Do we deal with their base? We can’t just deal with them without suffering any losses.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Let’s just wait. If we can’t deal with the supplies, then we’ll deal with the base. In any case, there’s no way for them to catch up to us.”

When she heard this plan, Laura didn’t stop it. She knew that Zhao Hai already had Cai’er monitor the seas for the next few days. Once they discover the Divine Race’s supply ships, then they would proceed to attack.

Cai’er was already at work. She didn’t even need to be focused on this task, as long as she paid attention to it from time to time, then it would be fine. At this time, Zhao Hai’s attention was turned to the O’Neal family.

Not only did the family send scouts to the northern part of the continent, they also sent a team down south. However, that team has yet to arrive at the Buddha Empire. Naturally, it was still impossible for them to discover the Demon Realm’s spatial rift. But they were close to arriving at the Accra Mountains.

Zhao Hai still had some undead mining for ores in the Ark Continent. However, their quantity wasn’t a lot and majority of them were iron armor beasts. There were also mining teams present in the Demon Realm as well as in the Taurus Continent.

The third day after Zhao Hai and Bingya talked, Cai’er told Zhao Hai that the Divine Race’s supply fleet had come. The transport fleet this time included warships aside from ordinary cargo ships. However, one could see that the amount of grain being shipped has been reduced.

Zhao Hai saw the situation and couldn’t help but smile as he said, “It seems that the Divines had no way of collecting ships in a short time. However, it also seems like they’re carrying more spatial equipment this time.”

Laura looked at the supply ships and said, “Will you make a move now, Brother Hai?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Of course. Let’s go and see who they sent this time to suppress my undead.” After that, Zhao Hai and the ship disappeared and reappeared once more in a place not too far from the fleet. Then Zhao Hai slowly increased the ship’s size as they approached the Divines.

Naturally, the Divines managed to spot the Hell King’s ship and immediately responded. The warships quickly surrounded the cargo vessels. At the same time, the people from the ships flew up.

But what made Zhao Hai confused was the lack of Supreme Elders. These people should know that besides Supreme Elders, nothing could bring any threat to him. Why didn’t the Divine Race send a Supreme Elder?

While Zhao Hai was confused, the sky suddenly turned black. Zhao Hai turned his head and saw a starry sky. There were large and small meteorites along with various planets. Not far away from these small celestial bodies was a star emitting a large amount of heat.

Zhao Hai and the others stared at this situation, enamored by the scene in front of them. This was especially true for Laura and the others. They didn’t know about outer space, naturally it was impossible for them to know what they were seeing.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was looking at it with curiosity. Although it was similar to the outer space that he remembered, he was sure that they weren’t out in space. There was no gravity in outer space, people just float in mid-air. There’s no air in space as well. However, those things were present where they were. Zhao Hai can be certain that this was the doing of the Divine Race.

Formation! This was the first word that popped into Zhao Hai’s mind. Zhao Hai was almost sure that this was a formation established by the Divines. However, he didn’t know what kind of formation this was.

He didn’t expect the Divines to have this kind of weapon. It can actually changed the environment around them. This caused Zhao Hai to anticipate what would happen next.

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the others and said, “Be careful, we’ve fallen into the Divine Race’s formation. I believe the Divines will attack us soon.”

Laura and the other nodded, but they didn’t worry too much. Zhao Hai’s abilities made them confident. Zhao Hai was almost invincible.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind this as he commanded the ship’s cannons to hit the celestial bodies at the distance. The energy beams launched out from the cannons and quickly reached the target. Several meteorites were destroyed immediately but the bigger planets only had a big hole. Everything was just like what would happen in outer space.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. To be honest, his understanding of formations was too poor. On the other hand, the Divine Race’s formations were truly mystical. Trapping those who were beginners to magic formations would be easy for them.

At this time, Zhao Ha discovered that several planets had linked with each other. Then, these white links connected into the Taurus constellation. Before long, a huge golden bull rushed straight towards the Hell King’s ship.

Zhao Hai frowned, these planets reminded him about the Taurus Supreme Elder. It was likely that this attack was the same one used by the Taurus Supreme Elder while using the Taurus Ultimate Weapon.

Zhao Hai didn’t make a move and just waved his hand. After doing that, the cannons on the ship immediately launched its attacks towards the incoming bull. 100 energy beams coalesced and became one huge beam and hit the bull. However, something out of Zhao Hai’s expectation happened. The bull just blurred for a moment before it continued on towards the Hell King’s ship.

At this moment, Zhao Hai didn’t have enough time to hide. When the bull approached the ship, the waves went on to mitigate its speed. However, the bull’s radiance just decreased, it didn’t vanish.

The bull rushed to the ship amongst the waves of water before it slammed on the ship. This caused the ship to sway gently.

This sway might be small, but it still made Zhao Hai frown. He discovered that this attack was actually stronger than the ones made by the Taurus Supreme Elder.

At this moment, Zhao Hai felt something rushing to the ship. When he turned his head, he saw several stars forming the sagittarius pattern. Then a horse-archer pulled his bow and sent a light arrow towards Zhao Hai.

It was time for Zhao Hai to move. With an intention, the ship shrunk as it quickly dodged to the side. But before Zhao Hai could calm down, the light arrow actually curved and homed into the ship.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai immediately made the cannons fire at the arrow. However, the result was the same as the Taurus bull. Although the magic cannons had hit the beam, the arrow only lost a bit of light as it continued to shoot towards the ship.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai coldly snorted and waved his hand. A giant scorpion appeared right by him and moved forward to meet the incoming arrow. When both became closer to each other, the scorpion used its tail to strike the arrow. With a banging sound, the arrow vanished.

Zhao Hai used this opportunity to return to his cabin and open the monitor. In the past, he was fortunate to escape the Dao Lotus due to the monitor. Zhao Hai wanted the monitor to help him this time as well.

However, Zhao Hai was left disappointed. The monitor was also confused, there simply wasn’t anything useful in its display. After Zhao Hai saw this, his expression changed. He understood that the Space’s monitor wasn’t all-powerful. Things like the Divine Race’s formations weren’t able to be penetrated by the Space.

This was equal to erasing Zhao Hai’s advantage. If the monitor was really rendered useless, then it’s possible that Zhao Hai was in real danger.

At this moment, Zhao Hai felt an unprecedented crisis!

Chapter 889: Way To Break The Formation!

Laura and the others were with Zhao Hai. They also saw the monitor’s display. Since this wasn’t something they had seen before, they became flustered after a while.

While Laura and the others panicked, Zhao Hai actually kept his calm. After a moment he opened his mouth and called out, “Cai’er, Cai’er, are you there?”

But Cai’er didn’t reply which was unprecedented. Under normal circumstances, Cai’er would immediately reply to Zhao Hai’s call. Zhao Hai can still feel his connection with Cai’er, but it seems like it has been blocked by something. At this moment, they had no way of contacting each other.

Zhao Hai’s face turned uglier. He slowly walked out of the cabin and looked all around. The scorpion was still by the ship’s side. One the other hand, the Taurus and Sagittarius constellations were constantly attacking the ship. But with the ship’s cannons, ram, waves, and poles moving to defend, the enemy had no way of dealing with Zhao Hai.

However, Zhao Hai soon noticed that on the left side of the Hell King’s ship, a constellation that looked like a goat lying on the ground and another constellation that was two fishes entangled with each other.

The two constellations slowly formed. Then, from the capricorn constellation,  a goat with two curved horns rushed out. At the same time, two fishes also came out from the pisces constellation. Both were rushing towards the Hell King’s ship.

Zhao Hai gawked, then he immediately ordered the ship’s cannons to attack the goat and the fishes. The waves went in to help as well. The task of dealing with the bull and the archer was left to the ship’s ram and pole. Zhao Hai was now sure that he was dealing with at least four Supreme Elders this time; the Taurus, Capricorn, Pisces, and Sagittarius. It seems like they’ve prepared this formation to kill him here.

At this time, Laura, with a scared tone, asked, “Brother Hai, what do we do now?” Zhao Hai looked at Laura and smiled, “Don’t be scared, it’s fine. They just want to drag us in. We don’t  have to fear when it comes to this battle. If they really wanted to stall for time, then let’s just see who comes out on top.”

Just as Zhao Hai said that,  a huge meteor was suddenly spotted heading towards the ship. The ship didn’t respond for a while, but just as the meteorite was about to hit it, flames immediately formed a wall. The meteorite was turned into ash, but not before shaking the ship.

At this time, more meteorites went crashing towards the ship. This caused Zhao Hai’s expression to change. He can now affirm that there weren’t only four Supreme Elders present. Instead, there should be five. Four were carrying the constellation attacks while one controlled the meteorites. Without a fifth elder present, the formation wouldn’t have been this stable.

Zhao Hai’s expression was ugly. Now that his connection with the Space was lost, asking for help from the Space was impossible. And although there were a lot of undead inside the ship, the strength of those undead weren’t much help compared to his current enemies. If he released the undead, then they would just be annihilated.

Zhao Hai didn’t know what kind of formation the Divines had used this time. However, there was one thing he can be sure of, this formation amplified the attacks made by the Supreme Elders. It can be said that once the continents worked together, then they would be able to increase the power of their ultimate weapons by many folds.

It was this point that Zhao Hai was careful of. To be honest, Zhao Hai wasn’t threatened by the ultimate weapons. What he was taking in mind was the Divine Race’s great formations.

The reason Zhao Hai was thinking about these formations was because they were able to cut his communication with the Space. If Zhao Hai wasn’t careful, then all of the Divine Realm’s ultimate weapons would gang up on him. Their power would surely be formidable.

If the Divines knew about Zhao Hai’s thoughts, then they would surely rage at him. Zhao Hai was currently trapped, but now he was even thinking about their formation.

Zhao Hai looked out and saw that the meteorites were still coming. Then his staff turned into a huge hammer as he proceeded to smash the meteorites one after another. As long as the hammer hits the meteorites, the meteorites would immediately be crushed.

While Zhao Hai was pounding at the meteorites, he was also keeping attention to everything around him. He didn’t want to spend too much time with the Divines, he needed to find a way to break the formation.

And just as Zhao Hai was looking at the meteors as well as the planets, he found out that the other planets were proceeding to smash themselves towards the Hell King’s ship. If those managed to hit the ship, then things would surely become more troublesome.

While Zhao Hai was paying attention to these celestial bodies, he suddenly discovered something peculiar. The formation of meteors and planets only had one sole body that stayed stationary all throughout the event, it was a star.

This discovery made Zhao Hai stare for a moment, then he decided to take the risk. With only a thought, Zhao Hai directed the ship towards that single star.

The reason Zhao Hai discovered this peculiarity was not only because this star remained stationary, it was also because this was the only star present in the skies.

Upon ruminating on this thought, Zhao Hai immediately went to deal with the star. The Hell King’s ship was very fast. In just a blink of an eye, he had almost reached the star. The waves underneath had wrapped the entire ship. A fire wall also supported the ship’s advance. But even so, Zhao Hai could still feel the heat coming out from that star.

Zhao Hai didn’t care so much about this as he went straight towards the star. However, something made Zhao Hai feel strange. He already pierced through the star, but the formation was still up.

Zhao Hai’s expression changed, then he muttered, “Did I guess wrongly? That’s impossible. In this great formation, everything other than this star had moved. This star should be the key to breaking the formation. Why was my action useless?”

Laura and the others couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai was planning to go straight towards the star. However, they still decided to trust Zhao Hai. Nobody moved as they all waited for a result.

After seeing that nothing happened as they clashed with the star, Laura and the others felt relieved. But at the same time, their current situation didn’t change.

Zhao Hai calmly scanned his surroundings, the heavenly bodies were still going towards the ship. The attacks from the four constellations also kept coming. This was not what Zhao Hai expected.

Zhao Hai looked at the star and saw no change. However, Zhao Hai still believed that this was the key for their escape. The ship just passing through the star didn’t affect this belief. If the star wasn’t the key, then it would’ve used its high temperature to assault the ship. However, the star stayed there, not doing anything. This was the flaw made by the other party. Their wisdom had caused their ruin.

However, Zhao Hai’s attack didn’t do anything to the star. So how could Zhao Hai get out of his current situation?

As he was thinking about the solution, Zhao Hai kept waving his staff as he smashed the incoming meteors. Zhao Hai suddenly thought about the contents of a book he had read before. In fact, there were a lot of books with the same content. Any big  formation would surely have their own core, and that core would need to be protected for the formation to continue existing. Take this formation for example, its core was surely supported by smaller formations.

However, Zhao Hai’s understanding with regards to formations was just too low. Him being able to break this formation was close to impossible. So what can he do now?

Zhao Hai frowned. And then his thoughts turned back to the time where he managed to break the Dao Lotus’ formation. At that time, it wasn’t so difficult. Was that because the Dao Lotus had no one commanding it?

As this thought passed through his mind, Zhao Hai’s gaze couldn’t help but shake. Since he had no way of contacting the Space, Zhao Hai’s means of action became limited. At this time, all he had was his staff, the Hell King’s ship, the scorpion, his undead. But among all other things that he could use, Zhao Hai actually forgot about one thing, the Dao Lotus!

The Dao Lotus was inside his body, not in the Space. Therefore, Zhao Hai can definitely use the Dao Lotus this time. When he thought of this, Zhao Hai immediately took the Dao Lotus out from his dantian. Zhao Hai didn’t use the Dao Lotus to defend himself, instead, he directed the lotus to attack the star.

Break the firmament of reality!

Zhao Hai suddenly thought of these words. Although these words only appeared on novels and might be ineffective at this time, Zhao Hai still tried. Therefore, he thought of these words as he sent the Dao Lotus out.

After releasing the lotus, Zhao Hai began to pay attention to it. The Dao Lotus didn’t meet with any trouble as it flew directly towards the star. The lotus looked as if it was going to be swallowed by the heat. However, from his connection to the lotus, Zhao Hai can feel that the lotus was spinning, it was still operating as normal.

Zhao Hai then controlled the Dao Lotus to launch an attack on the star. The eight trigrams appeared from the lotus; earth, wind, thunder, fire, mountain, water, heaven, and marsh. Then the lotus proceeded to rotate quickly, the eight trigrams followed along with it. In the end, the Dao Lotus was almost unrecognizable, the figure that can be seen right now was the scene of Primal Chaos!

Chapter 890: Most Violent Way

Zhao Hai hadn’t met this situation before. He just commanded the Dao Lotus to attack, but it seems that the Dao Lotus had a mind of its own and made its own move. This made Zhao Hai puzzled.

At this time, the scene of primal chaos exploded fiercely. Following a banging sound, the star vanished alongside the entire starry sky.

Zhao Hai looked outward and saw that the blue skies had returned. Not far away from him was the Divine Race’s grain fleet. There were five Divines surrounding the fleet, all had difficult expressions on their faces. One of them had a rotating plate on his hand while the other four were in full body armor. Zhao Hai could recognize the Supreme Elder of the Taurus Clan among the armored men. Although he didn’t know about the other three, Zhao Hai could still fairly guess who they were.

The one with two curved horns on his helmet should be the Capricorn Continent’s Supreme Elder. The one with a big pair of wings and was equipped with a bow and arrow should be the Sagittarius Continent’s Supreme Elder. And the one with fish fins on his armor should be the Pisces Continent’s Supreme Elder.

The aura of these people wasn’t small. The oldest one among them should be the Taurus Supreme Elder, the others seem to be younger.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t have time to talk to them as he heard Cai’er calling out to him. Cai’er appeared in front of Zhao Hai and then hugged his neck as she cried, “Young Master, young master, you just disappeared. I can’t find you. I was so scared.”

Zhao Hai lightly rubbed Cai’er’s head and said, “Cai’er, don’t be afraid. This Zhao Hai will never leave you.” After some time, Zhao Hai managed to calm Cai’er down. At this time, Laura and the others walked towards Zhao Hai. They looked at Zhao Hai with sincere gazes. They knew Zhao Hai would be able to solve this crisis.

Then Zhao Hai looked at the Divines and said, “And which Supreme Elders do I have the privilege to meet? I already know old Taurus, so there’s no need for introduction. How about I guess the others? Hmm, you should be the Capricorn Continent’s Supreme Elder. Should I call you Moroga?”

Moroga just snorted and didn’t answer Zhao Hai. Although he still had his proud look, his eyes were full of dread.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he turned his head to the person with wings and was equipped with a bow. “You should be the Sagittarius Continent’s Supreme Elder. Please forgive me, I don’t know your name.”

The Supreme Elder had a calm expression as he gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “Nice to meet you, my name is Shi.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to the elder with fins on his suit, “And you should be the Pisces Continent’s Supreme Elder. I apologize for not knowing your name.”

The Supreme Elder of the Pisces continent also gave a salute and said, “Mingdasir has seen mister Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Then he turned his head to look at the person holding the plate, he smiled faintly and said, “I’d like to guess this elder’s identity. If I have not guessed wrong, the formation was your doing. And the reason you’re able establish the formation was because of your formation plate. Since your formation allows ultimate weapons to coordinate with each other, you’re status shouldn’t be that difficult to guess.”

The Supreme Elder looked calmly at Zhao Hai. Seeing that the other party had stayed silent, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Divine Realm has 13 continent. Each continent had their own Ultimate Weapon. 12 of the continents have their names going according to the constellations, only the Central Continent did not. At the same time, the 12 continents have combat suits that correspond to their continent’s name. As far as I know, there’s no word about the Central Continent having their own combat suit.”

The Central Continent’s Supreme Elder’s eyes shrunk upon hearing Zhao Hai. Noting this small detail, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Central Continent’s Ultimate Weapon should be that formation plate in your hand. That plate could establish a formation that would allow the 12 continent’s ultimate weapons to coordinate. If my assumptions are true, then you should be the Central Continent’s Supreme Elder. But I have to apologize for not knowing your name.”

The Supreme Elder looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite. Mister’s guess is correct, I am indeed the Central Continent’s Supreme Elder. I’m just known as Elder Star. I didn’t think that mister would actually break the formation that we’ve prepared for a long time. Mister’s strength is truly one of a kind.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It is Elder Star that is being too polite. It seems like you’ve come here to kill me. Am I correct?”

Elder Star looked at Zhao Hai and then sighed, “To be honest, I didn’t want mister to become my enemy. Mister’s strength is beyond my expectations. However, Mister is just too strong, to the point of being a threat to the Divine Race. Because of this, I have no choice by to deal with Mister.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Elder Star really says interesting things. You don’t want to become my enemy? Then why did the Divines open a spatial rift to my Ark Continent? Why did the Divines sacrifice millions of the Ark Continent’s people, both young and old, for your blood sacrifice? My actions are something that the Divine Race had brought onto itself. You really think that the Divines could rein in every plane. However, you don’t realize that you’re just chess pieces for another person. A dog being commanded. A threat to the Divine Race’s existence? Hahahaha, the Divines shouldn’t exist to begin with!”

After Zhao Hai said that, the faces of Elder Star and the others turned ugly. Elder Star coldly snorted and said, “Zhao Hai, don’t think that you’re great just because I spared a good word or two for you. You think you can escape from our attacks?”

Zhao Hai laughed once more and replied, “Escape? Why would I escape? I want to collect all of your Ultimate Weapons for my own use. Did I just come here to watch you and run? And you hold me here while your grain ships would escape? Stop dreaming. From what I can see, there’s five of you here. There are still four Supreme Elders not accounted for. Two should be back defending your continents. As for the other two, are they planning to head here and surround me?”

As Zhao Hai said that, the expressions of the Divines changed. Then at this moment, an extremely huge whirlpool suddenly appeared on the sea. The entire Divine Race fleet was swallowed up, nothing but those Divines who flew were left.

When all the ships had vanished, a small ball suddenly flew out from the sea and headed towards the Hell King’s ship before plopping on top of Zhao Hai’s head.

That small ball was Bubble, the source of Myriad Water. Before Zhao Hai left the continent, he had Bubble released to the sea in order to swallow the grain ships into its own storage space.

To be honest, Zhao Hai can deal with five of these Elders at once. However, if he did that, then he would have to use his true strength. This would cause the plane’s suppression on him to become stronger. If he was unlucky, then he might prematurely ascend. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t proceed to quickly deal with the five elders. The reason he talked with them was in order for Bubble to have time to prepare. This ended with the grain ships being swallowed up.

Moreover, the words that Zhao Hai said wasn’t all just for the sake of conversation. The two Supreme Elders guarding the Taurus Continent were indeed heading here. They were the Cancer Continent and the Leo Continent’s Supreme Elders.

The two arriving here was something that Zhao Hai desired. Amidst the expressions of the Supreme Elders, Zhao Hai gave a smile and said, “Ever since I was born, today’s fight was the hardest one I’ve encountered. But everyone, I won’t be here for long. See you next time!” After he said that, Zhao Hai vanished along with the Hell King’s Ship.

Seeing Zhao Hai vanish, the expressions of the Supreme Elders changed. This was especially evident in Gold Ben as he said, “Not good! Nobody is left to defend our base in the Taurus Continent! Zhao Hai will attack!” When they heard this, the Supreme Elders’ expressions turned ugly. Elder Star immediately said, “Quick, everyone go back to the base. We cannot allow Zhao Hai to destroy it!” After that, all of them flew towards the Taurus Continent with all their might. But unfortunately for them, nobody can beat a Space Ability user when it came to mobility. They were bound to be defeated.

When the Hell King’s ship disappeared from the sea, it quickly re-emerged in an area not far away from the Divine Base in the Taurus Continent. After appearing, Zhao Hai immediately took a messenger fish and said, “Bingya, Bingya, are you there?’

Bingya’s voice came, “Mister, I’m here.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good. Listen, have the vassal soldiers prepare. We’ll be dealing with the base. At this moment, the base has no Supreme Elder defending it. It’s time to attack.”

Bingya gave a nod, then he gave an affirmation before putting the messenger fish away and preparing for the attack. Zhao Hai looked at the base and snorted, “It’s about time you fall.” Then he made the Hell King’s ship advance.

While the ship advanced, its size began to gradually increase. In the end, the ship became the size of a hill. At the same time, Zhao Hai released the scorpion as well as Bubble.

The Divine Race’s base wasn’t too far from the sea. This was made in order for them to receive supplies much quicker. But this also gave Bubble the chance to show his might.

Zhao Hai’s speed was very fast. While advancing, the ship’s cannons fired beams of light. Bubble went to the sea and began to make huge waves that crashed towards the base. These attacks caught the Divines off-guard.

Zhao Hai also released a large amount of undead to overrun the base. Although the Divines were fighting back with their cavalries and cannons, their progress wasn’t very good.

There were 20 Domain Weapon experts who went out of the base, but they were eliminated instantly by the Hell King’s ship. The ship’s attacks were now more powerful thanks to the yin flame. This flame was quite sinister, its attacking strength was nothing to scoff at.

Although it was still daytime and sunlight was the best counter to yin flames, that rule only affects ordinary yin flames. Zhao Hai’s yin flames don’t have this weakness.

However, the Divine Race’s base was built really well. Layers upon layers of protective formations made it hard for Zhao Hai to make a proper attack.

Zhao Hai knew that he couldn’t deal with 100 million Divine Race soldiers in a short period of time. And it would be more troublesome if the Supreme Elders arrive. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to have the Hell King’s ship hit the base head on.

The Divines constructed their base on a mountain, completely hollowing its insides. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to use the ship to collapse the mountain in one go.

Outside the base, Bingya, who was preparing to cooperate with Zhao Hai along with the vassal soldiers, stared blankly as Zhao Hai drove the ship to slam the mountain. It looked like a suicidal move.

Bang. The sound of collision reverberated as the mountain collapsed. Dust and debris went everywhere. Some huge rocks even managed to fly towards the vassal soldiers.

Upon seeing this, Bingya became shocked. However, he quickly recovered as he gave an order, “Quickly hide!” The vassal soldiers weren’t fools, they couldn’t just stand there and wait to be smashed. They immediately scattered in all directions. Zhao Hai’s attack gave them an extreme shock.

On the other hand, plenty of Divines inside the base weren’t able to run away and were directly buried alive. Although there were people who managed to escape, all of them couldn’t help but stare dumbly at what just happened. Their base was just destroyed, they were too shocked to think about escaping.

The Divines had thought about ways Zhao Hai could use to break through their base, and they even made all sorts of precautions. However, they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would use this barbaric method. Moreover, he even managed to destroy everything. The Divines were turned silly. All of their confidence and pride were now gone. For some, the only thing that was left was deep fear!

However, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to let them off. The undead encircled the Divine race army. Only a single word was required and Zhao Hai would be able to eliminate all of them.

Chapter 891: Shock That The Undead Brought

At this time, only 40 million out of 100 million Divine Race soldiers were left. The others were buried under the mountain.

Although the Divines were very strong, the weight of a mountain wasn’t something they can just neglect. Those Divines buried were more unlucky than lucky.

Even if those left were already surrounded, Zhao Hai didn’t order the Undead to attack. He discovered that those who were left had already lost their will to resist. In this case, there’s no point in killing them.

Sure enough, Zhao Hai’s thought was correct. Except for a few people, the Divines who were being surrounded had fear plastered on their faces.

At this time, Zhao Hai had his ship go towards the Divines. He looked at them and said, “Put down your weapons. I’ll send you to another place, you’ll be living there from now on. Those who resist will die!”

The Divines gawked when they heard Zhao Hai. They looked at each other, they didn’t know what to do. Then, one person dropped his weapon, then another one followed, then another. It didn’t take too long before all the Divines had disarmed themselves.

Zhao Hai looked at the Divines before opening a spatial rift. After the huge rift appeared in the air, Zhao Hai said, “Go in.” When the Divines let go of their weapons, they also let go of their dignity and pride. They didn’t resist and just accepted their fate as they flew towards the spatial rift.

Naturally, there were some who decided to rebel. However, even before they made a move, the undead were already on the move. Due to them being disarmed, they were too easy to capture.

After most of the Divines had entered the spatial rift, Zhao Hai turned his attention to the collapsed base. He waved his hand as a black gas surrounded the mountain.

The black gas got thicker and thicker. In the end, the entire mountain was covered in the black gas. After completing this, Zhao Hai shifted his gaze towards the vassal soldiers in the distance.

When the mountain base collapsed and the debris went flying everywhere, the vassal soldiers scattered when they fled. Now, they slowly gathered and reformed themselves.

At this time, Bingya and the others went to the Hell King’s ship and bowed, “We have seen Mister Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai looked at them and nodded. “You’ve done well. Hahaha. However, you need to tell the vassal soldiers to leave here as soon as possible. I believe the seven Supreme Elders would be here soon.”

When Bingya heard this, he paused for a moment before his expression changed, “Mister, I will immediately tell them to leave.” Then he quickly flew towards the vassal races.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at Laura and smile, “While they are leaving, we’ll go there for a while.” While he was talking, Zhao Hai pointed towards the black fog.

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Alright, let’s go.” After that, Zhao Hai commanded the Hell King’s ship to enter the black fog and they stayed there.

If other people could see the situation inside the Dark Mist, then they would certainly be surprised. From the collapsed mountains, Divine Race soldiers crawled one by one out of the debris. But this time, all of them had been turned into undead.

The reason why Zhao Hai wanted to cover the mountain with his magic was to turn those who died into undead. This way, his number of undead would be boosted even further.

After Zhao Hai entered the Dark Mist, he immediately opened the monitor to look at the Supreme Elders. At this point, the Supreme Elders had ugly expressions as they flew towards the Taurus Continent. They were already aware that they had been played by Zhao Hai.

After two hours, the Supreme Elders had entered the Taurus Continent, only too see that their base had been covered by a dark mist.

When the group saw this situation, their expressions couldn’t help but turn ugly. After some time, Elder Star said, “It looks like we’re late.”

The anger in Gold Ben’s Eyes were quite evident. With burning eyes, he said, “This is Zhao Hai’s black magic. He’s too ruthless.”

Elder Star turned his head to the others and said, “Let’s go and take a look. We’ll see what Zhao Hai plans to do this time. Be careful, don’t go too far from each other. If Zhao Hai is inside the dark mist while we’re separated, we won’t be able to react to his attack.”

The group nodded. At this point, they feel dread upon thinking of Zhao Hai’s strength. Because of this, the group didn’t separate as they entered the dark mist.

They were peak experts of the Divine Race, their Divine Sense were very powerful. However, they discovered that their divine sense had been limited inside this dark mist.

In the past, Zhao Hai’s dark mist wouldn’t have been able to do this. But after absorbing some of the Underworld’s dark mist, Zhao Hai’s own dark mist was able to evolve, gaining the ability to block divine sense.

This was the first time that the Divines had experience this. They had encountered things that can block divine sense, like domain weapons and magic formations. But things like this dark mist was unique.

This was the base that Gold Ben and the others had constructed, so they were quite familiar to its structure. Because of this, they felt that they would be able to leave this base to deal with Zhao Hai. Even if it was attacked by ultimate weapons, it could still hold some ground and buy time for the elders to come back.

However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to attack their base in a barbaric manner. In the end, the base was actually destroyed by him.

It didn’t take too long before Gold Ben and the others came upon their base. In fact, it couldn’t be called a base anymore. This was because the entire thing was in ruins, and was just a pile of debris.

Gold Ben and the others stared blankly at the base. To be honest, upon entering the Dark Mist, they already expected their base to be destroyed. However, they didn’t think that it would be ruined to this state. It was thoroughly scrapped.

At this time, Gold Ben suddenly saw a piece of rock moving. Gold Ben rushed to the area to investigate. Under Gold Ben’s eyes, the huge rock turned to the side, revealing a person underneath.

After seeing this person, Gold Ben couldn’t help but stare. He knew this person from what he wore. Just from the armor, Gold Ben knew that it was a Divine Race soldier. However, the armor wasn’t the one that attracted his attention, it was the weapons that this person had.

The Divine Race soldier had two weapons stuck in its body. One was a two-handed sword and the other was a spear. The spear was inserted on the person’s shoulder while the sword was stabbed into his lower abdomen. It can be said that the two points were extremely fatal.

While Gold Ben was looking at the person, the person also turned to look at Gold Ben’s eyes. The eyes had no expression, it was the same as the eyes of a dead fish. Then that person moved and slowly took out the weapons stuck to his body. The withdrawal of both the sword and the spear would give a person a very terrible feeling. The sound of friction between the person’s bones and the weapons was actually terrifying to hear.

After taking the two weapons out, the person looked at Gold Ben once again before he turned around and went deeper into the dark mist. In the entire process, no person uttered even a single word. Gold Ben and the others were too shocked to say anything.

Once the person flew away, Gold Ben let out a long breath. Those who were with him had difficult expressions. They knew that the person was no longer living, he had been turned into an undead.

Elder Star coldly snorted and said, “Good, Zhao Hai, good. You actually dared to turn my race’s soldiers into undead. Unforgivable!”

On the other hand, Gold Ben smiled bitterly. He was the first among them to fight with Zhao Hai. Moreover, the Taurus Divines and Zhao Hai hadn’t fought for a day or two, so Gold Ben knew something about Zhao Hai’s capabilities. Zhao Hai’s strongest subordinates were the undead. And most of the undead were from the Divine Race. Because of this, Gold Ben wasn’t too bothered about the Divines being turned into undead.

At this time, jie Yu’s voice was heard, “The undead went in that direction. Perhaps Zhao Hai is there, let’s go take a look.”

Elder Star looked at the other elders before he shook his head, “This place has been covered by the dark mist. It’s not good for us if we fight here. We should head out first and then have light magic scatter the dark mist bit by bit. When the time comes, it wouldn’t be too late to deal with Zhao Hai. Our divine sense is limited here and Zhao Hai is a divergent ability user. We have very small chances of success at this time.”

Upon hearing this, the group nodded, then they proceeded to leave the dark mist. Once they were outside, they immediately casted light magic towards the dark mist.

But to their surprise, once the light magic reached the dark mist, the mist actually scattered. Before long, the mountain was revealed. The only thing was left there was the remains of a destroyed mountain. There was no Hell King’s ship, there weren’t even any dead bodies!

Chapter 892: Elder Star’s Resolve

The expression on Elder Star and the others’ faces were quite ugly. When they departed, the base was still in good condition. It has only been a few hours since they left.

They thought that with the soldiers they left here, the base should be able to hold on for several hours. But this time, the base had been destroyed, everyone had disappeared. From the undead that the saw, they already had a faint idea about what happened to the soldiers.

Their faces were ugly not just because of the base being destroyed. They were also quite bothered about Zhao Hai’s strength.

The base had 100 million troops defending it. If they were turned into undead by Zhao Hai. they Zhao Hai’s undead would have a huge boost in numbers.

At this time, Elder Star turned to look at the camp of the vassal soldiers. Although the camp was also destroyed, the state of its destruction wasn’t that serious. In fact, the destruction was purely because of the debris from the mountain. There were no traces of battle.

Elder Star and the others noticed Jie Yu’s gaze and also turned their heads towards the vassal races’ camp. When they saw the camp, their faces couldn’t help but turn uglier.

With clenched jaws, Gold Ben said, “Those fellows really knows how to fight us. They actually endured all this time. The base’s destruction surely had something to do with them.”

However, Jie Yu shook his head and said, “Not necessarily. The destruction might not have anything to do with them. Don’t forget, we’ve pinched them from getting grain all this time. They would need to hunt and forage for food, they’re famished. Moreover, we didn’t let them assist in making our base. They are simply clueless about its structure. In this case, although it is possible that they had sided with Zhao Hai, I think Zhao Hai didn’t need their help. It’s more probable that Zhao Hai took them when he vanished.”

Elder Star nodded, “Correct. With Zhao Hai’s strength, he wouldn’t need those guys’ help. He alone is able to destroy the base.’

Gold Ben didn’t say anything. He understood that what Jie Yu and Elder Star said was correct. His earlier words were merely caused by his hatred. Gold Ben calmed himself down before turning his head to Elder Star and Jie Yu, “Who do we do now?”

Elder Star’s eyes flashed a cold light, “We can’t just eat this loss without retaliating. We aren’t familiar with Zhao Hai, so we can’t catch him easily. On the other hand, the vassal races have relationships with the foreign races. We’ll target the foreign races. If we do that, Zhao Hai would surely come and look for us. This is much better than looking for him ourselves.”

Gold Ben and Jie Yu’s face lit up. Although they were also Supreme Elders, their position wasn’t as high as Elder Star. And even if Elder Star’s weapon wasn’t the strongest one, his wisdom was much better then the others. Moreover, Star’s ultimate weapon can coordinate other ultimate weapons. This meant that Elder Star was the center point of all the Supreme Elders.

Gold Ben’s eyes coldly sparkled as he said, “Right, those foreign race bastards had been a headache for a long time. It’s about time we clean them up. We can use this opportunity to deal with them in one go.”

Jie Yu and the others didn’t say anything, but their eyes also had a cold glint. In fact, they had long wanted to deal with the foreign races. However, dealing with the foreign races was not easy. The foreign races were also quite strong. They also had three ultimate weapons. Another point was the fact that the Divines weren’t motivated to deal with the foreign races. At any crucial point, someone would always withdraw. Because of this, the foreign races were able to survive up to this point.

However, the situation this time was different. In the past, when they were in the attacking side, they could hit whenever they wanted to hit and withdraw whenever they can. The foreign races simply don’t have any way to fight back.

Now, the one being threatened were the Divines. If the Divines don’t fight, then they would risk extermination. With them being in dire straits, the entire Divine Race should unite.

The reason why the Divines couldn’t unite in the past was because they had different interests. In the previous wars against the foreign races, one Divine race group would fight while the other would be holding back. This would result in one party losing less than the other. In the end, the Divines wouldn’t be able to go on to finish the fight, their alliance would break.

This time, the situation had reached to the point of being a threat to the entire Divine Race. If they don’t make an effort, then they would be collectively defeated by Zhao Hai. Because of this, nobody refuted Gold Ben’s proposal. Although Gold Ben was practically alone right now, with the Taurus Continent being cleaned out, Gold Ben was still an ultimate weapon user. He still had the capital to talk.

Elder Star’s voice was heard, “We can’t be in the Taurus Continent at this time. Let’s return to our continents and immediately prepare our soldiers. Make it clear that this involves the life and death of the entire Divine Race. Make them know that this isn’t the time to scheme against one another.”

The group nodded. Although they were Supreme Elders of their continents, the leaders of the continents were still the respective patriarchs. Supreme Elders couldn’t just command the Patriarchs for no reason. Otherwise, the Patriarchs would rebel. Because of this, the Supreme Elders still needed to converse with the Patriarchs.

Naturally, the Supreme Elders still had a high status among the Divine Race. Moreover, most of them came from the Royal Clans. Because of this, their clans typically agree to their decision. But still, it was better to discuss this matter with their respective clans.

Elder Star looked at Gold Ben and said, “Elder Gold Ben, you return with me to the Central Continent. You’ve been wounded for some time. You need to be cured. We have to be in our peak condition so that we can defeat Zhao Hai.”

Gold Ben nodded. After that, Elder Star looked at that Taurus Continent and said, “In the future, we will reclaim this place. Not only would we reclaim it, we will get our hands on the Ark Continent as well.”

After saying this, he turned around and left. The other Elders also followed behind as they went out of the Taurus Continent. Actually, their action wasn’t expected by Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was looking at them using the monitor. While they were there, they didn’t use any concealing formations. Because of this, Zhao hai can hear their conversation clearly. Zhao Hai didn’t expect Elder Star to be decisive and leave immediately.

Zhao Hai just calmly looked at Elder Star and the others leaving, he didn’t plan to stop them. Larua, who stood by Zhao Hai’s side, said, “Brother Hai, it seems like that Elder Star wouldn’t be easy to deal with. He’s different from the other Divines. He’s arrogant but not to the point of losing his calm. Now they’re targeting the foreign races, should we tell Bingya and the others?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, this guy is good. Especially the ultimate weapon in his hand. If we can get his ultimate weapon, then we can combine the weapons we get. When that time comes, our power level would surely improve. We can even try to see if we can combine it with the Hell King’s ship. If it can, then that would be great.”

Laura smiled and said, “Certainly. Brother Hai, since we’re not short on money, how about we try to improve those domain weapons and then give them to Blockhead ,Rockhead, and the others. They have no talent for magic formations. So they might as well go out and follow you. This way, you won’t need to deal with things by yourself. Wouldn’t that be better?”

Zhao Hai thought about it for a moment and then said, “That’s reasonable. Let’s try that. However, now’s not the time. After we produce the first batch of combat suits, then that would be the right time to provide them with weapons.”

Laura smiled and said, “Alright. Then Brother Hai, let’s go tell Bingya and the others about the Divine Race’s plan. We can’t have them lose too much. Otherwise, the foreign races might come to hate us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, how are the O’neal family doing?”

Cai’er smiled faintly and said, “Young Master, feel relieved. The O’neal family didn’t do any significant actions. They were focused on sending their battleship to support the Aksu Empire. However, their squads on the south were bound to find out about the Demon Realm’s spatial rift. What do we do then?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then just let them go in. Don’t forget, the Demon Realm isn’t like any other plane. The air of the Demon Realm is poisonous. I want to see if their magic armors could block the plane’s poison. If they could, then that would be great.”

Zhao Hai already regarded the magic armors to be his. Because of this, the more capabilities the magic armor had, the happier he became.

Chapter 893: Way Out For the Vassal Soldiers

Bingya, along with the vassal soldiers, went deeper into the Taurus Continent and settled inside a big city. Bingya believed that Zhao Hai would be able to find them, so he wasn’t too worried.

Bingya not being anxious didn’t mean that the same was true for the vassal soldiers. In the beginning, the vassal soldiers weren’t too anxious, but after seeing Zhao Hai’s strength, they couldn’t calm down. They wanted to meet Zhao Hai and talk to him.

The vassal soldiers wanted to see Zhao Hai because their clans were currently fighting right now. These soldiers were the elites of their clans, without them, their clans would suffer great losses.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s capabilities, they wanted to ask Zhao Hai to help them return to their clans so that they can help in fighting against the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about the thoughts of these vassal soldiers. His connection with the vassal soldiers had always been through Bingya and the others. Because of this, Zhao Hai haven’t paid much attention to them.

This was also Zhao Hai’s intention to decentralize his interactions. If he personally went to the vassal races, then Bingya and the others might think that he wanted to pull the vassal races in which may cause some misunderstandings. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t contact the vassal races and just handed them over to Bingya and the others.

While everyone was still flustered, Zhao Hai’s group suddenly appeared in the city. Bingya and the others immediately left whatever they were doing and flew towards the Hell King’s ship to see Zhao Hai.

Actually, there weren’t a lot of things that Bingya and the others needed to do. After all, they weren’t the commanders of these vassal soldiers.

As Bingya headed to the ship, he saw Zhao Hai standing on the bow looking down at the city below. Bingya’s heart couldn’t help but jump, he came to see Zhao Hai twice without bringing anyone from the vassal races. Was Zhao Hai dissatisfied with this? Upon thinking about it, Bingya couldn’t help but feel uneasy.

When Bingya and the others arrived by Zhao Hai’s side, they bowed and said, “I’ve seen Mister Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at the three and smiled, “You did a great job. It seems like these people didn’t have a hard time. I came to see you today to tell you something. I reckon the Divines would shift their target to the foreign races, you need to warn your families.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Bingya’s expression couldn’t help but change as he asked, “Mister, are you saying the truth?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Of course it’s true. The Supreme Elders discovered that they couldn’t deal with me. Therefore, they decided to shift their sights to the foreign races. They have guessed that we have allied with each other, so they decided to go and deal with you instead. In turn, this would force me to have a decisive battle against them. You need to remind your families so that they could be careful around those fellows.”

Bingya’s face looked serious as he nodded heavily and said, “Mister, you can rest assured, we will immediately inform the family. Mister, how do you want to deal with the vassal soldiers? We can’t just have them stay here all the time.”

Zhao Hai frowned before he said, “Their strength isn’t something to be underestimated. And now that their people is fighting against the Divine Race, I reckon that they must want to return home. However, it would be unrealistic for me to send them back at this time. How about you send them to your continents. In any case, the war would come to the foreign races. After all, fighting with the foreign races can be regarded as supporting their own clans. I can’t take them with me since I plan to attack the Divine Race’s continents. While you hold them off, I want to see how they can deal with me.”

When Bingya heard Zhao Hai, his heart finally calmed down. He was afraid that Zhao Hai might have misunderstood, and that Bingya was deliberately making Zhao Hai unable to contact the vassal races. Because of this, Bingya was probling Zhao Hai’s reaction. If Zhao Hai showed any form of discontent, Bingya would immediately have the vassal soldiers meet him. But now, Zhao Hai seemed to not have any indications of wanting to meet with them. This outcome made Bingya feel relieved.

After Bingya calmed down, he immediately thought about Zhao Hai’s proposition. Bingya was a smart person, so he also knew about the ongoing emotion going through the minds of the vassal soldiers. He knew that the vassal soldiers really wanted to go home. But to be honest, it was impossible to send them back right now. Sending them back would just cause them to die, so he never mentioned it during their meetings.

And now that Zhao Hai pointed it out, it seems like there’s an alternative way. But can they send the vassal soldiers over to the continents controlled by the foreign races in order to help out? It’s true that the vassals and the foreign races were together in this war, but to trust them to fight would be difficult.

Yehta and Ryder haven’t spoken. Before the three would meet with Zhao Hai, they would always unify their ideas so that there won’t be too much talking. This way, Zhao Hai won’t be too annoyed.

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya who didn’t reply for some time. He also knew that his proposition was quite difficult for them. The vassal races won’t completely listen to Bingya, especially during this time. With how things were going through, the vassal races would also need to consider their future. In the end, this matter would need deep discussion with Bingya and the others.

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya and said, “In the past two attacks, I’ve managed to gain a lot of grain and military supplies from the Divines. If the vassal soldiers decide to help with the war, I can give all of those supplies over to you. But if they want to go back to their clans, then I won’t stop them and even give them food. However, I can only give them enough just to survive, I can’t just give everything to them.”

When Bingya heard this, his eyes shone. Zhao Hai said this to remind him that they can use the provisions to gain some ground in the discussion.

Bingya bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I will handle this matter properly. Please rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll leave these to you. Right, don’t forget to remind your people about the future attack from the Divines. Moreover, tell them that the Divines would send several Supreme Elders.”

Bingya nodded before disembarking from the ship along with Ryder and Yehta. When they left, Zhao Hai turned around and entered the ship before opening the monitor. The monitor was currently showing the state of the O’Neal family’s scouts. There were three war tanks and 50 magic armors outside the Demon Realm’s spatial rift.

One must know that the magic armors were manned by powerful people. Therefore, their range for scouting was very broad. And with how their magic armors were strong, it’s not strange that they would find out about the Demon Realm’s spatial rift.

In fact, their discovery of the spatial rift was several days earlier than what Zhao Hai expected. Zhao Hai thought that they would stay in the Accra Mountains for some time. After all, a long defensive line like the mountains was something rarely seen. Moreover, there were traces of battle on the mountain, so Zhao Hai expected the O’Neal family to stay there for a few days.

However, Zhao Hai miscalculated the ability of the magic armors. Although they had scouted the Accra Mountains, they didn’t stay there for as long as Zhao Hai thought. Additionally, since there were no magic beasts on the mountain, the O’Neal family scouts didn’t stay for long and just went straight to the Buddha Empire.

The same was to say for the Buddha Empire. There were a lot of cities with traces of fighting so they did delay the scouts. However, the scouts were also quick to discover the spatial rift right by the empire.

The Demon Realm’s spatial rift was very big, so it can be spotted very easily. Therefore, the O’Neal family were able to see the spatial rift.

Fortunately, there weren’t a lot of scouts sent to the south by the O’Neal family. Otherwise, the spatial rift to the Divine Realm would also be discovered. At this point, Zhao Hai was hesitant on what to do if the O’neal family were to find the spatial rift. Should he resist, or should he just allow the O’Neal family in?

If he resists, then he would be at war with the O’Neal family. This would allow him to acquire magic armors earlier. At the same time, they could also turn the Taurus Continent into their base, allowing Zhao Hai more flexibility in dealing with the Divines in the future. This was good for Zhao Hai.

On the other hand, if Zhao Hai allowed the O’neal family to enter the Divine Realm, then Zhao Hai might be able to use the O’Neal family to scare the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and Thunder Clan. At this time, the three clans were heavily injured. If they came to know about a new enemy, then they might consider getting an escape plan. When the time comes, Zhao Hai can push forward and convince them to enter the Space.

However, the second method might result in a backlash. The Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus had always been yearning to be free from the Divine Race. They had prepared for many years, and even ingratiate themselves to the Divines when the time for war has yet to come. Not many races had this much courage.

If Zhao Hai didn’t resist the O’neal family and just allowed them to come into the Taurus Continent, it was highly probable that the three clans would be in conflict with the new invaders. However, the three clans knew about Zhao Hai’s strength. When the time comes, they might suspect that Zhao Hai deliberately allowed the O’Neal family into the Taurus Continent. If Zhao Hai introduces his Space at this time, then the clans would immediately think that Zhao Hai was plotting against them, maybe even before he entered the Taurus Continent. In that case, it would be impossible for the three clans to enter Zhao Hai’s Space.

With such considerations, Zhao Hai was left to decide what to do. He didn’t know whether to resist or just allow the O’Neal family in.

Zhao Hai never treats other people as fools. He would rather think that they were smarter than him. That way, he would make fewer mistakes.

Moreover, Zhao Hai completely understood the three clans. He knew that the three clans weren’t stupid. They were only worried about themselves, that’s why they decided to cooperate with Zhao Hai. And even before the battle started, they managed to hide their intent for a long time. This feat would be impossible if the three clans were fools.

Also, Zhao Hai didn’t want to fool them. After all, Zhao Hai wasn’t cruel nor did he want deaths. Although he wanted to bring the three clans into the Space, he also didn’t want the three clans to lose too much people. The losses to the three clans were heavy and Zhao Hai didn’t want to further damage them. He was currently thinking about the solidarity of their alliance.

Zhao Hai knew about the saying, ‘Help a man once to gain grace, but help a man too much and one would gain hatred.’ Zhao Hai had helped the three clans before, so the three clans should be grateful to Zhao Hai. But if Zhao Hai were to deal with everything by himself and save the Taurus Continent on his own, then the help he would give to the three clans would be too much. In this case, the three clans might dread him. This wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to see.

Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to look for means to satisfy everyone. He needed the means to make the three clans enter the Space without suspecting him. And this goal wasn’t easy to accomplish.

However, this matter would need to be postponed for the future. Now, Zhao Hai needed to pay attention to the scout troops by the Demon Realm’s spatial rift. He wanted to see what the scout troop decides to do.

To be honest, the performance made by Theo and the other people from the O’Neal family surprised Zhao Hai. Their actions were remarkable, very well executed. Zhao Hai wanted to see if this squad was the same.

If this squad were as competent as Theo and the others, then Zhao Hai would gain an estimate on the strength of the O’Neal family.

People who haven’t been to the battlefield wouldn’t be great at being scouts. Even if they were strictly trained, they still needed real experience to be effective. There was a huge difference in atmosphere between training and true battle.

If the two scouting troops of the O’Neal family were doing well, then it meant that the O’neal family has experienced many battles and had a lot of well-trained veterans. Such a group is very dangerous. Zhao Hai might need to increase his estimated strength of the O’Neal family by fifty percent.

In fact, the difference between recruits and veterans was at least thirty percent. But considering that the O’Neal family had magic armors, Zhao Hai made the conclusion that the O’Neal Family wasn’t a presence that he could just ignore. They were people Zhao Hai needed to take carefully into account.

Chapter 894: What I Would Settle On In The Future

Penny was looking at a spatial rift in the distance. This was an incomparably huge spatial rift, much larger than the one that connects the Atlanta Plane to the Ark Continent.

This spatial rift was discovered not long ago by a magic armor pilot who was under his command. He didn’t expect to find anything here, but who would’ve thought that a huge spatial rift like this would exist.

Upon seeing this spatial rift Penny was shocked. This was the first time that he had seen a rift as big as this one. But then, his heart started to move, this was because nobody can be seen around this rift.

However, Penny was also a very careful person. After looking at the spatial rift, he turned to the person standing beside him and said, “Don, find five people and go inside the rift to see what’s inside.”

Don immediately nodded before turning around to leave. Before long, five magic armors got into the air and flew into the rift.

Penny looked at the magic armors while also preparing his other men. The others were inside their magic armors, ready to move at moment’s notice.

After a few moments, the five magic armors were flying out of the rift at a very fast speed. This caused Penny to be alarmed, he immediately had his magic armor pilots be in alert while the war tanks aimed their cannons towards the rift. However, contrary to what Penny expected, nothing else came out of that spatial rift. After the five magic armors came out, the rift remained peaceful.

Just as Penny was confused, the pilots of the five magic armors jumped down. However, the looks of the pilots were strange. Penny immediately ran towards Don, whose face was a little black. Don looked at Penny and said, “Antidote, quick!”

Penny gawked for a moment before he rushed towards the war tank and took some antidotes that were specially compounded by the O’neal family.

Penny took the cap from the bottle before pouring the antidote down Don’s mouth. After Don swallowed the liquid, he took a long breath before he closed his eyes. A while later, Don opened his eyes and said, “Goodness, that was very dangerous.”

Penny looked at Don and asked, “What happened? How did you get poisoned after entering the rift?’

Don smiled bitterly and said, “It’s too dangerous. On the other side of that spatial rift is a dark red world, even the sun is dark red. However, I didn’t expect the air to be toxic. If it wasn’t for Chik’s toxin detector blaring up, we wouldn’t have retreated.”

Penny looked at the others and then immediately fed them with antidotes. After the others were restored, Penny went towards a man who looked honest and was about 27 to 28 years old, “Chik, is it really poisonous inside that spatial rift?” Chik nodded and said, “it is. I’ve always had a detector with me to keep me safe whenever I enter a forbidden area. This time, I didn’t expect my detector to issue a warning. We didn’t touch anything there, so the only explanation for this is the air being poisonous.” Penny nodded and frowned. It’s impossible to leave this spatial rift unexplored. But it’s also inappropriate for them to scout it at this time.

The reason why Penny thought of this was because the existence of this poisonous air didn’t mean that the place was uninhabited. Instead, this meant that this place would have more formidable magic beasts.

There were also a lot of special areas in the Atlanta Plane, and some of them had poisonous environments. In these environments, if a magic beast managed to survive, then this meant that the magic beast was formidable and was extremely difficult to deal with.

And now there’s this spatial rift with a poisonous environment on the other side. This wasn’t good news for Penny. If they couldn’t scout this place out, then they would eternally be worrying about a hidden danger.

However, what made Penny worry the most was the existence of an extremely huge city not far from the spatial rift. This city can accommodate several tens of millions of people. But now, this city became uninhabited. Upon further observation, one could see that this city wasn’t fully fortified. It looks broken, but not because of disrepair, it was because its construction was abandoned.

A city of this scale would surely be a major project in the continent. But now, it was actually abandoned. This made no sense. In this case, there’s only one explanation. They encountered something that forced them to abandon this city!

Upon thinking about this, Penny couldn’t help but frown. The city had a different architectural style compared to those in the Ark continent. Moreover, its establishment near the spatial rift was too conspicuous to be a coincidence. One could see upon careful observation that the city was made for the spatial rift. In other words, this city was made by the people who lived on the other side of the rift.

At this time, a voice came from Penny’s side, “Penny, what do we do now?”

Penny looked at the spatial rift and said, “No matter what, we need to look into the other side of that spatial rift. Prepare shields and bring antidotes before going in.” Don nodded before he turned around and left. Don knew that Penny’s decision was right. However, he was still worried whether the shields could protect them against the poison. At the same time, this also meant that the consumption of energy would be greatly increased. A 10 thousand meter distance without shields would take the same energy as a 70 thousand meter distance with shields.

The energy consumption of the shields was huge. However, Don still supported this decision. If they cannot clarify what’s inside the spatial rift, then they won’t be able to feel at ease.

Zhao Hai was inside his room while looking at their movement. When he heard that the scouts would use their shields as they entered the rift, he couldn’t help but nod. Then he turned to Laura and said, “These guys are very competent. The O’Neal family truly isn’t an ordinary group. They have a lot of experienced veterans, they wouldn’t be easy to deal with.” Laura nodded, then she said, “Brother Hai, if the O’Neal family comes to the Divine Realm, what do we do? Allow them in? Or do we repel them?” Zhao Hai frowned and answered, “To be honest, I cannot make a decision right now. We need to weigh the advantages and disadvantages.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what do you mean?” Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “What I mean is, I want the Thunder Clan and the others to migrate to the Space. However, that won’t be easy. Their temperament aren’t that great. If they discover that I had plans for them, then it’s possible that they might die rather than entering the Space.”

When she heard this, Laura nodded. Then Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and the others and said, “Do any of you have any ideas?” Lizzy knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, if it’s possible, we can use the same method we used when the Divines came to the Ark Continent. We’ll have the Thunder Clan and the others participate in the defense of the spatial rift to have them witness the strength of the O’Neal family. When the time comes, it shouldn’t be difficult for you to convince them to migrate to the Space.”

Zhao Hai nodded. This wasn’t the greatest idea, but it was still very good. Megan also added, “Big Brother Hai, we can also tell the Thunder Clan and the others about the ongoing situation. Maybe it may prove useful.” Zhao Hai nodded, “It seems like we can only do it like that. If it doesn’t work, then we might have to give up on them. No matter what, we cannot force them like what we did to the Divines.”

Laura and the others nodded. At this time, the magic armors entered the rift. The magic armors had their shields on and the pilots also had antidotes with them.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and smiled, “Those magic armors are really good. Even their shields are noteworthy. It seems like we’ll be able to save a lot of energy in the future.”

Laura smiled faintly and before her expression mellowed down, “Brother Hai, those magic armors aren’t really that useful for us. Think about it, when the people in the Space grow up, the lowest rank they would have would be 9th rank. Eventually a great number of them would reach God-rank. When they reach God-rank we can just give them combat suits. I think that the magic armors would have little use at that point.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “At present, the magic armors don’t have great uses for us. However, we must consider the future. The present magic armors might only have God-rank strength. But what if we develop better magic armors? We might be able to amplify a God-rank’s strength by ten or even a hundred times. At that time, wouldn’t they be very useful? Moreover, even if the magic armors can’t help with our fighting strength, wouldn’t they improve our daily lives?”

When Zhao Hai said this, Laura couldn’t help but think about the magic armors that helped in making the huge ships. Laura nodded, the magic armors were perfect in large scale construction. If they had those magic armors, they would be able to save a lot of energy and manpower.

Chapter 895: The Two Sides of the Matter

Megan looked at the monitor and said, “Brother Hai, do we withdraw the undead and iron armor beasts that are mining in the Demon Realm? If we don’t, then they would be discovered.”

There were plenty of ores in the Demon Realm, of which Zhao Hai were mining using his undead and iron armor beasts. Some of the ores in the Demon Realm could be found on the surface. So although there were some mines that had been dug out, a lot of undead and iron armor beasts were still working on the surface. In this case, it wouldn’t take too long before Don and the others discover them. This was the reason why Megan asked.

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “It’s fine. I want to see what kind of reaction they would have after seeing the undead and iron armor beasts. If they turn hostile, then I won’t mind having the first batch of magic armor and war tanks be sent to the Space.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others can feel his killing intent. Although eliminating this scout squad at this time would possibly attract the attention of the O’Neal family, there were some advantages in doing so.

Currently, the O’Neal family should be focused on the Underworld. If Zhao Hai completely wipes the scouting squad out, then the O’Neal family might get nervous. However, it was certain that they won’t just give up on the Ark Continent like that. They would first send another team to the south to see the situation. And that would take at least a few days.

In the past, Zhao Hai was afraid of making a move on the O’Neal family since he didn’t want them to flee. Zhao Hai was still planning to gain benefits from the O’Neal family, it wouldn’t be good if he were to drive them away.

But now, it seems like Zhao Hai’s worries were unnecessary. For the O’Neal family, the Ark Continent was just too precious to give up on.

While Zhao Hai was spying on the family, the O’Neal family patriarch had received additional word from Lewis informing him that the innate yin domain was slowly expanding towards the continent. This caught the O’Neal family in quite a dilemma.

When they first discovered the underworld, the O’Neal family only thought that it was a forbidden area in the continent. As long as they didn’t provoke it, then the innate yin domain wouldn’t be a threat. But now it seems like this wasn’t the case. The innate yin domain found in the Ark Continent was different than the ones in the Atlanta Plane.

The O’Neal family’s Patriarch called the generals to his room once more and told them about the information sent by Lewis.

When they heard this information, the generals stared before their expressions changed as they discussed with each other. This was bad news for the O’Neal family.

The expansion of the underworld meant that it would slowly consume the Ark Continent. Although the family had made some arrangements and had sent strong cannons, it would be hard for these cannons to block the expansion of the dark mist.

In the Atlanta Plane, strong cannons would be able to deal with innate yin domains. However, innate yin domains in the Atlanta Plane don’t expand. This time, the innate yin domain was able to increase its size. And with its area already so big, the O’Neal family wasn’t sure if the strong cannons would be able to deal with it.

If the cannons prove to be useless, then that would be trouble for the O’Neal family. The family had already invested too much in the expedition to the Ark Continent. If the dark mist really makes them retreat, then the damage to the family would be very bad.

The O’Neal Patriarch looked at those present and said, “Calm down.” Although his voice wasn’t loud, everyone still became quiet. The Patriarch’s status in the O’Neal family was very high.

The Patriarch looked at his people and said, “Why are all of you flustered? The dark mist wouldn’t cover the continent immediately. It’s already reported that the increase wasn’t that fast. Moreover, the family’s cannons are on the way. When the time comes, it might be possible for us to get rid of the dark mist. What is important right now is our reconnaissance to the south. We know too little about the southern part of the continent. What we need to do is know as much as possible about the Ark Continent. This place has a lot of minerals, and some of them are very much needed by the O’Neal family. It can be said that this continent is a huge treasure chest. We cannot just give up on it. If the situation in the south of the continent it good, then we can develop it for our use. As for the innate yin domain, we can slow it as much as possible while we retreat. Haven’t you thought about it? Since the innate yin domain is expanding, it would reach our spatial rift one day. In this case, we might as well take the initiative and look for ways to deal with it.”

When everyone heard the Patriarch, they kept being silent. They knew that the Patriarch was right. The innate yin domain wouldn’t swallow the Ark Continent immediately. At the same time, the dark mist would still reach the Atlanta Plane’s spatial rift whether they retreat or not. They need to deal with it sooner or later.

It was just a danger that was discovered ahead of time. But putting the issue of the Dark Mist aside, the O’Neal family would be able to get a lot of ores and things they need from the Ark Continent. This was already a blessing for them.

When they shifted their thinking to this, the group calmed down. In fact, any matter has two sides, the good and the bad. One could look at the bad side, or one could see it from the good side. Either way, one would see different results.

The Patriarch looked at the group’s eyes and said, “Go, send more teams to scout the continent and we’ll relocate to the south. Be sure to clear the situation with the southern part of the continent at the shortest time. Go.”

The group nodded before they turned and left the room. After they left, the Patriarch let out a long sigh. To be honest, he didn’t have any optimistic views of the Ark Continent at this time. The situation of the south was still unclear. And with the north turning up as it was, things were looking bad.

After sighing, the Patriarch gently rubbed his brows. The Ark Continent had become a quagmire that the O’Neal family has been caught in. It would be too late for them to leave at this point. The O’Neal family only has two roads to go; one is to get engulfed by this quagmire, and the other was to rob this quagmire of its gold and happily retreat.

Meanwhile, Don and the others were still clueless about the situation back in the family. They were currently investigating the Demon Realm. But after looking through several cities, they couldn’t help but feel strange.

They didn’t know that this was the Demon Realm, but they can be assured that this wasn’t the Ark Continent either. The spatial crack was already quite a distance away, but the situation here was the same as the Ark Continent. Everyone had moved away, every single settlement was empty.

Moreover, judging by the situation here, the migration was much more recent compared to the Ark Continent. Also, it seems like there were more magic beasts here.

After looking at a few cities, Don and the others withdrew from the Demon Realm. Their magic armors don’t have much energy left. If their armor ran out of energy, then they would risk dying here.

This wasn’t the Ark Continent. In the Ark Continent, even if their magic armors were to run out of energy, they can still send a signal so that people would be able to meet them. However, in the Demon Realm, if their magic armors ran out of energy, both the magic beasts and the poisonous air would immediately claim their lives.

After seeing Don and the others leaving the Demon Realm, Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he looked at Laura and said, “From the current situation, it seems like the O’Neal family would take quite some time exploring the Demon Realm. We can feel relieved as we deal with the Divine Race.”

At this time, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, the O’Neal family just sent out several scout groups towards the south. It seems like they want to know about the situation in the south as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai stared before he shifted his monitor to the Rosen Empire. There were several scouts going southward from the Rosen Empire, moreover, their speed was very quick.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It looks like the O’Neal Family wants to understand the situation of the Ark Continent’s south in order to make a decision. Leave them be. We’ll arrange some people to defend the spatial rift, let’s see how they plan to deal with that.”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, why don’t we just deal with the O’Neal family? Wouldn’t it be better if we clean them up right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, we will take care of them sooner or later. But not now. What we need to do at this time is acquire the Divine Race’s ultimate weapons. If we add the O’Neal family, the energy I’ll use would be too much. If I ascend without acquiring the Ultimate Weapons, then we would lose so much.”

Laura and the others’ expression changed. Lizzy immediately asked, “What happened Brother Hai? Is the feeling of rejection getting stronger?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly nod. Now, every time he uses energy, he would immediately feel the laws driving him away.This made Zhao Hai feel uncomfortable. However, he didn’t have any means to deal with it. The only thing he can do right now was to reduce the instances where he uses his own energy.

Chapter 896: Blood Red Wine, Graceful Demeanor

While Zhao Hai was observing the O’Neal family, Bingya and the others were persuading the vassal races to head to the continents controlled by the foreign races. Before they met the vassal soldiers, Bingya and the others already prepared themselves to meet with difficulties. However, they didn’t expect that the situation would be harder than they expected.

After the vassal soldiers heard Bingya’s proposition, they immediately exploded. Even some of the well-tempered ones began to suspect Bingya and the others of twisting the truth in order to have them face the Divines. They thought Bingya wanted to use them as cannon fodder and fight against the Divine Race.

To be honest, it wouldn’t be strange for the vassal races to have this idea given their current circumstance. These people were the most faithful dogs of the Divine Race. They only dared to revolt because they had the number advantage against the Divines. If they didn’t outnumber the Divine Race, then they would’ve even helped in quelling the vassal race rebellion.

In the past, they didn’t dare to make any noise. But after Bingya’s proposition, most of them didn’t agree. These people immediately jumped up and ignited. Before long, the situation had become uncontrollable.

If Zhao Hai hadn’t given them food, then these people might have made a move against Zhao Hai.

Bingya and the others didn’t expect this situation at all. They were still young members of their respective races. Therefore, they didn’t have too much experience handling these types of things. Because of this, for a moment, they didn’t know what to do.

Bingya was currently sitting inside the room along with Ryder and Yehta. The three people looked distressed. Outside, the vassal soldiers had become noisy, Bingya and the others had completely lost control of them. Moreover, under the provocation of the more powerful vassal members, the vassal soldiers even wanted Zhao Hai to give them all the food to bring home.

If it wasn’t for Zhao Hai’s leaving a strong impression when dealing with the Divines, the vassal soldiers would have long since went to Zhao Hai and demand for food.

However, Bingya also knew that this passive situation wouldn’t last for long. This was because word had spread among the vassal soldiers that Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare do anything to them. Zhao Hai wouldn’t make move because there were nearly 100 million of them. And nobody was crazy enough to kill 100 million people in one breath.

This word started out small, after all, Zhao Hai’s strength has been seen by everyone. However, someone said that Zhao Hai only broke the base and didn’t actually kill that many Divines. Most of the Divine Race soldiers who were able to survive has been sent away by Zhao Hai using his Space Divergent ability, they weren’t killed. This gave the vassal soldiers confidence. This news became louder and louder in the vassal race camp.

Naturally, Bingya and the others knew that there were such voices among the vassal soldiers. Bingya was fully opposed to the vassal soldiers’ movement to ask for food from Zhao Hai because he knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t a good person. Slaughtering 100 million people wasn’t a problem for Zhao Hai. At this time, Zhao Hai’s undead had reached more than 200 million. Expecting a person like that to care about 100 million people would be a naive thought.

But at this point, no vassal soldier would listen to Bingya. Because of this, Bingya couldn’t do anything, he could only hide in his room and worry.

Ryder looked at Bingya and said, “Bingya, there’s no need to be polite to those guys. I think we should report this to mister, ask him to teach them a lesson.”

Bingya looked at Ryder’s eyes and smiled bitterly, “I also want to report this to mister, but this is something that Mister entrusted to us. Finally, we already gained this much face with mister. How could we just tell him that we failed?”

When Ryder heard Bingya, he became silent. He also felt that he wouldn’t have face to approach Zhao Hai.

At this time, it was Yehta’s turn to talk, “I still think that we should report this to Mister. If you let those people meet with mister themselves and Mister didn’t know about it, then Mister might be disappointed. We’ve already failed, we cannot fail a second time.”

When Bingya heard what Yehta said, he paused for a moment before his eyes shone, “Right, that’s true. We should report this to mister. Otherwise, we would fail mister once more. Let’s go see mister right now.”

However, Yehta blocked Bingya and said, “You can’t go out right now. If you go out, then those people would follow you. When they get there, they would immediately make demands to Mister Zhao Hai. I think you should use the messenger fish. In any case, we’ve already lost face, we can’t lose any more.”

Bingya looked at Yehta. He knew that Elves were the ones who cared about face the most. For Yehta to say that today meant that she was already confident in Zhao Hai.

Bingya didn’t reply and just nodded. Then he took his messenger fish and said, “Mister, Mister, are you in?”

Zhao Hai was currently thinking about how to deal with the multitude of scouts that the O’Neal family had sent out. Sending these many scouts meant that they would discover the spatial rift to the Divine Realm much sooner. When the time comes, a fight would break out.

Although Zhao Hai said that it would be fine as long as he stationed some soldiers in the rift, this matter wasn’t actually that simple. The core problem was the three clans.

Zhao Hai wanted to bring the three races over into the Space. Since he had fought with them, Zhao Hai was sure that if he left, the three clans wouldn’t be able to resist the Atlanta Plane and the Underworld. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted the three clans to move into the Space and live the same life as the Demons, the people from the Ark Continent, and the Goblins.

But naturally, this wouldn’t be easy. The most difficult thing to guess was a person’s heart. Zhao Hai was afraid that his good intentions would be misunderstood by the Thunder CLan and the others. And that wouldn’t be good.

At this time, Zhao Hai felt his messenger fish move. When he took it out, he heard Bingya’s message. He held the messenger fish bottle and said, “Bingya, I’m here. How’s the preparation doing?”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Bingya couldn’t help but feel shame, then he said, “Mister, I’ve failed you.”

Zhao Hai stared, he was confused so he asked, “What happened?”

Bingya told Zhao Hai everything. He told him that he had completely lost control of the vassal soldiers.

After listening to Bingya, Zhao Hai’s face turned a bit ugly. He didn’t think that the vassal soldiers would be so ignorant. They even wanted to make demands to him.

Since Lizzy and the others were also with Zhao Hai, their expressions couldn’t help but change as well. Before, they thought that Zhao Hai was excessively worrying about how to deal with the three clans. They felt that there was no need to consider it too much.

But now however, with how the vassal races reacted, they could finally understand Zhao Hai’s worries. Zhao Hai’s thoughts weren’t baseless, it’s actually possible for something to go wrong.

Take these vassal soldiers for example. Their people were fighting against the Divines while they were selling their lives to the same people. The saddest thing was the Divines wanted to starve them to death and wait for them to lose during the fight before dealing with them.

Bingya bringing food for them at this time was the biggest kindness that they could receive. And Bingya’s proposal to send them to the Foreign Races’ continents was something that was good for them. And yet they actually reacted this way. This wasn’t something that Lizzy and the others expected.

When Bingya was finished talking, Zhao Hai said, “Alright, I understand. You don’t have to worry about this matter. Nothing has happened yet, but you still need to protect yourselves.” After putting the messenger fish away, Lizzy’s face turned ugly as she said, “Brother Hai, these people are too ignorant. Should we teach them a lesson?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he coldly said, “Don’t worry, we’ll teach them a lesson. But we also need an excuse to do so. We need to rile them up a bit more.”

Laura and the others knew Zhao Hai very well, and they could hear a bit of killing intent from Zhao Hai’s words. It was clear that Zhao Hai was really angry. It seems like the vassal soldiers would soon be unlucky.

However, they didn’t think about stopping Zhao Hai. The reaction of the vassal races also angered them. If it wasn’t for Zhao Hai showing his anger, Lizzy would have already commanded the undead army to deal with the vassal soldiers.

Bingya put away his messenger fish before turning to Yehta and Ryder before he said, “What do you think about Mister’s response? How do you think he will deal with the vassal soldiers?”

Ryder sneered and said, “Mister is surely not a kindhearted person. Those people will suffer bad luck. But this is also good, they don’t have any sense of thankfulness. If it weren’t for us, then would have already been starved to death. Now that they are full, they actually forgot the kindness that was given to them.”

Yehta smiled faintly and said, “Right, they need to know how terrifying mister can become. With this, they shouldn’t be able to dare go against mister in the future. And leading them should become easier.”

Just as the three people were talking, the vassal soldiers were ready to go to Zhao Hai and make demands. The Hell King’s ship wasn’t too far from the city they were in. They can go to Zhao Hai with Bingya leading the way.

At this point, the vassal soldiers were so agitated that they had lost reason. They already forgot that they used to starve, and that Zhao Hai and Bingya had brought grain to save them. In their minds, Zhao Hai was thinking of using them as cannon fodder. They need to make Zhao Hai know about how terrifying they could be.

Before long, under the agitation of several people, about 100 hundred million soldiers flew towards Zhao Hai’s ship, encircling it.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside his room, watching the movements of the vassal soldiers. When he saw that the ship was surrounded, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Those people are really impatient, they’re quick to be riled up. They can’t think for even a moment. Meg, go set up some tables outside. I want to see how those people deal with us. Cai’er, remember to look at the surroundings, make sure that nobody is able to escape.”

Meg and Cai’er nodded and then went on to prepare. Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and the others and said, “Let’s head out. I want to see what methods those guys will use to force me to give them food.”

Laura and the others stood up and went out. Meg already set the table outside. There were a few small snacks on the table as  well as a few glasses of red wine. It was a blaringly red wine, the same color as blood.

Zhao Hai sat on the seat of honor while Laura and the others sat on the side. The group just sat there under the gazes of the vassal soldiers surrounding them.

What does it feel to be surrounded by 100 million people? Whether it be in the Ark Continent or back on Earth, maybe nobody can give an answer. Even if you ask Zhao Hai, he might say that he doesn’t know.

Zhao Hai looked at the vassal soldiers calmly, there was no trace of fear on his face. He was calmer than an person looking at 100 million ants. If someone saw 100 million ants, then one might be scared to death. It’s because those ants could swallow his life.

But in the eyes of Zhao Hai, these people were different from 100 million ants. Although ants were very weak, a 100 million of them would have terrifying power. As for these people, although they have gathered together, they will panic as soon as they encounter any problems. They weren’t worth mentioning at all.

The vassal soldiers were getting closer and closer to Zhao Hai. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was just calmly looking at them with his wine glass in his hand. Zhao Hai gently swirled his glass, forming a vortex with his blood red wine. At the same time, Laura and the others were just calmly sitting there, sipping the wine in their glass.

Laura and the others didn’t use to have this demeanor. But ever since they saw Zhao Hai doing it, they saw that it looked really good and graceful. Because of this, they learned Zhao Hai’s aura and just sat there calmly. It was as if they had nothing to do with what’s happening around them.

The vassal soldiers have already encircled the Hell King’s ship. The ship didn’t become bigger. Surrounded by 100 million people, the ship looked like a small boat swallowed by the vortex.

However, no vassal soldier dared to embark on the ship. They just encircled the ship and looked at the bow, where Zhao Hai was drinking his red wine. While looking at Zhao Hai’s graceful movement, they couldn’t help but swallow their saliva. They found out that they were somewhat anxious.

Chapter 897: You Think Too Highly Of Yourselves!

Zhao Hai currently wasn’t looking at these people, he just stared at his wine glass as he calmly said, “What’s wrong? Why are all of you here?”

The vassal races found that Zhao Hai’s voice was calm, and his body didn’t exude any imposing aura. However, they didn’t know why, but they still got more and more nervous. This was especially true for those people who were yelling before. More and more people swallowing their saliva were heard, nobody talked for a while.

Zhao Hai looked up and scanned those present. Then he turned his gaze to the glass in his hand as he lifted it up towards the sun. This action made the wine inside the glass more gleaming. But in the eyes of the vassal soldiers, it looked so strange.

In the end, the vassal soldiers couldn’t just stand there as one of them talked, “Mister Zhao Hai, we want to talk to you.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to the person and then glanced at the people surrounding the Hell King’s ship before he said, “You want to talk? You bring so many people to talk to me? You people are quite special.”

The person’s face turned red, then he glanced at those behind him before breathing a sigh of relief. Then he turned to look back at Zhao Hai as he said, “Mister Zhao Hai, first we want to thank you for saving us. If it weren’t for you, we would’ve already been starved.”

Zhao Hai didn’t make too much noise, but he just swirled his glass as he said, “It’s not my idea to save you. Bingya told me that you’re allies and asked me to save you.  Why would I want to rescue you? If it weren’t for Bingya, I wouldn’t have placed you in my eyes.”

The man was stunned by Zhao Hai. Originally, he wanted to express his thanks as a gesture of politeness before making his demands. But now, it seems like Zhao Hai didn’t intend to accept the gesture.

The man’s expression sunk, with a cold voice he said, “Since Mister said so, then we don’t need to feel grateful. Can mister give us back our grain?”

Zhao Hai became more disappointed at these people. He looked at the person and made a puzzled look as he asked, “Grain? What grain? When did this Zhao Hai owe you grain?”

The man calmly replied, “Don’t mess with us. You robbed the Divines of food. Now give us the grain.”

Zhao Hai looked at the man as he suddenly smiled faintly and said, “First, I need to confirm something, are you a Divine? If so, then I can’t give you food because you’re my enemy. Have you heard of someone returning an enemy’s supplies? If you’re not a Divine, then you are either my ally, or a an uninvolved person. If you are my ally, then I will provide you with food. But my allies have to listen to my arrangements. And if you’re not an ally, then you’re someone who has nothing to do with me. Why would I give some food to someone I don’t care about?”

What Zhao Hai said was flawless. These people didn’t have any reason to claim Zhao Hai’s plundered food. If they classify themselves as a part of the Divine Race, then they would be Zhao Hai’s enemies. If they were Zhao Hai’s allies, and even if Zhao Hai didn’t state it clearly, this meant that they would obey Zhao Hai’s orders, and why would allies be aggressive in asking for grain? And lastly, if they weren’t allies, then they were just uninvolved people. Why would people who had nothing to do with Zhao Hai want to get his grain?”

The vassal soldiers stayed quiet for a moment, they were caught speechless. Then after some time, someone loudly said, “Zhao Hai, I ask you. Isn’t the fact that our people are at war with the Divines a lie that you made up? You’re just tricking us into working for you.”

Zhao Hai looked at the person as though he was looking at an idiot. After some time, he said, “You? What are you talking about? What good would I gain if I lie to you? Work for me? I don’t need you. The grain in my hand is even more valuable than your lives. Moreover, the undead army under my command doesn’t need to eat food. Most importantly, they also follow every single word I say.”

Zhao Hai made Cai’er remember the people who just talked. These men chose to use this opportunity to incite the vassal soldiers’ hatred towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s response was quite interesting. The vassal soldiers were able to witness Zhao Hai use his undead to deal with the Divines who managed to escape from the collapsed base. Zhao Hai had quite a lot of undead. What Zhao Hai said this time essentially meant that he didn’t care about the vassal soldiers.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, some of the vassal soldiers calmed down. When they had been instigate before, they haven’t managed to think about this point. Now that Zhao Hai reminded them, they suddenly remembered Zhao Hai’s enormous number of Undead. Moreover, it’s evident that their fighting strength wasn’t weak.

However, there were still some vassal soldiers who held Zhao Hai’s response with contempt. They clamored and seemed to prepare to make a move.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the soldiers. The few people that he paid special attention to were now standing proudly among the crowd as they watched Zhao Hai. It seems like they wanted to see how Zhao Hai plans to deal with this scene.

Zhao Hai’s gaze swept through the crowd like a blade. He took up his wine glass and downed the wine. After placing his glass back on the table, he slowly stood up and said, “You’re saying that I’m deceiving you? That your people aren’t really fighting against the Divine Race? And I just want you to point your swords towards the Divines? Well, let me ask you. Why would I need to do that? I’ve occupied the Taurus Continent. Five Supreme Elders tried to deal with me but they couldn’t. Seven Supreme Elders wanted to look for me but ended up withdrawing. Why do I need to use you? Aren’t you looking too highly upon yourselves?” When the vassal soldiers heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but get stunned. Zhao Hai’s voice was clearly transmitted to their ears. This feat alone made the soldiers feel Zhao Hai’s might. Some soldiers became calm.

But at this time, a voice came about, “Don’t listen to his nonsense. He just wants to work us to death while also pulling our families in. The reason the Supreme Elders retreated was likely because we are here. We need to head back to our clans and explain to the Divines. Otherwise, we would risk going to war!”

These words were akin to putting more oil into the fire. The minds of the soldiers who managed to calm down were once again shaken.

Right, there were a lot of vassal races that wanted to rebel against the Divines. However, if they wanted to rebel, they must do their preparations in absolute secrecy. Otherwise, their plans would be found out by the Divine Race and they would be suppressed. Because of this, most of the vassals didn’t know about any plans that their clans had made. The Divines had implanted a deep fear inside the hearts of the vassal soldiers. Because of this, upon hearing this person, they subconsciously believed him, even if they didn’t know who it was.

As the vassal soldiers were clamoring, someone from the crowd suddenly flung their axe towards Zhao Hai’s Hell King’s ship. Although the axe was immediately flung away by the waves on the ship, the axe acted as a signal for the vassal soldiers to push forward and overrun Zhao Hai. Upon seeing this development, Zhao Hai’s gaze turned frigid. He coldly snorted as the ship increased in size instantaneously. Those who were rushing towards Zhao Hai suddenly found out that they were faced with the dark blue underside of the ship.

They managed to see the ship change its size before. However, that was from far away so they didn’t feel any shock. But now it was different. They were standing underneath the ship while looking at it. In this state, it was natural for them to feel an unnatural pressure coming from the Hell King’s ship. Those who were rushing forwards found themselves frozen. They didn’t know whether they should advance or retreat.

While they were stunned, Zhao Hai didn’t hold back. He immediately directed the ship to go straight forward. The speed of the ship was very fast, the vassals who were controlling the soldiers from the shadows couldn’t even make an order to form a line. With no place to retreat or hide, every soldier that were ran over by the ship were eliminated. The ship was like a roller that passed through a group of ants. No soldier can be seen where the ship had gone through.

In just a blink of an eye, Zhao Hai was already out of the encirclement. After which Zhao Hai turned the ship and realigned its bow to face the vassal soldiers once more.

When the vassal soldiers looked at the Hell King’s ship and then to the gap it made, their hearts couldn’t help but turn cold. They just saw the ship overrun a minimum of a million people. The image was too terrifying.

Now that Zhao Hai had realigned the ship’s bow, the hearts of the vassal soldiers couldn’t help but beat faster. They discovered that they were nothing in front of Zhao Hai. In Zhao Hai’s eyes, they were just dust. They thought that with their numbers, Zhao Hai wouldn’t do anything to them. It seems like they were too naive.

It was at this time that people remembered Zhao Hai being a Dark Mage. A Dark Mage capable of commanding more than two hundred million undead. Could such a person he soft-hearted? What a joke!

At this time, the ship began to go forward once more. This caused the soldiers’ position to collapse. There were some who threw their weapons away in order to escape.

The vassal soldiers weren’t all heroes, there were dogs among them as well!

Chapter 898: Two-man Act

The vassal soldiers soon found out that they had lost the opportunity to escape. On the outskirts of the battlefield, Zhao Hai’s undead had been stationed, encircling them inside. If they wanted to escape, then they would need to go through the undead.

At this point, the vassal soldiers regretted provoking Zhao Hai. They had discovered that they were looking too highly upon themselves. They simply couldn’t contend with Zhao Hai. With Zhao Hai’s strength, he could deal with the Divines without the help of the vassal races.

With such strength, why would Zhao Hai deceive them? And with the vassal soldiers’ strength, could they pass on to be Zhao Hai’s cannon fodder?

If someone asked the vassal soldiers right now if there was something more sad than being a cannon fodder, then they certainly get a concrete answer. It was having no qualification to become even cannon fodder.

The confidence of the vassal races was completely destroyed. They were left not knowing what to do. They used to hope that their numbers would provide them with safety. But as far as the situation had gone, this hope had been destroyed, popped like a bubble and blown away by the wind.

Just when the vassal races felt that the world was collapsing around them, a loud voice was suddenly heard, “Mister Zhao Hai, please stop!” It was Bingya.

After this sound was heard, both the Hell King’s ship and the undead stopped while the vassal soldiers felt relief. After that, everyone glanced towards the direction of that voice. It was Bingya and the others who were pressured by the vassal soldiers a few days ago. At that time, they didn’t look highly upon Bingya’s group. But now, Bingya and the others looked very pleasant.

It was at this moment that the Hell King’s ship had reduced its size. Zhao Hai’s group was seen once more with Zhao Hai still holding his glass of blood red wine. Upon seeing the wine on Zhao Hai’s hand, the vassal soldiers couldn’t help but tremble. At this point, if someone told them that Zhao Hai was actually drinking blood, then they would have believed it.

While holding his wine glass, Zhao Hai looked at Bingya and said, “Bingya, what do you want? You already asked me to give these people food. Are these the people you want to save? You did this on purpose didn’t you? Did you expect me to lower myself just because I’ve allied with the foreign races?”

Bingya immediately bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is a misunderstanding. These people are just worried about their own families. It was only under the instigation of ambitious people that they became like this. I ask Mister to spare them and not to punish them heavily. Please let them go this time.”

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya before turning his gaze towards the vassal soldiers. When the vassal soldiers saw that Zhao Hai’s gaze was on then, their bodies couldn’t help but shrink. Although Zhao Hai looked very calm, he looked terrifying in the eyes of these people.

After sweeping the vassal races with his gaze, Zhao Hai turned back to Bingya and said, “Can you guarantee that they won’t offend me again? If they dared to, then I would have to be impolite.”

The vassal soldiers couldn’t help but feel a chill when they heard this. Zhao Hai had already killed more than 1 million of them. This was Zhao Hai being polite? Then what would his impoliteness be? They couldn’t even dare think about it.

Bingya immediately responded, “Mister can rest assured, this matter will absolutely never be repeated.” Zhao Hai snorted before he swept the vassal soldiers once more and then returning to his cabin. After that, the ship vanished along with the undead that was surrounding the vassal soldiers.

He disappeared. Those present didn’t even know how Zhao Hai left. It was now that they understood that Zhao Hai wasn’t going all out in eliminating them. Otherwise, they would have been wiped out a long time ago. Zhao Hai being polite right now wasn’t a lie.

After Zhao Hai left, Bingya turned to the vassal soldiers. He sighed before saying, “Let’s go back to the camp. Go have a rest, we’ll talk later.” After saying that, Bingya’s group went back and returned to their room. The vassal soldiers were also adamant about returning to the camp. However, what the vassal soldiers failed to see was the smile on Bingya’s face as he turned back.

Actually, Zhao Hai and Bingya’s exchange was something they planned for the vassal soldiers. Zhao Hai told Bingya about this just before he drove the Hell King’s ship towards the soldiers. The plan was to have the two of them perform a play.

It was impossible for Zhao Hai to kill all of the vassal soldiers. He wasn’t a ruthless person, and he just wanted to teach the vassal soldiers a lesson. Therefore, Zhao Hai planned to have Bingya come out just as he was about to make his second attack. Turning Bingya into the hero while Zhao Hai plays the villain, subduing the vassal soldiers in the process.

Zhao Hai was now a sword hanging on top of the vassal soldiers’ heads. As long as Zhao Hai was present, the soldiers would follow Bingya’s orders.

Just as Zhao Hai said before, the vassal soldiers aren’t useless. Once these people united, their strength would be great. This time, their minds were muddled. Their people were currently fighting against the Divines, but this news was still uncertain. With how their thoughts were scattered, it was easy to persuade them at this moment.

Zhao Hai believed that the Patriarchs of these vassal races weren’t simple characters. Once the Divines start to fight against the foreign races, these Patriarchs would certainly see the situation and gauge who the true enemy was. As long as they go against the Divines, Zhao Hai believed that they would be able to hold out for a long time.

While the vassal soldiers returned to their camp, the Hell King’s ship reappeared at another place in the Taurus Continent. Zhao Hai was still holding on to his wine glass while Laura and the others were beside him. However, there were some of them who didn’t have a happy expression on their faces.

Zhao Hai still had a calm expression as he drank from his wine glass. Seeing Laura and the others’ unhappy expression, Zhao Hai gently placed his glass on the table and said, “What’s wrong? Are you still angry? There’s no need to be mad. You didn’t want me to kill those people don’t you?”

Lizzy snorted and said, “I hated seeing those guys. You should’ve dealt with them Brother Hai. They’re expendable anyway.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They’re not expendable. If we deal with them, then we would incur a lot of enmity. Those soldiers are the main forces of their clans. If they are absent, then those vassal clans wouldn’t be able to fight against the Divines. If they were to know about today’s matter, then they not only wouldn’t hate us, they might even feel grateful.” Lizzy harrumphed and replied, “I still think that they’re disrespectful. Forget it, I always get angry whenever I think about those guys. In any case, what happened is more beneficial to us. Right, Brother Hai, what do you plan on doing now?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Next, we do nothing. Just let the Bingya and the others send them to the Foreign Races’ continent. I don’t think it would take too long before the Divines make a move against the foreign races.”

Lizzy nodded. At this moment Cai’er suddenly flew to Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Young Master, the O’Neal family has sent a war tank with shields to the Demon Realm. They’re approaching a mine. It won’t be long before they see the undead and the iron armor beasts.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright. I knew this day would come sooner or later. It’s just much earlier than I expected. Don’t worry about them. Just observe the reaction of the O’Neal family when they see the undead and iron armor beasts. I want to see if they’ll just investigate or immediately attack.”

Cai’er nodded before turning around and entering the Space. After that, Laura said, “Brother Hai, what do you want to accomplish by doing this? Do we just let the O’Neal family know about the undead and iron armor beasts?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They would eventually find out anyway. Don’t worry, there’s nothing remarkable about them discovering our mining operations. At the same time, this would also attract more attention from the O’Neal family. This way, they would be more focused on the Demon Realm.”

Laura thought about it and felt that Zhao Hai’s thinking wasn’t wrong. They will have to face the O’Neal family eventually. With a strange place like the Demon Realm, the O’Neal family would surely be interested. With their investigations, there’s no mystery if they were to find out about the undead and iron armor beasts. Instead of hiding all the time, they might as well show themselves and see how the O’Neal family reacts.”

Lizzy turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you want Penny to discover the undead and iron armor beasts in order to attract all of those scouts from the O’Neal family? Can we really delay the discovery of the Divine Realm with this method?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Impossible. The O’Neal family will not abandon the scouting of the continent in exchange for the Demon Realm. They will find the Divine Realm’s spatial rift soon. But we have undead stationed in the rift, they should be able to hold on for a while. We can also use this opportunity to let the three clans be involved. This way, they’ll be able to see the strength of the O’Neal Family.”

Chapter 899: Just A Step Closer!

Inside the war tank, Penny looked out into the dark sky of the Demon Realm. Due to the presence of the sun, he understood that it was currently daytime. However, daytime here was pretty similar to the dark night in the Ark Continent. Therefore, the war tank had to turn on its lights in order to travel normally.

Penny was very worried about this place. He already sent word back to the family so that they could send reinforcements to support him. He needed to figure out what this place was.

They had already affirmed that there were people living in this place. Although their architecture was different from those in the Ark Continent, there was the unfinished city outside the rift that had a similar style. It was already certain that the ones who built that huge city were people from this place.

Judging by the construction of that big city, the spatial rift should have been opened at most in the last two years.

What surprised Penny the most was the huge broken magic formation outside the rift. This was a never before seen formation. The formation wasn’t small, and Penny was sure that the formation had something to do with the rift.

Most importantly, what shook Penny’s heart was the fact that the people from this place had the same fate as those in the Ark Continent. All of them disappeared!

Where did the people from this plane go? How about the people from the Ark Continent? Whatever the reason for these two phenomenon was, it will certainly affect the O’Neal family. All of these thoughts plagued Penny’s mind.

Because of this, after writing the letter to be sent back to the family, he personally led the team, a war tank and ten magic armors, into the Demon Realm.

The war tanks of the Atlanta Plane didn’t need shields. Its main function was to transport magic armors. Installing shields on one would be a waste of resources.

Penny’s war tank, however, was different. A shield was installed in it because they were the ones who went first inside dangerous areas. Therefore, what was bestowed on them were the best war tanks of the family.

But what Penny didn’t know was that their route was going to clash with an ore deposit that Zhao Hai was currently mining. Everything was under Cai’er’s attention. So after she was sure that the scout team would meet the mine, she immediately went to inform Zhao Hai.

Penny was clueless about all of these. His heart was still very heavy, and the state of their team wasn’t very peaceful. The magic beasts in the Demon Realm were more aggressive than the ones back in the Ark Continent. Moreover, the numbers of magic beasts here were a lot more. Although the magic beasts had entered the Space after the beast tide, not all magic beasts participated. Therefore, there were still a lot more magic beasts in the Demon Realm. Even Zhao Hai’s mines were being attacked by these beasts from time to time.

The scouting team were already attacked more than ten times. Although every wave was repelled, the process didn’t come easy. The weapons on the war tank couldn’t even repel the magic beasts, so they would need to deploy the magic armors each time.

It was because of these attacks that Penny knew how aggressive the beasts in the Demon Realm were. Naturally, because of how formidable the magic beasts were, their crystal cores were also much bigger compared to the ones back in the Ark Continent. This allowed Penny’s team to have enough energy to continue on with their journey.

At this time, a red dot was flying towards the war tank. After looking at the red dot, Penny immediately said to the war tank’s driver , “Stop, Mosquito is back.”

Mosquito was just a name given to one of the magic armor units under Penny’s command. Although they were using the war tank to traverse the Demon Realm, Penny still sent magic armors to explore what’s ahead. Magic armors were faster than war tanks, and could observe from the sky. Magic armors were able to see things the war tanks couldn’t.

The war tank driver immediately responded and stopped the war tank. Then the driver pressed a button to make the roof of the tank open up, allowing entry to the magic armor. The magic armor’s pilot was very good, although it entered the war tank, the tank didn’t shake at all.

Penny went towards the back of the war tank, just in time as the front of the magic armor opened and the pilot got out. Upon seeing Penny arrive, the pilot immediately gave a salute and said, “Captain, we’ve discovered something.”

Penny’s spirit shook, he looked at the person and said, “What is it? Tell me.”

The pilot nodded and said, “About four hours ahead of us is a mine. We discovered that there are some undead and some magic beasts mining. From what we can see, they are probably digging gold ore.”

Penny stared for a moment before his two eyes shone, “You mean a gold mine? Are you sure?”

The pilot nodded. He couldn’t blame Penny for his reaction. In the Atlanta Plane, gold was the circulated currency. Therefore, upon hearing about the gold mine, it was no wonder that Penny would have this expression. If there was really a gold mine, then the O’neal family’s invasion of the Ark Continent would immediately pay for itself.

However, Penny continued to ask questions, “So you’re saying, there are undead and magic beasts mining there? Are you sure that they are undead?”

The man nodded, “I’m absolutely sure that they’re undead. But they seem to not have spotted me, and they also look quite weak.”

Penny frowned, “That might be an illusion. We shouldn’t forget about where we are. The magic beasts here are more formidable than those in the Ark Continent. It’s certain that magic beasts have attacked that mine. For them to survive up until now means that they have clever means. We need to be careful.”

After saying that, Penny turned to the war tank driver and said, “Go towards the target. Drive at full speed for two hours. Mosquito, is the road ahead good?”

Mosquito nodded and said, “It’s good. There are no obstructions nor magic beasts.”

Penny frowned, “That makes it even worse. For there to be no magic beasts nearby only means that they had been cleaned up. We’re not too far from the spatial rift, and there are only low-ranked undead and magic beasts in the mine. It seems like this place didn’t have much importance to the other party. The opposite party’s true strength might have been hiding in this plane. It’s imperative that we become extra careful from now on.”

Mosquito gave a serious nod. After that, Penny beckoned towards Mosquito, making him take a rest. Penny needed to guarantee that his people were always in optimum condition. This place is very strange, and they didn’t know how much danger they were going to meet.

Zhao Hai was paying attention to this squad. But from what he saw, he decided to not care about it. The squad was still some distance away from the mine. He’ll just have to wait until the group got into contact with the undead and iron armor beasts.

This would take some several hours. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried. Aside from the O’Neal family’s scouting groups, Zhao Hai was also paying attention to Bingya and the others.

The other scouting teams that the O’Neal family sent out this time weren’t in separate missions. Although they were divided, they weren’t too far apart, and they still communicate with each other from time to time. This was made in order to form a huge surveillance net to scour the southern part of the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about stopping them. If they want to come, then just come. It would just advance the date of their confrontation. There was nothing remarkable about it.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation with Bingya and the others. At this point, the vassal leaders were having a meeting with Bingya’s group. Their expressions were of grief, as though they were asking to have their lives spared.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai knew that Bingya would have these people under control. Now, he needed to think about the next step. The next step that Zhao Hai thought was quite simple. He would get in touch with the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus. He would tell them about the recent developments in the Ark Continent and then ask them to help guard the spatial rift’s defensive line.

Although they were quite busy, Zhao Hai was certain that they would agree. This was because if the O’Neal family were to break through their defensive line and reach the Divine Realm, the first to be unlucky would be the three clans. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried that the three clans would refuse.

And as long as they were willing to send troops, everything else would be very easy to handle. The troops would surely get in contact with the O’Neal family. And once they meet the O’Neal family, then they would come to know how formidable the magic armors were. As long as they can perceive their future losses, Zhao Hai’s invitation to the Space would be more enticing to them.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately took out a messenger fish and contacted Fei’er. It has been quite a while since they two had talked.

Zhao Hai held the messenger fish and said, “Fei’er, Fei’er, are you there? It’s Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai expected that he would have to wait for quite a while. However, he didn’t think that Fei’er would immediately respond. Fei’er’s voice came out of the messenger fish, “Mister Zhao Hai, did something happen?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There is. I have something to tell you about the Divine Realm and the Ark Continent.”

Fei’er went silent for a moment, then after calming himself down, he said, “Mister, tell me.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “The situation in the Divine Realm is going smoothly. We’ve made an agreement with the foreign races. Together, we will deal with the Divines. I also managed to kill a Supreme Elder, the Scorpio Supreme Elder. The other Supreme Elders gathered to deal with me, but they failed. At the same time, the vassal races of the Divine Realm had started a rebellion. The Divines are currently pressed with dealing with this. Also, I managed to defeat 100 million soldiers that the Divines had sent to the Taurus Continent. In the future, the Supreme Elders would shift their focus on the foreign races in order to force me to have a decisive fight with them.”

Although Zhao Hai’s tone was carefree, Fei’er’s heart was actually terrified. From what he heard, Zhao Hai had been in battle against the Divines several times. Otherwise, the Divines wouldn’t have shifted their focus to the foreign races. The method Zhao Hai used against the Divines was the same method he used back in the Ark Continent.

However, Zhao Hai seems to have the upper hand. And for Zhao Hai to be able to compel the other vassal races to rebel was something that was beyond Fei’er’s expectation.

When he heard nothing from Fei’er, Zhao Hai continued, “On the other hand, the situation in the Ark Continent isn’t very good. The underworld is still expanding. The O’Neal family had sent people to the continent. They had discovered the dark mist and are now trying to investigate the south. At this point, they have troops exploring the Demon Realm and soon they will find out about the Divine Realm. I currently don’t have enough strength to stop them from stepping here. Therefore, I plan to ask the three clans for help. What do you think?”

As Zhao Hai thought, Fei’er was silent for a while. Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t something that can be discussed immediately. He just wanted to open the topic so that Fei’er can discuss it with his people.

And just like that, after keeping silent for some time, Fei’er said, “I cannot take responsibility for this matter. I need to discuss this with the Patriarch. Can Mister give us some time?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course. It also doesn’t matter if you cannot send troops. I will muster any manpower I can get in order to defend the spatial rift as much as possible. I just told you about these matters in order to inform you of the current affairs.”

Fei’er nodded and said, “Alright. Mister, I will also convey this matter with the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus. I will give Mister a reply as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. If you have news, then you can just call me any time. Goodbye.”

Fei’er replied, “Goodbye, Mister.” After that, Zhao Hai put the messenger fish down. Plastered on his face was a smile. This was because he felt that the Thunder Clan and the others were now one step closer to migrating to the Space.

Laura and the others were currently sitting next to Zhao Hai. After Zhao Hai and Fei’er’s conversation was over, Laura said, “It seems like our previous actions had made the three clans less wary. Otherwise, Fei’er wouldn’t have taken responsibility of this matter. We have taken a big step this time.”

Zhao Hai lightly smiled and said, “We need to make big steps. If we take small measures, then I might ascend before the three clans decides to enter the Space. Now, I have confidence that the three clans would be migrating to the Space.”

Laura and the others chuckled. They also knew that the three clans were now unable to escape Zhao Hai. The Space needed to be strengthened!

Chapter 900: Finally Reached

Penny’s magic armor was on a hill, looking into the mine in front. This mine wasn’t large. Moreover, there weren’t any living persons here. Those working on the mine were undead and magic beasts.

This kind of magic beast was something that Penny had never seen before. It was covered in scales, and although it wasn’t very tall, it was very powerful and not that slow.

On the other hand, the undead all had skeletal appearance. However, Penny didn’t think like Mosquito and regarded these undead as weak. In fact, Penny thinks that these undead were very strong. However, compared to the scout team, the strength of these undead wasn’t enough.

After all, they were the elites of the O’Neal family. Every magic armor present were God-ranked. Even for the O’Neal family, manufacturing such a magic armor was very difficult. Therefore, seeing the undead as lower level than them was appropriate.

Penny was very rich in experience. He wasn’t the same as Theo, who hadn’t experienced a real war. It can be said that Theo was one of the more recent geniuses that the O’Neal family had trained.

This time, the O’Neal family thought that the Ark Continent was a very good place, so they took Theo to try his talent. But who could’ve known that there were so many strange things happening in the Ark Continent, causing Theo to end up in the frontlines.

On the other hand, Penny didn’t become famous as early as Theo. Moreover, in terms of talent, it can be said that Penny had none. Penny crawled from the lowest level to his current position. After going through several hundreds of missions, Penny’s experience was very abundant. Because of this, he became the captain of this scouting squad.

Penny didn’t dare to look down on the mine. Although it seems like its defense wasn’t that solid. He could see upon further inspection that the undead were distributed quite reasonably. The undead were currently doing their own work, as if there were no threats in the surroundings. However, Penny knew that no matter which angle he attacked the mine, he would still be discovered by the undead. It can be said that the person who arranged this mine was an expert.

What surprised Penny the most was the fact that the the undead who were mining here had nobody commanding them. There wasn’t even a house in sight, only a lot of open mines with undead and magic beasts going in and out. Penny couldn’t see anybody else, which made him very puzzled.

In Penny’s experience, the undead are controlled by a Dark Mage. Moreover, it was impossible for a Dark Mage to keep this kind of operation for a long time, it would consume a lot of magic power.

Even God-ranked Dark Mages of the Atlanta Plane couldn’t make their undead go out all the time. During battles, they would release their undead. And when the fight ends, they will take the undead away.

However, Penny was already on the hill for two hours, and yet the undead were still religiously doing their work. There weren’t a moment of weakness nor loss of control. This made Penny both confused and wary.

Although there weren’t that much undead and magic beasts in this mine, what Penny saw was different. This mine was definitely not the only one being worked on by the opposite party. In other words, the other party had a lot more undead and magic beasts. Moreover, the other party had the ability to keep their undead working outside for a long time. This meant that the controller of these undead had the advantage with regards to longevity compared to Penny’s team. After all, the magic armors needed energy while these undead apparently didn’t.

After looking at the mine for some time, Penny decided to retreat. There was no need to observe this mine. Penny also wasn’t ready to attack this mine because most of the workers here were undead. Although these undead might not have a controller, according to Penny’s past experiences, these undead would have a spiritual connection to their owners. Attacking the undead would certainly attract the attention of the other party. And being noticed wasn’t what Penny wanted right now.

However, what Penny didn’t know was that his every action had been seen by Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai now held great admiration towards these scouts of the O’Neal family. If he didn’t have the Space, then he wouldn’t have found Penny. Penny’s way of moving about was something that was difficult to deal with.

However, although Zhao Hai was looking at Penny, his main focus was placed on the other scout teams that were sent to the south. Their advance was very fast. They had almost reached the border between the Buddha Empire and the Radiant Empire.

As long as they pass this border, then these people would have a huge chance of discovering the Divine Realm’s spatial rift. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s attention was placed on them.

At the same time, Bingya and the others had also reached an agreement with the vassal soldiers. Bingya would deliver news back to his people in order to pick the vassal soldiers up as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai didn’t care too much about this matter. The only thing that surprised Zhao Hai was Bingya using such a laborious method to send the vassal soldiers to the Foreign Races’ continent.

However, Zhao Hai soon came to understand. After arranging the vassal soldiers’ matters, Bingya and the others immediately went to the Hell King’s ship. It seems like Bingya was planning to join him once more.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to drive Bingya and the others away. They can come whenever they want to. They won’t have any influence to Zhao Hai. what Zhao Hai was waiting for at this time was the news from Fei’er and the others. He wanted to know the result of their discussion.

It took only five days before the people sent by the Foreign Races came to pick up the vassal races. After Bingya handed the vassal soldiers over, Zhao Hai gave the vassal soldiers their food before they left.

However, what Bingya and the others didn’t expect was their people’s anxiety to leave with the vassal races. They didn’t even stay for a minute. This confused Bingya and the other two.

But when Bingya saw his people having a look at the Hell King’s ship, he understood. These people were afraid of Zhao Hai, they wanted to leave this place as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai didn’t manage the vassal soldiers, he just left them to the foreign races. He had more important things to do. The O’Neal family’s scouts had finally reached the spatial rift to the Divine Realm.

The O’Neal family’s scouts had already discovered the spatial rift four days ago. But after seeing it, the scouts didn’t immediately go forward. Instead, the kept steadily moving. It looks like they were wary for any traps left by the enemy.

This way, they spent four days moving along before arriving at the spatial rift. Zhao Hai had also set up a large number of troops, waiting for the O’Neal family’s arrival.

In addition to the undead army, the spatial rift also had a large number of Thunder Clan, Barbarian, and Winged Pegasus troops. After discussing for two days, the clans finally decided to send troops to the rift to help Zhao Hai defend.

Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised about this decision. Therefore, when Fei’er told him about their answer, the food was already prepared for them. The only thing left to do was to wait for the troops to arrive.

As the O’Neal family’s troops arrived at the spatial rift, the armies had also arrived. However, nobody saw anyone as they were at both sides of the rift.

This time, the trio led the troops. Zhao Hai already knew Fei’er, Ding, and Shan. After all, they were acquainted back in the Ark Continent.

When the troops arrived at the defensive line, they discovered that Zhao Hai was already waiting for them. After looking at the Hell King’s ship in the distance, Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but feel uplifted. The ship was too marvelous, their hearts couldn’t help but feel at ease, their minds settled.

With an intention, Zhao Hai made the ship descend to the ground. While looking at the troops sent by the three clans, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Everyone, after you get settled in, please come on board to have a chat.”

Fei’er and the others understood what Zhao Hai meant. Therefore, they nodded before they settled their troops. Only after everything was taken care of did they go to the Hell King’s Ship.

When the three arrived at the ship, the discovered that Zhao Hai had prepared a table full of food and wine.

After seeing the three people arrive, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You’re here. Come, take a seat. Let’s share a few cups of wine.”

Fei’er and the others gave a salute before they sat down. After that, Zhao Hai said, “You coming here really made me happy. Come, join me in this toast.”

The group raised their wine glasses and then downed the contents in one go.

After placing the glass down, Zhao Hai looked at the three and said, “I know you’ve gone through a lot of trouble in bringing these troops. For this I need to thank you.”

Fei’er smiled bitterly. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would guess their situation. Just as Zhao Hai said, the troops were sent after some troubles. This was because the elders of the clans were divided whether they should cooperate with Zhao Hai or not. There were some who wanted to help Zhao Hai. After all, Zhao Hai gave them aid in dealing with the Taurus Divines. There were also those who wanted to stop cooperating with Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was currently at war with the Divines. If they cooperated, then it’s possible that they would get pulled into the conflict. It’s possible that the three clans would perish in this war.

Chapter 901: A Fight On Both Sides!

Actually, the argument started when the Taurus Divines were destroyed. The three clans didn’t think that they would have this much loss in the war. Because of this, they became afraid.

Fei’er and the others worked extremely hard. They were still young, but they were intelligent. Compared to the conservative elders, their ideas were different.

Fei’er and the others knew that they were now closely tied with Zhao Hai. They had been able to destroy the Taurus Divines thanks to Zhao Hai. Fei’er and the other also knew that destroying the Taurus Divines will not keep their peace. It was impossible for the other Divines to just leave the Taurus Continent. It can be said that the destruction of the Taurus Divines was just the start of an endless war against the Divine Race.

Fei’er expected that such a day would come. In fact, Fei’er thought that Zhao Hai’s report came a bit too late. Fei’er expected that after the Taurus Divines were extinguished, the Divine race would immediately retaliate. The reason why their clans hadn’t met any attack was surely because Zhao Hai had kept the Divines off. If it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then the Divine Race’s army would have come to retaliate.

Now that Zhao Hai had asked them to send some troops to defend the spatial rift, no matter what purpose, the three clans couldn’t refuse. It was because it will cause a crack between them and Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai stopped helping them, then with the strength of their tribes, it was impossible to stop the Divine Race army.

Moreover, Fei’er and the others were a little worried. Since Zhao Hai was able to defeat the Taurus Divines, then this meant that Zhao Hai had the means to save himself. If Zhao Hai decides to leave, then the three clans would surely be finished.

Fei’er and the others have been in contact with Zhao Hai for a long time. Although Fei’er didn’t know about Zhao Hai’s Space, Fei’er could still understand that Zhao Hai was a person with many solutions. Being able to defend the Ark Continent from the attacks of the Demons and the Divines, and eventually going to the Divine Realm to conquer a continent, this only meant that Zhao Hai had methods that Fei’er and the others couldn’t understand.

Fei’er hopes that, one day, once Zhao Hai decides to leave the Divine Realm, that he would help the three clans move. Even if he cannot move the three clans, then at least Zhao Hai could leave behind some means of preservation so that the three clans could continue existing.

Fei’er, Ding, and Shan had experienced battles together many times, so they had developed a deep sense of friendship. Moreover, since Zhao Hai’s messenger fish was with them, the three met for an exchange once in a while. Therefore, Ding and Shan knew about Fei’er’s ideas, and they completely support Fei’er.

Because of this, for the deployment of troops, the three of them worked extremely hard. The three were now the most accomplished people in each of their clans. Therefore, the three had enough clout in their family to make decisions.

However, all of these conflicts were made in secret. All the while, the three clans were doing their best to keep a good relationship with Zhao Hai. Therefore, when Zhao Hai guessed the situation, Fei’er was somewhat surprised.

The reason Zhao Hai managed to guess this matter was because the troops that Fei’er and the others led were devoid of any elders. This alone must be a type of signal. Therefore, Zhao Hai spoke his words as a probe, he didn’t expect that there would be a result.

When Zhao Hai saw the reaction of the three people, he placed a marker on his heart. Then he looked at the three and said, “In the decisive battle against the Taurus Divines, the loss to your clans was great. It’s natural for your people to develop war weariness. The reason I  asked you for troops this time was to make you take a look at the kind of enemy that you will face. If I can’t stop them one day, and your clans couldn’t find any countermeasures. Then you will suffer even bigger losses.”

When Fei’er heard this, he couldn’t help but feel ashamed as he got up and said, “I’ve been unfair to Mister. Our people has been unfair.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “It’s fine. Your clansmen are just thinking about your people. At this point, my battle with the Divine Race had gone to the point of using ultimate weapons. Even if you participate in the war, there’s not much that you can help. On the other hand, you need to be careful when facing the people from the Atlanta Plane. Their way of fighting is something that you and I have never encountered before.”

Fei’er and the others nodded. They were still young, and they’re still at an age that they looked up to someone. With Zhao Hai’s strength, it’s natural that the three would be deeply respectful to him.

Zhao Hai looked at the three people and smiled, “Alright, we’ll not dwell on this anymore. Let’s enjoy the meal today. Later on, I will provide you with supplies. If you need anything else, don’t hesitate to tell me. I might not be here in the future. I heard that the Divines are planning to deal with the foreign races. I will use this opportunity to go to their continents to cause trouble.”

When they heard Zhao Hai say this, Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but laugh. Naturally, they could understand what Zhao Hai wanted to do. When the time comes, the Divine Race would be have a hard time.

They didn’t know whether they became drunk or not, but they always relaxed in front of Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai didn’t drink too much, he arranged some rooms for the three before returning to his room. Laura and the others were already there waiting for him.

When Zhao Hai returned to his room smelling of wine, Meg immediately gave him a cup of strong tea. This was a habit that Zhao Hai developed. Every time he drank wine, he would like to drink tea right after. With the Space’s water, the tea would immediately solve Zhao Hai’s drunkenness.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, how about we tell Fei’er and the others more of our secrets. From what I can see, they looked very respectful towards you. If we have their help, then we might be more successful in moving their clans to the Space.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “We’ll look for an opportunity to tell them. Right, how is the situation with the O’Neal Family?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “They seem to be relaxed. It looks like they will enter the spatial rift tomorrow. How do we deal with them?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Since there is a defensive line by the spatial rift, then we might as well make use of it. Let’s make the O’Neal family know that we are waiting for them here.”

At this time, a knock was suddenly heard outside the door. After that, Bingya’s voice came, “Mister, are you in?”

Bingya and the others haven’t come out of their rooms today. They knew that Zhao Hai was having a meeting with Fei’er and the others, therefore they decided to stay inside.

When he heard Binya, Zhao Hai stared for a moment. He knew that something must have happened. Otherwise, Bingya wouldn’t have come to disturb him at this time. Zhao Hai nodded to Laura who went to the door and opened it before asking Bingya to come in.

This was the first time that Bingya had entered Zhao Hai’s room. Bingya thought that Zhao Hai’s room was just a bit bigger than the others, with nothing special inside. However, upon entering, Bingya couldn’t help but get shocked. This wasn’t a room, this was a completely independent space. There was grass on the ground and there was even a villa not far away.

However, when Bingya saw Zhao Hai, he immediately recovered. Then he walked towards Zhao Hai and bowed, “Mister, the family had just sent information to me. The Divine Race’s army has been prepared. By tomorrow, they will dispatch troops towards our continent.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows when he heard this. The O’Neal family would send their scouts in tomorrow. At the same time, the Divines would also send their troops. It seems like a fight on both sides wasn’t something that he can avoid.

Bingya saw Zhao Hai frown. He thought that Zhao Hai was feeling some difficulty. Bingya’s heart couldn’t help but tighten. Bingya was confident that Zhao Hai could defeat the Divine Race, something that he didn’t trust his own family to do. Therefore, when Zhao Hai frowned, Bingya couldn’t help but get anxious.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai just slightly frowned and nodded, “Alright. It seems like the Divines are ready to fight. Right, can you find out whether the Supreme Elders are coming to deal with the foreign races?”

Bingya nodded, “I’ve inquired. I heard from the family that seven are coming.”

Zhao Hai nodded. This was what he expected. Leaving two Supreme Elders to defend while the others would attack. This went according to what Elder Star and the others discussed. However, this was an opportunity for Zhao Hai.

After seeing that Zhao Hai hasn’t spoken for a while, Bingya looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, do you have any words to send to our family?”

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya and smiled, “Not too much. Just tell them that they need to defend well. I will go to the continents of the Divine Race in order to deal with this matter.”

Bingya nodded and said, “There is another thing. The vassal races had reached the foreign races. When their clans found out that they had fought with Mister, they were very ashamed. They had me come here to express their apology.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “It’s fine, no need to say sorry. So, are they willing to fight against the Divines? Right, if you clan needs any weapons, I might provide some for you.”

When Bingya heard this, he immediately replied, “Thank you Mister. Our family does need some weapons right now. Magic beast mounts, javelins, and some magic cannons would be good.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I can give you some magic beasts. However, I can’t give you magic cannons. My blood lightning javelins are also quite deadly. They should be fine.” Bingya’s face lit up as he thanked Zhao Hai before taking his leave.

Chapter 902: Science and Technology Background and Universal Scanner

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t give Bingya any magic cannons was because Zhao Hai’s magic cannons used special crystals. And he didn’t want the Divine Race to know about that.

One day quickly passed by. The next day, Fei’er and the others were still tipsy. It was only after eating breakfast did they recover. They also knew from Zhao Hai that the Atlanta Plane may attack today. Therefore, they immediately returned to their armies after eating.

Zhao Hai also knew that the Divines would attack the foreign races, however, he wasn’t anxious to deal with them. He wanted the Divines to fight against the foreign races for a period of time before he goes to give aid. In the meantime, Zhao Hai wanted to stay here and deal with the O’Neal family in order to get a couple of magic armors for himself.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t planning to fight with the Divines right now, he was preparing to deal with them. The most important thing for him right now was to get more God-ranks and produce more Scorpio combat suits to be handed over to the Devil Legion.

These days, Zhao Hai had already accrued several hundred Scorpio Combat suits and had given it to the Devil Legion to use. Because of the added functions of the combat suits, the Devil Legion had yet to get fully accustomed to using them. Therefore, they needed to train for some time. Only then can Zhao Hai take them and then sweep the entire world clean.

In addition to the combat suits for the Demons, Zhao Hai also produced a lot of God-rank potions. At this point, almost all of the Buda Clan’s members were God-ranks, even Laura and the others. But although they had reached God-rank, their combat power was still a lot worse than a full God-rank expert.

The O’neal family didn’t let Zhao Hai wait for a long time. At around 9 in the morning, a 30-man team of magic armors flew in from the spatial rift.

The reason why the O’Neal family failed to find Zhao Hai’s defensive line was because the defensive line was covered by Zhao Hai’s fog. This thick fog wasn’t the dark mist but just an ordinary white fog. However, this fog can block the Divine Sense of God-ranks and other means of detection. Therefore, the O’Neal family had no way of knowing what was going on inside the fog.

It was because of Zhao Hai’s arrangement that the O’Neal family wasn’t able to discover that Zhao Hai had set-up a defensive line.

The 30 magic armors flew towards the white fog slowly and carefully. Moreover, they maintained their humanoid form and didn’t transform. They needed to be prepared for battle at any time.

Just as the team were being careful, a few blue lights suddenly went straight towards them. The O’Neal family immediately avoided the lights.

This tactical avoidance was something that magic armor pilots must study. This was in preparation to avoid attacks made by both battle qi and magic.

And since these scouts were the elites of the O’Neal family, their movements were extremely done well. No blue light was able to hit even a single magic armor.

However, just as the blue light missed, another barrage of blue lights came in, and with greater magnitude. The O’Neal family’s soldiers didn’t have the means to hide immediately so they quickly established their shields. At the same time, they also launched an attack towards the blue lights.

The magic armor attacks came in the form of white energy beams that seemed more concentrated. When the white energy collided with the blue energy, a loud noise was immediately heard.

The two energy beams collided together, causing a huge explosion that blew the fog away. This allowed the O’Neal scouts to see their enemies. Not far from them was a defensive line. There seems to be a lot of shadows on that defensive line, signalling how large the army was.

Upon seeing this, the O’Neal family’s scouts stopped. Then they went into a tactical formation and slowly retreated.

However, it was too late for them to retreat at this time. Blue lights came in from behind them. The blue lights were woven into a light net, surrounding the magic armors. They can’t even hide if they wanted to.

However, the O’Neal family’s scouts reacted very quickly. They immediately formed a circular formation. All the magic armors set up their shields and then sent out energy beams from their hands. The cooperation of these people were well-coordinated, the blue lights were unable to hit them even once.

But the blue light kept coming. The O’Neal family’s scouts felt the pressure on them getting bigger and bigger.

At this moment, someone from the team loudly said, “Explosive attacks! We’ll blow a path for retreat. Otherwise, we will get stuck here forever.”

It was obvious that his person was the commander of the team. As soon as he said that, the magic armors immediately moved. Something suddenly elevated from their shoulders, of which had four holes each.

On each shoulder were four small missiles. The missiles were immediately launched and headed towards the source of the blue light.

After a loud noise, the blue lights coming from that place evidently decreased. The O’Neal family scouts used this opportunity to retreat back towards the Ark Continent.

Meanwhile, blue lights kept coming towards the scouts, getting blocked by the shields all the time. Although the blue lights were lessened, those left were still quite a lot. The scouts can only resist and block the blue lights. It was necessary for the blue lights to be blocked by the shield. However, using the shield to block the blue lights consumed energy. The energy on each magic armor was getting consumed rapidly.

Then suddenly, two magic armors on the rear of the team were grazed by uniquely strong blue lights. Their shields flashed for a moment before it disappeared. There was no need to wait before the two magic armors were bombarded by the blue lights.

The two magic armors didn’t explode. Instead, they were frozen in an instant. The magic armors immediately fell, but before reaching the ground, a spatial rift took them in.

The demise of the two magic armors were naturally seen by the other scouts. They became startled, but they also became more careful.

They didn’t know what the blue lights were, and they didn’t know why the rift appeared. However, they can affirm that the two magic armors and their pilots were already gone.

Actually, the two strong blue lights weren’t anything special. They were just light beams made from combining several magic cannons.

This time, Zhao Hai didn’t attack from start to finish. He just let the undead attack the magic armors using magic cannons. He wants to see how how capable the magic armors were.

The result startled Zhao Hai. He didn’t think that the magic armors would actually be this defensive.

After taking the two magic armors, Zhao Hai immediately threw them to the Space. When the two armors were sent in, a prompt immediately came, “Magic and Technology machine detected. The machine is the primary product of the combination between magic and science. The machine has fulfilled the requirements of opening science and technology backgrounds. Asking host for permission to open science and technology backgrounds.”

Zhao Hai stared, for a while he didn’t understand what the Space said. After a short time, an additional prompt came, “Due to the discovery of a unified magic and technological item, a special item has been offered, the Universal Scanner. This machine can analyze, design, compute, and simulate various items from magic civilizations, science and technology civilizations, and even cultivation civilizations.The machine can be upgraded further.  In order to use this item, host needs to achieve level 80 and above, has unlocked magic civilizations, and science and technology civilizations, as well as 5 million gold coins. Asking host for permission to unlock this item.”

Zhao Hai was stunned. The Universal Processing Machine already gave him a surprise. Now, he didn’t expect that a Universal Scanner would exist, and it could actually be upgraded. It looks like its functions were formidable. Zhao Hai went still, he felt that his head was turning.

However, Zhao Hai managed to recover quickly as he said, “Open the background and the special item.”  After saying this, he can immediately feel the Space taking more than 5 million gold coins from his wallet. After that, a building appeared right beside the processing machine.

The processing machine’s building looked just like a simple workshop, there’s nothing magnificent about it at all. On the other hand, this new structure was three stories high. It had the standard architecture of a science and technology civilization. It was made with metallic frames and also had glass for windows. It appeared neat and clean.

Zhao Hai badly wished to enter the Space right now to look at this scanner. However, he stopped himself from doing so. He can only look at the scanner through the monitor. This was because Zhao Hai was afraid that if he enter the Space, then he would ascend the moment he went out.

This was something that Zhao Hai felt. He feels that if he entered the Space, then he would have to ascend once he goes back out again. It was precisely because of this feeling that Zhao Hai doesn’t dare to enter the Space. He could only command the Space through his mind and look through its situation through the monitor.

As Zhao Hai processed the Space’s prompt, the O’Neal family’s scouts were continually being hunted. Although some of them were shot down by the magic cannons, most of them eventually managed to get out.

In addition to the magic armors’ strength, the people outside the rift also played a role in assisting the retreating scouts. With the combination of magic armors and war tanks, they were able to escape smoothly.

Fei’er and the others led their army and stood by the side, watching the undead as they fought against the magic armors. To be honest, the result of the fight was beyond their expectations. Not only because they were happy that five magic armors were taken down, but also because they only had this much achievement.

They knew how formidable the magic cannons were. Even the Divines wouldn’t dare to block them directly. However, those magic armors actually suffered a lot of attacks from the magic armors without being wiped out. This startled Fei’er and the others.

And then there was also the attacking strength exhibited by the magic armors. One must know that there were over a thousand magic cannons who participated in the attack. In the end, they only managed to down five magic armors. This result was below expectations. And when the counter-attack from the magic armors came in, they actually ruined 200 of Zhao Hai’s magic cannons. These magic cannons were destroyed undear Zhao Hai’s defensive magic formations. The attack not only depleted the energy of the formation, it also managed to destroy 200 magic cannons. Such attacking strength made Fei’er and the other feel cold in their hearts.

Zhao Hai’s defensive formations were very formidable. Even Divines would treat them as a headache. Who would’ve thought that the magic armors would actually destroy them in one round of attacks.

Once the magic armors retreated back to the Ark continent, Fei’er and the others began to loosen up. Although the time of today’s battle was short, they had the sense of being breathless just by observing it. It was too fierce, it was to a degree that surpassed their imagination.

After the fight ended, Fei’er, Ding, Shan, Bingya, Ryder, and Yehta looked at the battlefield. Their expressions sunken. It was at this point that they finally believed Zhao Hai. The opponent was indeed difficult to deal with.

Think about it, there were only 30 magic armors and they were under attack by a thousand magic cannons. There was also the geographic advantage as well as the element of ambush. In the end, they only managed to shoot down 5 of the 30 magic armors. The rest ran away while also causing Zhao Hai to lose 200 magic cannons and more than 100 undead.

Fei’er and the others knew that Zhao Hai only used 9th rank undead in order to man the magic cannons. In their opinion, 9th ranks weren’t very strong. After all, Fei’er and the others were all God-ranks.

However, although these undead weren’t strong in their eyes, 9th rank undead were still a threat. Even demigods wouldn’t be able to easily deal with them. But now, an explosion caused by the enemy party actually managed to kill more than 100 of them.

The undead under Zhao Ha’s command were very hard to deal with. Fei’er and the others knew how Zhao Hai managed to destroy the Taurus Divines. These undead were not only offensively strong, they’re quite defensive as well. Under the undead attacks, no enemy would feel easy. This fact alone showed how formidable magic armors were!

Shocked, frightened, and a feeling hint of despair, these emotions were running around Fei’er and the others’ hearts!

Chapter 903: Zhao Hai’s Thoughts

Zhao Hai didn’t know about what Fei’er and the others were thinking. Right now, he badly wanted to see the changes made in the Space, but he still resisted. He still had a lot of things to do, he didn’t want to ascend right now.

Zhao Hai made the undead clean the battlefield before returning to the Taurus Continent. At this time, Fei’er and the others also arrived on the Hell King’s ship.

As soon as Fei’er and the others entered the ship, Zhao Hai could see the evident weight on their expressions. It looked like they were the ones defeated in the battle.

Zhao Hai gawked, he looked at Fei’er and said, “What’s wrong? Why do all of you look so sad?”

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and smiled bitterly before he said, “Mister, this enemy has gone beyond our expectations. They seem to be more formidable than the Divine Race. Can we really win against them?”

After hearing this, Zhao Hai immediately understood why Fei’er and the others were looking  so sad. To be honest, Zhao Hai was also startled at the performance made by the O’Neal family. However, he didn’t think the same as Fei’er and the others. Although the attack power of the magic armors wasn’t bad, to say that they were invincible was too much.

Moreover, Zhao Hai knew that the magic armors of the O’Neal family scouts were high-level magic armors. It’s impossible for the whole of O’Neal family’s troops to have that kind of firepower.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and the others, he smiled faintly and said, “It’s alright. There’s no need to be worried about this matter. Those people didn’t come in due to our provocation. And if they really did come, it’s impossible for us to not resist. However, they are not invincible. I have some understanding about these people. Come and have a seat while we talk.”

Fei’er and the others nodded before they sat down. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “I have met with a person from the Atlanta Plane before. At that time, I didn’t express my status. The only thing I told him was the fact that I’m someone from the Ark Continent. I didn’t tell him the state of the continent as well. I told him that the Ark Continent only had 9th ranks and couldn’t raise God-rank experts. During that time, I was preparing to counter-attack the Divine Realm.”

Fei’er and the others didn’t expect that Zhao Hai to have met someone from the Atlanta Plane. This information startled them. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “The people from the Atlanta Plane are special. Actually, the Atlanta Plane is….” Then Zhao Hai introduced the Atlanta Plane to Fei’er and the others, and the fact that only the O’Neal family were their enemies.

Fei’er and the others silently listened to Zhao Hai. They didn’t expect Zhao Hao to have looked into the enemy this much. He even managed to learn that Atlanta Plane’s language.

Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “Although the magic armors we saw today are very strong, those are already the elites of the O’Neal family. They are the strongest troops of the family. Defeating even a single one of them is already good, judging by how valued they are to the O’Neal family. In addition to this, magic armors have a fatal weakness.”

Fei’er and the others looked puzzled at Zhao Hai, they were waiting for what was next. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The magic armors has a problem when it comes to long term encounters. Inside those magic armors are people, yet those people don’t supply energy to the armors. Instead, the magic armors have their own power supply. All of the power needed by the magic armors are also made by energy conversion devices. I don’t know how the people of the Atlanta Plane did it, but the energy conversion device can extract energy to form magic crystals that can power magic armors. It can be said that without magic crystals, magic armors are just pieces of scrap iron.”

Upon hearing this, the eyes of Fei’er and the others shone. They understood what Zhao Hai just meant. They  were people who had been in battles in the past and were experienced with matters of war. Therefore, upon hearing Zhao Hai speak about this energy source, they immediately knew about the magic armors’ weakness.

When he saw the group’s expresion light up, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “So now you know their weakness? Hahaha. Yes, the magic armors couldn’t fight for a very long time. Moreover, when they make battle, their energy consumption becomes much stronger. This is our enemy’s biggest weakness.”

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, those people didn’t play for long and just ran. Is it because the magic cannons are too strong, consuming their energy? Is that why they retreated? If they didn’t, then they would have been rendered useless. When the time comes, we can just round them up.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Correct. Therefore, during their attacks, they always have war tanks following behind. Those war tanks might be quick and defensive, but their attacking strength isn’t a lot. If we can constrain those war tanks,  then we can cripple the advancing speed of those magic armors. And if the war tanks aren’t available, then the magic armors wouldn’t be able to fight. Most importantly, those war tanks aren’t able to fly.”

Fei’er and the others had a smile on their faces. They thought that the magic armors were invincible. But it was just because they didn’t have an understanding of them. Now, with Zhao Hai’s information, there’s no need to be afraid.

After seeing his goal achieved, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything more. Instead, he proceeded to discuss with Fei’er and the others about how to deal with the O’Neal family.

Besides Fei’er’s group, Bingya’s group was also in the Hell King’s ship. Bingya and the others had followed Zhao Hai ever since he attacked the Taurus Divines, therefore, they were also acquainted with Fei’er and the others. It can be said that their relationship wasn’t bad. Because of this, sitting and chatting with each other wasn’t an awkward event.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the group. It can be said that the people onboard were all targets of Zhao Hai. He wanted to pull them to his side and become his people.

However, Zhao Hai knew that he couldn’t be direct to these people just like what he did with the Demons. The reason Zhao Hai succeeded with the Demons was because the Demons wanted to change their environment in the first place. The Demon Realm was just too terrible a place to live in.

On the other hand, the people of the Ark Continent moved to the Space because of many reasons. The first reason was due to them having three enemies at that time, the Demons, the Divines, and the Underworld. Moreover, either one of these enemies wasn’t something that the Ark Continent could deal with. The second reason was Zhao Hai’s high prestige among the people.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t treated as a god at that time, there were people who placed his portrait on their houses. They were already looking at him as an idol.

With these reasons combined together, the Ark Continent’s people decided to leave and move into the Space.

Meanwhile, the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus had living environments much better than the Ark Continent. Their respective planes could produce God-rank experts. Naturally, their planes weren’t as good as the Space. However, they also won’t envy those living inside the Space, making them very different than the Demons.

In addition to this, the Thunder Clan and the others had just broken out from being controlled by the Divine Race. Although they had cooperated with Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai’s reputation among their people wasn’t that high. Making the three clans migrate to the Space would be quite difficult.

Although Fei’er and the others were very respectful towards Zhao Hai, these three people were considerate to their own races. If Zhao Hai wanted to win them over, then he would have to be careful.

The situation with Bingya and the others was much more complex. Bingya and the others’ status in their clans weren’t high, they didn’t have too many rights to make decisions. And with them being very loyal to their people, winning them over wouldn’t be very easy.

Because he needed to consider all of these, Zhao Hai decided to refrain from telling these people many of his secrets. Zhao Hai knew that the Space wouldn’t be able to convince these people given the Space’s weak power over beings with wisdom.

The reason why the Great Demon King, a person with extremely firm mental state, decided to move towards the Space was only due to the Space’s highly beneficial environment. And the Demon King also believed that if Zhao Hai doesn’t deliver on his promise, then the Demons would surely retaliate. It was precisely because of these reason that the Demon King decided to agree with Zhao Hai’s proposal and moved the Demons to the Space.

Moreover, after entering the Space, the Great Demon King was still fighting for the interests of the Demons. This wasn’t the same as what Zhao Hai experienced before.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was made aware that the Space wasn’t an all-powerful existence. With regards to intelligent lifeforms, the Space’s abilities were very limited.

Fei’er’s group as well as Bingya’s group were vastly different compared to the Great Demon King. The Great Demon King was the lord of the Demon Realm, an incomparably high existence compared to any other Demon. One could say that as long as one persuades the Great Demon King, then the entire Demon Race would also be persuaded. And with Lu Wei’s matter, Zhao Hai was able to take the risk and persuade the Great Demon King.

On the other hand, Fei’er and the others weren’t the leaders of their own people. There were still people with positions above them. Words spoken by Fei’er and the others wouldn’t bear too much of a weight. Even if Zhao Hai managed to persuade them, it didn’t mean that he had persuaded their entire clans. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t risk expressing all of his secrets.

At this time, Zhao Hai was still observing Fei’er and the others. As long as Zhao Hai’s position in Fei’er and the others’ hearts stump their feeling towards their people, only then would Zhao Hai try to make a move.

Zhao Hai needed people at this time. Now that he had unlocked the science and technology background, this meant that he would have more space. If nobody occupies those backgrounds, then they would be wasted. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to recruit as many people as he can. However, he couldn’t do this unreasonably. Making a lot of people aware of his secret wasn’t a good thing to do.

Chapter 904: Lesser Science and Technology Background

George felt like he had a nightmare as we walked out of his armor. He was a bit depressed. He didn’t think that he would be beaten and lose 5 magic armors during a scouting mission. For him, this loss was not small.[1]

Just as what Zhao Hai said, these magic armors were high-quality armors of the O’Neal family. Compared to ordinary magic armors, the construction costs of these advanced armors were many times more. Now that they had lost five, the losses were very heavy.

Besides the loss of magic armors, the damage to the morale was also very big. George was a man bent on winning. But when the Clan didn’t send him on the first scouting mission, George couldn’t help but feel unpleasant.

In big families, scouts were the most essential troops. Having the family send you on a scouting mission didn’t meant that they want you dead. Instead, the family trusted you and has given you favor. This also meant that one wouldn’t be far from being promoted.

George was very ambitious. He wanted to be an officer and one with a very high position. Not being sent on the first scouting mission made him feel depressed. George thinks that his ability was no worse than Lewis. Moreover, to George, Lewis was just a fallen genius, not someone that can compare to him. Also, Penny was someone who was extremely careful. He will always pause before making a move. In George’s opinion, these two people were inferior to himself. The first choice to be a scout should be him.

In the end, he was left disappointed. Fortunately, the family sent him on the second batch of scouts. Because he had waited eagerly for this time, George wanted to perform well.

The net formation before was George’s doing. One has to recognize that George had talent, but his luck was very bad.

Lewis met the Underworld. And as long as one withdraws from the Dark Mist, then the underworld’s creatures wouldn’t pursue you. The underworld’s range was only within its territory.

Penny met the Demon Realm. Nobody was inside the Demon Realm. Therefore, Penny wasn’t attacked like George.

On the other hand, George entered the Divine Realm, Zhao Hai’s backyard. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be polite to him.

Although their losses weren’t catastrophic, George was still furious. This was because Lewis and Penny brought benefits without any losses. Although George also managed to get information, the losses he incurred still stung.

After George came out, he immediately turned to the person beside him and said, “Immediately arrange for people to report back to the family. Make the situation here clear and express our losses. Ask the family to send support as soon as possible.”

The man beside George immediately nodded before turning around to make the preparations. George looked around him and saw 20 war tanks and 300 or so magic armors. This number couldn’t be underestimated. However, George still thought that this wasn’t safe. At this time, they had no idea what kind of weapon the enemy was using. Because of this, George immediately said, “Transmit this command. Everyone retreat to the closest city for repairs. Give monitoring priority to this spatial rift.”

Although George was depressed, but as a competent scout he still made the correct decision. He might badly want to be an accomplished officer, but this wouldn’t necessarily be a weakness. Sometimes, this mindset was beneficial because he would need to watch his every action, making sure that he doesn’t make the wrong moves.

He knew that his greatest asset right now was his ability to be a scout. As long as he performs well, he was likely to be a high-ranking official. Therefore, he always made sure to make the best moves.

George’s order was immediately performed. The war tanks quickly proceeded to retreat. George didn’t actually enter the war tank, instead he stood on the roof looking at the Divine Realm’s spatial rift. His facial expression was somewhat complex. After some time, he coldly snorted and said, “Just wait, I will come back.” After saying that, George jumped into his war tank and flew towards the nearest city.

The city that George chose was the closest city to the rift. Departing from this city using a war tank, one would only need two hours before reaching the spatial rift. And while standing on the city’s walls, one could clearly see the spatial rift. This was the reason why George chose this place.

At this time, attacking the rift wasn’t a choice. What they needed to do was to monitor the rift and report what happened back to the family.

But what George didn’t know was that Zhao Hai was keeping an eye on him. After giving relief to Fei’er and the others, Zhao Hai had the group go back and prepare. After this, Zhao Hai’s attention was turned to the Divine Race. As for the O’Neal family, Zhao Hai was fine as long as they were outside the Divine Realm.

Naturally, the defense of the rift was handed over to Fei’er’s group. Zhao Hai believed that Fei’er and the others could block the O’Neal family, but amidst a few losses. In this case, it would be much easier for them to enter the Space.

After Fei’er and the others left, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately turn his attention to George’s group. He first returned to his room and opened the monitor. Then he called Cai’er over in order to know more about the science and technology backgrounds.

For Zhao Hai, both the magic armors and the Divine Race weren’t as important as improving the level of the Space. What surprised Zhao Hai this time was the fact that there were no prompts about levelling up. It just said that science and technology backgrounds were unlocked. Therefore, he called Cai’er over to ask.

Laura and the others didn’t know that the Space wasn’t upgraded. They were somewhat confused about Zhao Hai suddenly calling Cai’er.

After Cai’er came, Zhao Hai immediately asked, “Cai’er, how is the Space doing now?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, it’s doing great. The science and technology backgrounds have been unlocked. The Young Master can now buy ten backgrounds, but these could only be science and technology backgrounds.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s what I thought. Are these science and technology backgrounds useful?”

Cai’er smiled faintly and said, “Of course they’re useful, they’re very useful. Young Master doesn’t know about this. But at this time, you can only buy lesser science and technology backgrounds. In these backgrounds, there are some buildings that you can use. Once you buy a background, there would be things like gas manufacturing facilities and car making sites available.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai’s eyes immediately shone. This meant that buying a science and technology background was akin to buying technology. Means of making automobiles, mobile phones, and perhaps satellites would be available. All of these things were very useful for Zhao hai.

Take the present, for example. Zhao Hai’s means of communicating with Bingya and the others was through messenger fishes. If Zhao Hai could make mobile phones, then he could use those mobile phones to communicate, which was more convenient.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai said, “Cai’er, this science and technology background, what level of technology has it reached?”

Cai’er smiled faintly and said, “Lesser science and technology backgrounds can explore the universe!”

Zhao Hai’s expression lit up when he heard this. Exploring the universe was something that Earth’s technology has reached. If this was the case, then Zhao Hai would be gaining equivalent to ten Earth-like backgrounds.

Thinking about this made Zhao Hai laugh. However, Laura and the others were still quite confused. To be honest, they didn’t even understand what science and technology was, much less about exploring the universe.

After some time, Zhao Hai calmed down and immediately said, “Cai’er, I don’t think that those magic armors are only up to this level. Why can I only buy lesser science and technology backgrounds now?”

Zhao Hai can remember very clearly that although the Earth can explore the universe, it couldn’t make magic armors. Magic armors, or mechas as they were known on Earth, only appear on fantasy novels. Magic armors should be part of an advanced science and technology civilization.

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, you must know that magic armors aren’t purely mechanical constructs. In the innermost core of magic armors are magic formations. It can be said that magic armors are a combination between magic and technology. Because of this, you can only get the lowest type of science and technology background.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he nodded. Then he said, “How can we upgrade it?”

Cai’er replied, “Only after the Young Master manages to find products made by advanced level science and technology civilizations. Once the Young Master receives those products in the Space, the backgrounds would get upgraded.”

Zhao Hai then said, “How about the Universal Scanner?” Cai’er smiled and said, “The Young Master can find this out yourself. Put the Hell King’s ship in the Space and let the universal scanner analyze it.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He waved his hand and made the Hell King’s ship smaller before throwing it into the Space. After that, his magic staff increased in size as he stood on top of it along with Laura and the others.

While on the staff, the monitor showed Zhao Hai the scene with the Hell King’s ship. Since Zhao Hai cannot enter the Space, he can only use this method to observe.

After the ship entered the Space, it immediately flew towards the three-storied building. The door to the building opened automatically as the ship went in.

The monitor immediately showed the situation behind the door. What Zhao Hai saw inside was not what he expected. Zhao Hai thought that the three-story building was just one vacant room. Who would’ve thought that the small building was simply a huge machine!

Upon passing through the door, the Hell King’s ship descended to the ground. Then, that bright and clean floor suddenly turned into a transport belt, taking the ship around the room. As the ship went on, various lights were shining on top of it.

* * *

I think this George isn’t Mad Dog

Chapter 905: Modern Era Women

Those lights were scanning the Hell King’s ship. It took some time before the ship went through the building and went out on the other side.

Not only Zhao Hai, even Laura and the others were curiously looking at the monitor. They wanted to know what the Space would do.

At this time, a prompt came in, “Analysis starting. Analysis will take ten minutes.” Then a number appeared on a window of the building and started to count down.

Zhao Hai and the others weren’t anxious and just waited there. Ten minutes quickly went by. When the counter reached zero, a prompt was immediately heard, “Analysis complete. Item is an intermediate Cultivation Civilization weapon. Item has undergone an upgrade. Intermediate defense, intermediate attack, advanced speed. Materials used are golden sand, chaos crystal, iron essence, iron mother. On the hull are long-ranged magic cannons, weak attack. Improvements available, suggestions for improvements are…..”

Zhao Hai and the others were shocked as they listened to this prompt. In their eyes, the Hell King’s ship was already formidable. But after being analyzed, aside from its advanced speed, all other attributes were only intermediate. Moreover, this specific Hell King’s ship was an upgraded version of Lu Wei’s treasure ship. Even so, the scanner still had means to improve it. Wasn’t this ability too strong?”

While Zhao Hai was thinking about these, the Space’s prompt continued, “Host may improve the item using the Universal Processing Machine. After improvement, weapon speed will be increased by 20%, defensive strength by 40%, attacking strength by 40%, as well as magic cannon attack by 40%. Upgrade would need 1 million gold coins. Host would also need to provide goldmetal wood, innate yin fire, heart of earth fire, and 120 magic formations. Upgrade will take three hours.” After saying this, the Space didn’t say anything more. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai and the others were left standing there. They didn’t expect the Universal Scanner to be this useful.

After some time, Zhao Hai recovers as he laughed and said, “Good, very good. Immediately upgrade the Hell King’s ship. Transform according to the Universal Scanner’s recommendation.” With this order, the Hell King’s ship immediately flew towards the processing machine. A light shone on the ship before it disappeared.

When the Hell King’s ship disappeared into the processing machine, Zhao Hai turned and look at Laura and the others before laughing, “This time, we gained a very good treasure.”

Laura and the others were also very happy. Lizzy quickly said, “Brother Hai, didn’t Cai’er say that you can buy science and technology backgrounds? Go do it now, let’s see what they are.”

After being reminded by Lizzy, Zhao Hai remembered that they could also buy science and technology backgrounds. He immediately nodded and turned his head to Cai’er, “Cai’er, let’s see what science and technology backgrounds we can buy.”

Cai’er waved her small hand and the image on the monitor immediately changed to the store. There were small pictures on this page, and some of them were in black and white while some were colored. Zhao Hai understood that those in black and white were things he couldn’t buy. Some of the black and white pictures were from ordinary backgrounds and magic backgrounds. It looks like his level was insufficient to buy more of those. This time, the only thing he could buy were science and technology backgrounds.

Zhao Hai looked at these science and technology backgrounds. There were some hints on those images, however, those were just introduction and weren’t of much help for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai carefully scanned the backgrounds, carefully looking for the ten he would pick. However, this task wasn’t easy. These backgrounds numbered more than 100. Looking for something that suited him would not be a simple matter.

At the same time, Laura and the others were also looking at these backgrounds. Things on those images were something they had never seen before. There were over a hundred tall buildings, there were automobiles present. There were even things they couldn’t name, this caused them to be curious about those backgrounds.

Cai’er haven’t seen these things as well. However, she was tied together with the Space. Because of this, once the science and technology backgrounds were unlocked, she immediately got some information sent to her head.

It took half a day before Zhao Hai managed to pick ten backgrounds. Although Zhao Hai wants to live in a modern setting, it was a pity that he couldn’t enter the Space now. Because of this, he could only look at the monitor with envy.

Naturally, Laura and the others wanted to explore the backgrounds, and Zhao Hai didn’t stop them. He let Cai’er take Laura and the others for a tour and see what things lay inside those science and technology backgrounds.

After processing these matters, Zhao Hai turned his attention to George and the others. However, George’s team was already at the city, paying attention to the spatial rift. At this time, they didn’t have the intention to attack.

After seeing that George didn’t intend to attack now, Zhao Hai felt relief. He continued to sit on his transformed staff and calmly looked at the bustling army.

Fei’er and the others went back to their clans to prepare for the next battle against the O’Neal family. At the same time, Bingya and the others were at the defensive line. It was because of this that Zhao Hai had the confidence to send the Hell King’s ship for scanning.

Upon thinking of the Universal Scanner, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but feel hot. He immediately thought of things that the scanner can analyze. Can it scan the undead? After thinking of this, he immediately opened the monitor and made an undead enter the scanner.

The undead walked into the door of the building before a white light covered it. Then the undead became smaller and smaller until it reduced to the Hell King’s ship at that time. After that, it underwent the same process as the ship.

Zhao Hai stared blankly at the process. He didn’t expect that this would be the case. The scanner actually needed the subject to be small. It was too strange.

However, upon thinking that the scanner was the prize given by the Space and that these abilities were no big deal, Zhao Hai decided to not care about it anymore. What he wanted to know right now was the result of the scan done to the undead.

Once the undead came out of the back door, it immediately turned into its normal size.

After that, a prompt came, “Analysis starting. Analysis would take ten seconds.”

Ten, nine, eight, …”Analysis completed. Item is a robotic-type object. Item made from ordinary minerals. Attacking strength is weak. Item can be upgraded by the Space. Host is currently using the method of placing the item in the hell background in order to upgrade. This is the recommended method. An alternative method can use the Universal Processing Machine. Required materials are yin iron mother, golden sand, primal chaos crystal, a hundred thousand gold coins. Since Host can only provide golden sand, host can buy materials. After paying 5 million gold coins, the robot will be upgraded. After the upgrade, robot-like item will improve attack and defense by 200%. Note that after this improvement, robot can no longer be strengthened. Asking the host to think carefully.”

Zhao Hai blankly stared at the result. He didn’t expect the Space to have another means of upgrading the undead. But although the fast approach could improve the undead, Zhao Hai didn’t want to use it.

After seeing this result, Zhao Hai returned the undead to the hell background. Then he thought about the scorpio combat suit on his staff, so he had the scanner analyze it.

When the scorpio armor went to the back of the building, a prompt was heard, “Starting analysis program. This item is a defensive combat suit produced by the Space. Currently, the item is perfect. Host’s level is insufficient, Host is unable to improve it.”

Zhao Hai stared. He didn’t think that the scanner would have a high evaluation of the combat suit. However, if Zhao Hai were to think about it, he could understood what was going on. Now that the Space was making these combat suits, then it’s natural that they would be perfect. Moreover, if the combat suits could be upgraded right now, the processing machine wouldn’t be able to do it. Therefore, the analysis would give this answer.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before he had a domain weapon scanned. Zhao Hai had always wanted to improve the domain weapons for a while, but there was no time. Although the processing machine can improve items, it couldn’t compare to the scanner. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to see if the scanner would have any results regarding domain weapons.

The procedure went on as before, then a result came in, “Analysis results. Item is a rough and inferior level weapon. Weapon’s design is unreasonable, energy usage is too big. Attacking power is weak, defensive strength is weak, speed is weak. Materials used are ordinary. Host is recommended to destroy this weapon in order to get raw materials. Then Host can use the raw materials to make weapons or other items using the Universal Processing Machine.”

Zhao Hai felt depressed. Domain Weapons, both in the lower realms and in the Divine Realm, were extremely powerful items. Even in the Divine Realm where combat suits existed, warriors would still scamper around just to wield a domain weapon.

The result that the scanner brought up had no merit to speak of. Everything said about domain weapons were negative. Zhao Hai didn’t even know if there were any redeeming values.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he stored the domain weapon. He thought about it, if the scanner could tell the shortcomings of the Hell King’s ship, then the domain weapons naturally wouldn’t be spared.

The reason why the scanner didn’t have any means of improving the combat suit was because the combat suits were now a product of the Space. Once the Space levels-up, then it’s natural that the combat suits would follow. Because of this, the analysis didn’t say anything about improvement.

But still, the results of the scanner had aroused Zhao Hai’s interest. He immediately threw a magic armor towards the scanner. The procedure came in as a prompt came, “Analysis starting, time for analysis, 30 seconds.” After the timer finished, another prompt arrived, “Item is an armor type weapon made by a magic and science civilization. Attack strength is low, speed is low, defense is low. Unable to provide means of improvement due to the materials used.”

Zhao Hai gawked, he didn’t think that the result would be this. It seems like the scanner wasn’t all-purpose. It can only analyze items within the Space’s range, all other materials cannot be scanned.

One must know that Karen and the others were still trying to improve their magic formations in hope of using them for the magic armors in the future. However, the scanner actually can’t do this. It seems like talents were still needed during crucial moments.

At this time, Laura and the others walked out from the Space. To Zhao Hai’s surprise, each on of them had mobile phones on one hand while having laptops on the other. Their clothes were also from the modern era. If Zhao Hai didn’t know, he would’ve thought that he had returned back to Earth.

When Laura and the others saw Zhao Hai’s reaction, they couldn’t help but chuckle. After that, each one of them chirped about their adventures through the science and technology backgrounds.

Inside these science and technology backgrounds were these things called malls. These were the same malls that can be seen everywhere on Earth. Naturally, these malls had clothes, jewelry, and tech products. Since Cai’er had information about all of these, she introduced them to Laura and the others. Laura and the others were very curious about these things, so they took some phones and laptops along with clothes with them before going out of the Space.

Of course they didn’t forget about Zhao Hai. When they came out, they also gave Zhao hai a mobile phone and laptop.

Laura thought that Zhao Hai was also clueless about mobile phones and laptops, so when she took out the phone she said, “Brother Hai, look. Come here, let me teach you. With this thing, you wouldn’t be using messenger fishes anymore.” Then she proceeded to hand a phone to Zhao Hai and explained its functions.

Zhao Hai looked strangely at Laura, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, can we use these things here?”

Chapter 906: Mysterious Hell King’s Ship

Cai’er nodded and said, “These mobile phones can be used in any backgrounds inside the Space. If outside, it can only work in an area 10 thousand meters around Young Master. Beyond this range, the phones cannot be used.”

Zhao Hai nodded, the current monitor also has a range of 10 thousand meters with him as the center. It seems like because of its relationship with the Space, the mobile phones can also work on the same range.

Zhao Hai looked at the mobile phone in his hand. He couldn’t see what brand it was, but it was beautiful. There weren’t a lot of buttons on the device. Aside from normal buttons on typical mobile phones, there weren’t anything else. The screen was very large, black, and simple.

Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod before pressing the power button. The screen of the phone immediately lit up. It had a different boot animation from the other phones that Zhao Hai had seen before. Once the phone was turned on, the boot animation was a farm, then the farm slowly disappeared into a background of a clear sky, white clouds, and green grass. At the same time, an image of an ordinary home screen appeared.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied of this mobile phone. During his time on Earth, he had used a lot of mobile phones. He could say that there wasn’t any phone like this one.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at Laura and said, “Laura, what is your number?”

Laura and the others were looking blankly at Zhao Hai’s movements. Zhao Hai looked more skilled than them when using the phone, looking like it wasn’t his first time using it. This made them puzzled. Now that Laura heard Zhao Hai, she immediately gave him her phone number.

Once he heard the number, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It was because Laura’s number didn’t have 11 digits, instead it only had 7. The number belonged to a phone that wasn’t upgraded.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t care. He conveniently dialed Laura’s number on his phone. It didn’t take long before a delightful sound was heard, it was Laura’s phone that made the sound.

Laura took her phone out and saw Zhao Hai’s number plastered on the screen.

Zhao Hai looked at his number and almost gasped. Goodness, this number was too overbearing, 6-1-1. This was the first time Zhao Hai saw this number on a phone.

Zhao Hai looked at his number and said, “You didn’t get to choose your numbers? You need to have one like this.” Then he referred to his mobile number. The number that Laura had wasn’t very easy to memorize, being seven numbers.

When Laura heard Zhao Hai say this, she smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine, it looks interesting this way. Right, Brother Hai, how are you able to use mobile phones?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t forget, I’m the Host. It wouldn’t be strange for me to use mobile phones comfortably.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others nodded. Naturally, Zhao Hai cannot tell them that he was from Earth. This was his deepest secret, and he wasn’t prepared to tell anybody yet.

Zhao Hai saved Laura’s number. The phone could also take pictures, so he took Laura’s picture to save with the phone number.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai skillfully using the phone, Laura and the others couldn’t help but surround him. This way, Zhao Hai could help them get used to the phone.

Zhao Hai didn’t decline and saved everybody’s number on his phone. Then everybody took everybody else’s pictures.

Seeing Laura and the others happily playing around with their phones, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. Actually, Laura was still quite young at 20 years old. Meanwhile, Meg and Ni’er were the youngest being 18 years old. Back on Earth, women of their age would still be thinking about what to wear when they go out, they would still be quarelling with their boyfriends. On the other hand, Laura and the others were currently working like mature women, the disparity was too big.

Seeing the women play around with their phones, Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them. He can understand their current mood, he was the same with his very first mobile phone. He even couldn’t sleep the following night, he was much worse than Laura and the others.

Zhao Hai took the laptop that Laura handed him and confidently opened it. The inside was the same as any other computer. But unlike the one he had on Earth, this laptop didn’t have as much programs installed. There were only default programs and it didn’t even have a way to connect to the internet.

Zhao Hai then asked Cai’er who was sitting on his shoulder, “Cai’er, what other programs are installed in this computer?”

Cai’er replied, “Young Master, aren’t these the only ones needed to be installed? Right, I also saved information about magic formations on this computer.”

Zhao Hai also remembered that although he now has a computer, his situation still wasn’t the same as back on Earth. There was no internet here so he couldn’t just surf the web freely.

Only then did Zhao Hai nod and said, “How did you solve the problem of electric power?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master can rest assured. I have prepared a lot of solar panels so that we can charge the phones and laptops.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. Right, prepare to give father-in-law some of these laptops. The computers would surely help with their research on magic formations.” Cai’er immediately complied.

At this time, a prompt was heard from the Space., “Hell King’s ship modification finished. Asking Host for permission to summon.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he quickly said, “Summon.” Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the Hell King’s ship appeared right in front of him. Zhao Hai inspected the ship and couldn’t see any obvious change. It didn’t look different than before. This confused Zhao Hai.

Laura and the others had also discovered that Zhao Hai had summoned the Hell King’ ship. Since he couldn’t see anything different with the ship, he Zhao Hai immediately went in.

But the moment he made the ship move, it was then that Zhao Hai felt the difference.

In the past, when the ship started to move, it would undergo the process of acceleration. In other words, the ship wasn’t fast in the beginning. Only after a few seconds would it reach its quickest speed.

But now it was different. As long as Zhao Hai made the ship move, it immediately reached its maximum velocity. Moreover, the ship was steady and more flexible. When the Hell King’s ship moved, magic formations would appear on its sides, almost covering the entire ship. In turn, this made the ship look more mysterious.

Zhao Hai tried moving the ship a few more times. He can now assure that the ship had become more flexible. In the past, due to the ship’s speed, turning would be very difficult, you would need to make a huge bend. Currently, the ship would immediately turn when Zhao Hai issued his command. The ship was now more like a fish swimming in the sea.

Besides its speed, the Hell King’s ship’s attacking power has also been improved. In the past, the ship’s ram wasn’t too agile when attacking the enemy, it wasn’t the same case now. The pole and the magic cannons were also similar. Zhao Hai tried them and knew that the ship’s fighting strength had indeed been promoted.

At the same time, although the Hell King’s ship’s water didn’t look like it changed, Zhao Hai could see the changes once he commanded it to move. The water of the new Hell King’s ship now had more volume in every action it made. Now, the water underneath the ship would roll with each action. Magic formations would also appear with each action, aiding the water to keep rotating in place. One could see at a glance that this was much better compared to before.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with the changes to the Hell King’s ship. After testing, he led Laura and the others to enter their room. There were no major changes made in their cabin, but it became larger than before, it was now like a small Space.

Zhao Hai liked the recent changes. After returning to their room, Zhao Hai immediately turned the monitor on to see the situation with the O’Neal family.

George’s letter had yet to be delivered to the O’neal family, so Zhao Hai still wasn’t clear of their reaction. But since the reinforcements had yet to come, it can be said that George wouldn’t make a step further into the rift.

This made Zhao Hai relieved. What he needed to do right now was to wait for the news coming from the foreign races. As long as they can drag the Divines for a while, then Zhao Hai can be sure to upturn the Divine Race’s continents.

At this point, nearly 10 thousand Devil Legion soldiers were fitted with scorpio combat suits. They were still adapting to the combat suit but Zhao Hai could see that their combat power seemed to be inferior compared to the Divines.

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind once he understood why. The Devil Legion were already inferior in strength compared to the Supreme Elders. At the same time, the Supreme Elders wouldn’t be able to use the combat suits for a long time since it consumed too much of their energy.

The Space may have thought of this shortcoming when it transformed the combat suit into a seed. Right now, these combat suits were unable to exert as much power as the ones the Divines had. This was not only due to their wearer being weaker, it also came due to the changes made to the combat suits. In return for its reduced performance, Zhao Hai’s combat suits didn’t have the same side effect as the ones the Divines had.

One could say that the combat suit in the hands of the Supreme Elders was just like giving a three-year old child am 18 jin sledgehammer. Even if the child was quite strong, it would still be exhausted after using the sledgehammer for a few times.

Zhao Hai’s combat suits didn’t have such a weak point. His combat suits were more like clothes than a heavy weapon. If in the hands of a child, the combat suit would just be like a small stick. Only when yielded by an adult would the combat suit become the best weapons.

Chapter 907: Can It Be A Trap?

After thinking through this point, Zhao Hai moved on. Although the Devil Legion couldn’t reach the strength of the Supreme Elders in a short time, he was still very happy.

Zhao Hai could understand that a hundred birds in the forest was still not as good as a single bird on one’s hand. Although the Devil Legion with combat suits were inferior compared to the Supreme Elders, the strength of the Devil Legion was still greatly improved. To Zhao Hai, this was already enough.

Zhao Hai regarded the Devil Legion to be important. Their potential couldn’t be measured. If the Devil Legion suffered any side effects when using the combat suits, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t deploy them. Although they were weaker than the Supreme Elders, at the very least Zhao Hai could still use them.

At this time, Zhao Hai wanted to find weapons that could be used by the undead. He wanted the undead to increase in strength.

However, Zhao Hai had yet to find an appropriate weapon for them. Originally, Zhao Hai planned the undead to join the Devil Legion and be equipped by combat suits. However, the amount of combat suits needed would be enormous. Zhao Hai might not be able to afford it. Because of this, Zhao Hai can only delay this matter to a later time.

Three days later, Zhao Hai was still observing the situation with the O’neal family. George travelled too far this time, so it wasn’t so easy to send the letter back to the family. Three days have passed but the letter had yet to arrive. However, Zhao Hai had no time to consider this right now. Bingya just came to Zhao Hai bearing news, the Divines had sent their troops!

The Divines were now heading out with their army but had yet to make contact with the foreign races. However, Zhao Hai understood that he now has to make preparations. After sending Bingya away, Zhao Hai sat inside his room, staring at the O’Neal family. He didn’t move for half a day.

Laura and the others were sitting next to each other as the fiddled around with their laptops. After learning how to use it, they had come to like the computers. Although there weren’t any games installed, the machine was still able to make things convenient for them.

In the past few days, Laura and the others were busy trying to import their materials to the computer. This wasn’t a simple job. The information they gathered up to this point was a lot. Just trying to sort through the information would take quite a while.

At the same time, Zhao Hai was currently thinking about how to tackle the Divine Race, and find a way for the Divines to be unable to deal with him. The Divines now had some sort of understanding regarding Zhao Hai’s strength. It wouldn’t be good for Zhao Hai if the Divines had prepared something for him.

However, whether the situation was good or not, Zhao Hai still needed to make a move. The Divines were faithful dogs of Lu Wei, they needed to be cleaned up.

When facing the other nine continents, Zhao Hai needed to pick which one to attack first. After Zhao Hai attacks, he would immediately attract the attention of the Divines. The Divines would then retreat. And by then, Zhao Hai needed to solve the encirclement of the Divines.

Zhao Hai was currently suspecting that this large Divine Race army wouldn’t have any Supreme Elders with them. Bingya’s report that said they would send 7 Supreme Elders might be false information that the Divines deliberately released.

The Divines released this information so that Zhao Hai would be compelled to attack the Divines. They might be preparing an ambush there, waiting for Zhao Hai to bite the bait.

If this was the case, then the discussion made by Elder Star that time might have been intentionally made in order for Zhao Hai to listen in.

Upon thinking about this, Zhao Hai’s brain couldn’t help but run faster and faster. Every single fight Zhao Hai had with the Divine Race were won with the help of the Space. It would be acceptable if the Supreme Elders were to find something out. Although they might not know about the Space, they still should have noticed that Zhao Hai had special methods of finding things out. Therefore, Elder Star might have deliberately discussed their plan for Zhao Hai. Meanwhile, they would stage an ambush in the Divine Race territory.

Attacking an enemy’s rear in order to compel them to retreat. This might be a simple statement but it was something that everyone understood. Elder Star and the others couldn’t contend with Zhao Hai even if there were five of them. But now, they decided to leave two Supreme Elders to defend their rear? This was completely unreasonable. Because of this, they could be waiting in the Divine Race territory for Zhao Hai to sneak attack. At the same time, they wanted Zhao Hai to believe that they were attacking the foreign races.

The more he thought about this, the more it seemed true. Zhao Hai’s fight with the Divines didn’t only take one or two days. Although most of the Divines they defeated had been thrown to the Space, it was difficult for all the fishes to be captured by the net. At this time, information about Zhao Hai should have come out. Thunder Yun used an all out attack before in order to deal with Zhao Hai. At that time, Zhao Hai attacked the Radiant Church, causing the Divine army to be in chaos. Because of this, Thunder Yun drew back, incurring heavy losses along the way.

With such losses, the Divines certainly wouldn’t fall for it a second time. For the Divines to use the same method right now would be too strange.

After thinking up to here, Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, this attack towards the foreign races, can it be a trap?”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Lizzy couldn’t help but frown. After a moment she said, “It’s possible. If that is really the case, then we would meet trouble when we attack the Divines. Brother Hai, how about we directly deal with the Divine Race army.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No need. Now that the Divines had lost one Supreme Elder, they should also understand that if the Elders were to be separated, then they would only be dealt with. Therefore, the Supreme Elders could only lay in ambush inside the Divine Race territory. With them being together, this might also be an opportunity for us.” Lizzy thought for a moment and said, “But at this time, the Divines have 9 continents. How will we know which one they had set a trap in?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That is not important. The Divines had been the overlord for many years, so they should have a very firm foundation. The Radiant Church had a few pieces of spatial items, so the Divine should have some as well. If they have a weapon that can allow them to travel from continent to continent, then choosing which continent wouldn’t be a problem. Although we haven’t seen the Divines use such things before, that doesn’t mean that they didn’t have them. Don’t forget, our enemy is  Lu Wei. Even if the Divines don’t have such items, then Lu Wei might have some. Lu Wei’s avatars have been destroyed by me twice. He hates me. I don’t know why he didn’t descend anymore, but with his status he shouldn’t let this enmity go. He can use the Divines instead in order to deal with me.”

When Lizzy and the others heard this, their expressions couldn’t help but sink. Their faces weren’t attractive. Lu Wei was their archenemy, and he worries them. If not because of Lu Wei, then they wouldn’t have this much trouble living.

Laura said, “Brother Hai, so what do we do now? Do we just let them ambush us?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Correct. Even if we know about the ambush, we still need to push on. We need to make the Divines know that no ambush can deal with us.”

Laura looked puzzled at Zhao Hai as she asked, “Brother Hai, what do you mean?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Now that the Hell King’s ship has been upgraded, its speed had become much quicker. It’s impossible for them to overtake the Hell King’s ship before, much less now. In any case, the war had begun. We don’t need to be polite. It would be better for the war to end as soon as possible.”

Laura and the others nodded, then Laura said, “Brother Hai, if Lu Wei gave the Divines a weapon, then wouldn’t it be dangerous for us?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Even if Lu Wei gave them a powerful weapon, they still need to be able to use it. If they couldn’t, then that weapon would just be useless. Lu Wei already managed to give us two items. If he gave the Divines some items, then who would use it? Hehe, don’t worry about it.”

Lizzy nodded. Then she said, “Big Brother Hai, so which continent are you planning to attack?’

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Central Continent.”

This answer made Lizzy gawk. She was puzzled as she asked, “The Central Continent? That is very far from here. If we attack the Central Continent, then we would be very deep into the Divine Race’s sphere of influence. Wouldn’t that be dangerous?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “If you thought about that, then the Divine should be the same, everyone would think the same. Because of that, the Central Continent would have the most lax defenses. Although the Divines treated all continents equally aside from the ones controlled by the foreign races, one could see that the Central Continent is the foremost continent of them all.”

Lizzy thought about it for a moment and said, “So it’s like this. In the previous battle, it also looks like the other Supreme Elders are listening to the Central Continent’s Supreme Elder. If that is the case, then attacking the Central Continent would be a good choice. Once we succeed, then we can eliminate the Divines bit by bit.”

At this point, Lizzy and the others weren’t afraid of Ultimate Weapons. However, they were also clear that if Zhao Hai were to go all out in fighting the Divines, then he would immediately ascend. This would leave the Divine Realm in an awful mess. Most importantly, they would get to meet Lu Wei much earlier than they anticipated.

Because of this, they can only do as they planned. As much as possible, they wouldn’t let Zhao Hai make a move. They needed to defeat the Divine Race little by little!

Chapter 908: Sneaking on the Seabed

To deal with the enemy, one shouldn’t be merciful. One must find their life point and strike a heavy blow on it. And where was the Divine Race’s core? Where do they think it was safe?

The only answer to the question was the Central Continent. This sounds credible, and in fact the Central Continent had always been a special existence in the Divine Realm. And it wasn’t only  because of its location and ultimate weapon.

The Central Continent was placed in the exact middle of  the Divine Realm. At the same time, their ultimate weapon was the most handy weapon in the Divine Race. Because of this, the Central Continent had a different status compared to the other continents in the Divine Realm. Most people in the Divine Realm looked at those living in the Central Continent with respect.

In fact, the reason why the Central Continent has such a position was due to their ultimate weapon. Their ultimate weapon had a certain restraint on the other ultimate weapons. If Gold Ben and Elder Star were to fight, then Elder Star’s ultimate weapon would be able to suppress Gold Ben’s combat suit. Gold Ben could only fight with 80% of his strength while Elder Star would be strengthened to 120%. This difference could spell the fate of any battle.

The reason the Divines were yet to deal with the foreign races was because the foreign races’ Supreme Elders didn’t dare to face Elder Star. The three Supreme Elders knew that Elder Star was able to suppress their power, therefore, every time they wage war with the Divines, they always make sure to not face Elder Star.

Moreover, the three Supreme Elders generally acted together while also fighting with the Divine Supreme Elders as little as possible. Just like Zhao Hai’s approach, the three Supreme Elders would make an attack on the rear once the Divine Army attacks. Because of this, the Divines had no way to deal with the foreign races. Although the three foreign races suffered losses, they could still persist for many years.

It was because of the Central Continent’s special status that the foreign races didn’t attack it despite repeatedly attacking the other continents. Due to this, the Central Continent was able to develop quite well over the years. It had the largest population and the strongest fighting power. This added to its special status as the central location of the Divine Realm.

Zhao Hai was now heading to the Central Continent. He now suspects that the Divines might be waiting there for him, staging an ambush. Although he has to find a way to deal with them, he still didn’t think about changing his plan.

If Zhao Hai attacked the Divine Race army and he saw the Supreme Elders there, then it only meant that they didn’t stage an ambush. If that was true, then Zhao Hai would have to smack himself in the head.

When that time comes, the initiative would fall into the hands of the Divines. This wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to see.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to go on with his plan. While the Divines dispatched their army to the foreign races, he would go and attack the Divine Race territory. In the past, Zhao Hai planned to deal with the outside continents, but now he decided to head directly to the Central Continent.

Wasn’t the Central Continent the strongest? If that was the case, then they needed to be defeated to serve as an example. Let’s see how the Divines rescue themselves then.

After making up his mind, Zhao Hai left the defensive line to Fei’er and the others. After that, he took Bingya and the others prepared to leave.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about leaving Fei’er and the others behind. After all, the spatial rift was quite large. It would be impossible for the O’neal family to muster up enough forces to claim the entire area. Zhao Hai also left magic cannons and undead behind. And if needed, he could still provide help. There shouldn’t be any problems in the defensive line.

After talking things over with Fei’er and the others, Zhao Hai proceeded to leave the Taurus Continent. But this time, they didn’t fly in the sky, that would be too revealing. Zhao Hai believed that even if the Divines were attacking the foreign races, they would still pay attention to the Taurus Continent. If the Divines discover that Zhao Hai was heading out, then they might make arrangements in advance. There was no need for Zhao Hai to make things harder for himself.

Because of this, Zhao Hai immediately released Bubble upon leaving the Taurus Continent. Bubble wrapped the Hell King’s ship as it entered the seabed before heading towards the Central Continent.

This was exactly what Zhao Hai wanted. Bubble was the source of myriad water. He was just like any other drop of water in the sea. Even if the Divines were powerful, it would still be impossible for them to distinguish the difference between two drops of water. Because of this, there wouldn’t be any problems with Bubble traversing the sea. Additionally, Bubble was very fast. Zhao Hai just sat on the ship’s deck and watched the surrounding waters.

Actually, the seascape before Zhao Hai was fairly the same as the ones back in the Ark Continent. After seeing this scenery for a long time before, Zhao Hai was already quite tired of it.

At this time, Zhao Hai was looking at a map stretched on a table. This map was provided by Bingya and the others, it showed the general layout of the Divine Realm.

Laura and the others were also present and were looking at the map. On the other hand, Bingya and the others were focused on looking around them. They looked like countrymen who never managed to see the world before.

While looking at the map, Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. The map was too crude, it didn’t even have a scale. There weren’t even sea landmarks shown. For Zhao Hai, the map wasn’t really that great.

Zhao Hai looked at the map for some time. But after understanding nothing, he decided to give up. He turned to Bingya and the others, who were still enthralled with their surroundings, and said, “Bingya, are you sure that our current direction isn’t wrong? Will we really arrive at the Central Continent this way?”

It was at this time that Bingya recovered. His admiration towards Zhao Hai had become very high. Zhao Hai could actually traverse the seabed. Moreover, the numerous aquatic magic beasts didn’t even attack them. It seems like the ship didn’t exist. This move by Zhao Hai made him feel shocked.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Bingya immediately said, “Mister, there shouldn’t be any mistakes. If we don’t deviate from our heading, then we will surely arrive at the Central Continent.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He wasn’t worried much about deviating from the Central Continent. Others might deviate from going at a straight line, but Bubble wouldn’t.

Zhao Hai also looked at the aquatic magic beasts. He understood why these beasts didn’t attack them. It was all due Bubble. Bubble was the sea, and the sea was Bubble. Have you seen aquatic magic beasts attacking the sea? Therefore, these magic beasts naturally wouldn’t attack Zhao Hai.

Laura and the others continued to study the map for a longer while. In the end, they gave up. Lizzy rolled the map and lobbed it over to Bingya before she said, “I really doubt that you managed to defend your domains with such a map. Can that be really used for war?”

When Bingya and the others heard Lizzy, their face couldn’t help but turn red. They didn’t dare to refute. The reason for this was because they saw Zhao Hai’s map of the Taurus Continent. This map was something Zhao Hai had Cai’er make. The Space’s ability to analyze was very high, moreover, there were scales and all landmarks could be seen.

When Bingya and the others saw that map, they couldn’t help but get shocked. They didn’t expect that such a map would exist. They could read the map very clearly, the cities were depicted very well. This was another aspect that made them admire Zhao Hai.

Therefore, when Lizzy criticized their map, Bingya couldn’t refute. Their map was too inferior, he would just shame himself if he were to defend it.

….

Sailing underwater was actually very interesting. One could see all kinds of plants and animals in the sea. One would feel like they were sent to another world.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t idle all this time. He was currently in his room paying attention to the O’neal family. It was early morning and the O’Neal family had started to receive the letter that was sent by Penny. When the discovery of the Demon Realm was announced, the people from the O’Neal family couldn’t help but feel wild with joy.

The O’Neal family invaded the Ark Continent because of resources. At this time, the O’neal family had managed to discover a lot of minerals in the Ark Continent. This information made them feel ecstatic. And now, there was actually another plane connected to the Ark Continent and wasn’t any smaller in comparison. For the O’Neal family, this was an unexpectedly good news.

But at the same time, when the report came to the part where Penny discovered the undead and iron armor beasts, the Patriarch of the O’Neal family couldn’t help but flinch. In his opinion, they needed to obtain the resources in the Ark Continent and the Demon Realm.  They might encounter war with this result but they were already prepared for this.

Their reaction was completely seen by Zhao Hai. To be honest, Zhao Hai had expected this. Zhao Hai had long known why the O’Neal family invaded the Ark Continent. Their current reaction was just confirming what he knew.

Zhao Hai was prepared to withdraw the magic beasts and the undead from the Demon Realm. In any case, the Space wasn’t lacking in metals right now. There was no need to mine for more.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai thought of another way of acquiring ore, that was to rob. Didn’t the O’Neal family want to mine the ores? Then Zhao Hai might as well have them mine it. After they got the ores, then Zhao Hai would sweep in and take it for himself.

Zhao Hai had long planned to do this. He was never polite to his foes. Since the O’Neal family were now his enemies, then he would have to be impolite.

The third day after Zhao Hai entered the sea, George’s letter was finally delivered to the O’Neal Patriarch’s desk. After looking at the letter, the O’Neal Patriarch’s heart couldn’t help but race.

From the Atlanta Plane to the Ark Continent, everything for the O’Neal family had gone smoothly. They didn’t find any enemies and they even found so many minerals. Additionally, there was even an additional plane. The only thing that was bugging the O’Neal family’s mind was where the people of the Ark Continent moved.

The disappearance of the people from the Ark Continent was an extremely huge mystery. If they couldn’t discover the reason, then this would only be an ongoing threat. Now, they had finally ran into an enemy. The O’Neal family Patriarch believed that the enemy that George had ran into was related to the Ark Continent’s people!

Chapter 909: We’ve Gone Astray?

The current pressure on the O’Neal Family has been great recently. There was the disappearance of the Ark Continent’s people as well as the slowly encroaching innate yin domain. Although the innate yin domain wasn’t very fast, a day would come that the O’Neal family would need to face it. The most troublesome thing was that the innate yin domain was too big. It wouldn’t be very easy to deal with it.

The disappearance of the people from the Ark Continent wasa huge mystery. This has become a hidden threat to the O’Neal Family. The O’Neal Patriarch needed to keep this thing in mind at all times.

The O’Neal family had already invested too much in the Ark Continent. They had already discovered minerals in the Ark Continent, something that they needed in the very beginning. But at the same time, this was the exact reason why the Patriarch couldn’t help but worry. He was very eager to know why the people of the Ark Continent decided to move, and where they went to.

George’s report to the family was a crucial one. An unseen enemy was the most dangerous. Once you can make clear of your enemies, only then can you make countermeasures to defeat them. When he read George’s report, the Patriarch couldn’t help but feel excited. Even if they had suffered some losses, these were unimportant to the Patriarch.

When he read this information, the Patriarch immediately called for the family’s generals. He arranged for people to go and assist George’s team.

George needed to be reinforced. After all, the enemy has been spotted. Moreover, the O’Neal family was still clueless about what was behind that spatial rift.

Penny also needed support. There were a lot of mines in the Demon Realm and these mines were being worked on by the undead and iron armor beasts. To the O’Neal Patriarch, this was an unacceptable thing. Those mines already belong to the O’Neal family. Anyone who wanted to touch their property would be provoking the family.

Zhao Hai was also paying attention to the response of the O’Neal family. He expected this reaction, but also didn’t think that they would reinforce the Demon Realm. When this happened, Zhao Hai immediately withdrew his undead and iron armor beasts. Zhao Hai only left a few undead in the Demon Realm in order to attract more attention from the O’Neal family.

Zhao Hai did this in order to reduce the pressure on his defensive line in the Divine Realm. Additionally, this would also make the O’Neal family think that the undead only had to do with the Demon Realm.

The Hell King’s ship was still traversing the seas. One could see new sceneries every minute. Even if these sceneries weren’t that attractive to Zhao Hai, they also weren’t annoying to look at. The group has been living comfortably in the past few days.

However, Zhao Hai also found out that the Divines were a bit smarter than he expected them to be. They had also arranged for people to monitor the seas. It was just because they didn’t go too deep that they failed to discover Zhao Hai.

The Ark Continent had the Fishman race, so the Divine Realm would surely have them as well. However, the Fishman race of the Divine Realm wasn’t a single power. In the Ark Continent, the Fishman race has been under the control of the Mermaid Race, an independent entity. On the other hand, the Fishman Race of the Divine Realm were under the control of the Divines that were nearest to them. Because of this, the Divine Realm’s Fishman race has been divided into 13 clans.

Naturally Zhao Hai didn’t know about this, it was Bingya who told him. Bingya was able to come in contact with these Fishmen before, so he managed to find things out about them.

Although Zhao Hai had been at sea for several days, his communication with Fei’er and the others didn’t get interrupted. Moreover, Zhao Hai even told Fei’er about the O’Neal family’s situation in order to have them prepare.

Another two days passed by, but Zhao Hai felt that they were still on the same state. According to Bingya’s map, if they really were going on a straight line, then they should be close to the Central Continent judging by their speed.

Zhao Hai walked out from his room and saw Bingya and the others still looking at everything they passed by. Zhao Hai knew that Bingya was also thinking the same thing as him.

Zhao Hai looked at the expression of the three and smiled, “What? Are you worried? Don’t worry, we’ll go up soon to see where we are.” After that, Zhao Hai directed the ship to slowly head up.

Actually, Zhao Hai already looked at the monitor and saw that there weren’t any Fishmen around. Only then did he decide to go into the surface.

Zhao Hai had the ship shrink while still being wrapped by Bubble. They needed to bring the least attention to them as possible.

After Zhao Hai and the others emerged on the surface, they saw a piece of land in the distance. With how large that landmass was, it couldn’t be an island, but a continent instead.

Zhao Hai turned to Bingya and said, “Is that the Central Continent?”

Bingya smiled bitterly as he shook his head. The Foreign Races knew very little about the Central Continent since none of them had gone there before. They had been isolated by the Divine Race for so long.

After seeing Bingya’s appearance, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything more. He smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine if you don’t know. Bubble, go back down first and proceed slowly. Find a large body of water, maybe a river. Let’s go see which continent we’ve bumped into. It would be best if that is the Central Continent.”

Bubble complied before diving down once more. To be honest, Bubble was very glad to do this. He was always comfortable around bodies of water. He was the same back at the Space. He would only stay on places with water, never any other place. Not like Cai’er who always flew from one place to another.

At this time, Laura and the others were still together inside the room. Bingya and the others couldn’t understand why the women kept themselves in all the time. They were able to stay there for days on end. Bingya and the others even thought that Zhao Hai’s group had been doing shameful things inside their room.

However, ever since Bingya entered Zhao Hai’s room, they completely dropped this idea. To be honest, if they were given the same room, they could also stay there for days at a time.

Bubble moved for two hours before reaching the shore. The shores of the continent looked very lively, Zhao Hai could even see some Fishmen swimming around while ships were coming and going.

But none of those people managed to spot Zhao Hai and the others. Bubble couldn’t be easily seen in his own habitat.

Bubble followed Zhao Hai’s instruction and investigated the shore. He was feeling for a current of water and headed towards it. Before long, he entered the riverbed.

Zhao Hai and the others don’t know much about this river. However, this river was indeed depp. Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to shrink the Hell King’s ship before entering, but Bubble stopped him from doing it.

Zhao Hai asked Bubble why this was the case and Bubble said that his own body can shrink just like the Hell King’s ship. Those inside Bubble’s body would be subjected to the Space inside. Although Bubble had shrunk, the ship still remained its original size.

It was at this moment that Zhao Hai remembered the time where he got Bubble in the Northern Icefield. Bubble was able to absorb a lot of things into his own body. Moreover, Bubble’s size remained the same regardless of the size of the item. The Hell King’s ship wouldn’t be a problem for Bubble.

After listening to Bubble, Zhao Hai decided to go along with it and had Bubble go into the big river. Upon entering the river, Zhao Hai suddenly had the feeling about its importance to this continent. This was because he saw how much ships were coming and going in this river. What surprised Zhao Hai the most was the presence of Fishmen on this river.

The Fishmen were working here. They rode their magic beasts here and there, helping the ships dock as well as transporting freight. They were busily going about their jobs.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai said, “Bubble, go towards that port. Let’s listen to their conversation.” Bubble complied and slowly floated up. This caused Bingya and the others to get nervous. They still had no idea that they had shrunk right now.

Before long, Bubble had floated to the river’s surface. They were several meters away from the port. Although they weren’t near the riverside, the distance still allowed them to hear conversation.

The hubbub of shouting and haggling was easily heard, the voices of many people mixed with each other. There weren’t too much useful information but Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. He just kept listening in for keywords that might be useful. In the end, they managed to hear some names of the cities.

Upon hearing the city names, Bingya and the others couldn’t help but change their expression. Bingya turned to Zhao Hai and said, “I’ve wronged Mister. We have reached the wrong place. This isn’t the Central Continent but Leo Continent. If we head east, we should arrive at the Central Continent.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He couldn’t blame Bingya and the others. After all, the Divine Realm’s map making technology wasn’t that great. It’s completely reasonable for the maps to deviate by a few degrees.

Zhao Hai turned to Bingya and asked, “How many days will it take?”

Bingya paused before saying, “With our speed, we should be there in three days. I’m sure of it this time”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Bubble, I’ll leave it to you. We need to reach the Central Continent in three days.” Bubble complied and sank to the river’s bottom before going towards the sea at full speed and then heading east.

The reason why Zhao Hai let Bubble wrap them wasn’t because the ship couldn’t travel underwater. Instead, it was because Bubble doesn’t cause any ripples when traversing the sea. This was something that the Hell King’s ship couldn’t do.

Chapter 910: Along the River, Through the Center

Three days quickly went past. But in these three days, the O’Neal family weren’t idling. Their reinforcements had entered the Radiant Empire while another had reached the Buddha Empire to reinforce the Demon Realm’s troops.

However, Zhao Hai was already prepared for these two situations. As long as he can connect himself with Fei’er, then everything would be fine. There would be no need for him to manage things at this point.

After three days, Zhao Hai and the others has yet again resurfaced to see a piece of land, a continent. This time, Bubble didn’t need Zhao Hai’s instruction as he sank back down and looked for a river to enter into the continent.

Bubble initially wanted to find a small stream to enter, but Zhao Hai instructed him to find a large river instead. They would enter the continent through that big river.

After entering, Zhao Hai found a place with a lot of people in order to listen to conversation. After listening for a while, he finally was able to hear several names. When he heard these names, Bingya immediately turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, there’s no mistake. This is the Central Continent. Do we make a move now?”

After hearing the confirmation from Bingya, Zhao Hai smiled but shook his head as he said, “Don’t worry about it. But if we act now, our harvests wouldn’t be too big.”

Bingya looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Did you know why I made Bubble look for a big river to enter the Central Continent?’

Bingya shook his head. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s because great rivers are lifelines to any civilization. If we enter a small river, then we might not reach too far into the continent. But if we enter a big river, then it’s possible that we can enter the middle of the continent stealthily.”

“We need to attack important cities. And if we can attack their capital city, then that would even be more perfect. What result would we have if we settle on small cities? In addition to not affecting their system, they can also react immediately and encircle us. On the other hand, if we attack their important cities, then how much damage would we cause?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Bingya and the others paused for a moment before their eyes shone.

Bingya laughed as he said, “Mister, the heavens are truly helping you. The Central Continent’s Capital City isn’t too far from its largest river. Even ordinary magic beasts would take a few days of travel. It would take much less if we fly. If the river we going into was Divine Gift River, then we can immediately go to the capital, Central City.”

Zhao Hai didn’t know about this matter. Now that he heard Bingya, he immediately became interested, “Bingya, is that true? Then we should head there.’

Bingya smiled and said, “Mister shouldn’t worry about this. Central City has four satellite cities outside. Divine Gift City is right next to Divine Gift River. As long as we get to Divine Gift City through the river, then we can directly head to Central City.”

Zhao Hai’s expression shook, he nodded and said, “Alright, then that would be the best. Bubble, don’t go back down, we need to pay attention to things on shore.” Bubble complied and moved forward along the river. Their speed actually slowed down as they payed attention to the things on shore.

Zhao Hai wanted to pay attention because; one, he wanted to find Divine Gift City, and second, he wanted to see if the Central Continent was prepared. If the Central Continent had made preparations, then Zhao Hai would have trouble advancing. But if they didn’t, then everything would be fine.

Although Zhao Hai and the others were thinking that they weren’t going fast, they were already very quick compared to the ships in their vicinity. Very soon, Zhao Hai and the others were ways long the river. In the process, they had also confirmed that they were in Divine Gift River. This discovery made Zhao Hai glad. This time, they weren’t on the wrong path.

Every time they met a city, they would stop to listen for a while and see if they had reached Divine Gift City. However, they were quickly disappointed, they had yet to reach Divine Gift City.

Upon arriving in the Central Continent, Bingya and the others could no longer offer Zhao Hai any help. This was because they had never been to the Central Continent before. Therefore, they had very limited information regarding its geography.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t want to make any wrong moves at this time. Because of this, he asked Laura and the others to head back to their room and look at the monitor. As long as they reach Divine Gift City, they would immediately know. Only then could they act.

But what surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that they had yet to reach the city despite travelling for an entire day; and on a speed much faster than average. If they weren’t able to confirm that they were in Divine Gift River, then Zhao Hai would’ve thought that they had taken the wrong route.

After the day passed and the skies turned dark, Zhao Hai stopped advancing. Then he had everyone rest, their trip would continue tomorrow.

Zhao Hai has a reason to do this. They will soon fight against the Divines. At this time, they need to be in their best condition. Although it wouldn’t be a problem for them to not rest for a few days, Zhao Hai still wanted to make sure that everyone gets enough rest.

After taking a rest, Zhao Hai and the others continued onward. But this time, they weren’t left disappointed for long. After two hours, they had finally arrived at Divine Gift City. The ones to discover the city first were Laura and the others.

Zhao Hai haven’t even approached the city when Laura and the others walked out of their room. As soon as they came out, they immediately told Zhao Hai that they had reached their destination. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to not go ashore. Instead, he commanded Bubble to go down. They would survey Divine Gift City and see where there were only a few people. Only then would they go and head directly towards Central City.

In the beginning, Bingya and the others didn’t know why Zhao Hai suddenly stopped. However, they didn’t say anything. They knew that Zhao Hai may have something on his mind.

Bubble’s advancing speed wasn’t very fast. Looking for a place with a few people wasn’t very easy to find. Divine Gift River was the largest river in the Central Continent, a lot of people rely on this river for their livelihood. Naturally, this river was the busiest one in the Central Continent.

Zhao Hai already made some calculations and they were now quite a distance away from Divine Gift City. However, they were yet to find a place with a few people. This caused Zhao Hai to knit his brows.

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and knew what he was thinking about. She smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother Hai, I think looking for a proper place at daytime wasn’t a good idea. How about we wait until evening comes. With Central City being the Central Continent’s biggest settlement, it should be brilliantly illuminated. When the time comes, we can use the lights to guide us.”

Upon hearing Lizzy, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but tap his own head. He was too focused on getting ashore and didn’t think about the opportune time to do so.

Although the strength of the people here in the Divine Realm was much greater than the people in the Ark Continent, they still needed to take a sleep and rest. When night comes, then that would be a good time to attack.

After thinking through this point, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Bingya and the others and said, “Alright, then everyone should go back and take a rest. We’ll move in the evening.”

When Bingya and the others heard this, they all looked at each other before turning to Zhao Hai with confused expressions.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We can’t waste too much time looking for a proper place. Moreover, going out at daytime would attract too much attention. We will go at night.”

Bingya and the others immediately understood what Zhao Hai meant. They gave Zhao Hai a nod before going to their own rooms. They didn’t know why Zhao Hai was so confident, but they knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t just say things without reason.

Zhao Hai’s group also returned to their rooms. Inside the room, Zhao Hai turned the monitor on.

Seen on the monitor were the Divines who were bustling about. They looked no different to the people from the Ark Continent. All of them were rushing here and there for their livelihood. One couldn’t see the legendary image of the Divine Race in them.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai? Are you feeling regret?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and shook his head, “There’s no time for regrets. Our enmity needed to be settled. If the enemy exists in the future, then we wouldn’t be able to feel free. If we show compassion today, then we might be the ones to suffer tomorrow.”

Laura gave out a sigh then turned to the monitor, “If the Divines didn’t provoke us into war, then we might still be doing business in the Ark Continent. Visiting Brother Wales from time to time in order to have a drink.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “What’s there to reminisce. We can just go to Brother Wales now and have some drinks.”

Laura shook her head and said, “Forget it. We have a big night ahead of us, we don’t have time to go drinking. Let’s take a rest. Who knows what things the Divines have in store for us. Brother Hai, we shouldn’t take them lightly.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I won’t drink. Go and take a good rest. I still need to count on you for the battle ahead.”

The women nodded before they turned around and left.

It can be said that they were now quite used to wars. They knew that they needed to take a rest since nobody knew when they could after the battle starts.

They rested for the rest of the day and then had dinner in the evening. When Zhao Hai and the others came out of their rooms, the skies were already dark. The shores were brilliantly illuminated and was still quite lively.

Chapter 911: Connecting Heaven Palace? Attack it!

Looking at the lights on the shore, Zhao Hai was unexpectedly calm. He knew that as the leader of their team, he couldn’t show too much emotion or else it would affect the morale. Fortunately, Zhao Hai had other people to take command. Zhao Hai really didn’t have the talent for strategy.

At the same time, Bingya and the others also came out of their rooms. Their expressions were tinged with excitement.

As members of the Foreign Races, they had never dreamed that they would be able to attack the capital of the Central Continent. This was something impossible for them before, but now they were actually here. How could they not feel excited?

Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious. He stood quietly on the Hell King’s ship as he looked at the shore. Slowly, the clamor became smaller and smaller, the people on the shore becoming less and less. Before long, the place had gone quiet while the lights had become sparse.

Zhao Hai was still unmoving. This caused Bingya and the others to be anxious. They looked quite uneasy. In the end, Bingya couldn’t help but take a step forward and approach Zhao hai.

After Bingya arrived by Zhao Hai’s side, Zhao Hai looked at him and said, “What’s wrong? Worried?”

Bingya gawked, then he immediately nodded and said, “I’m quite worried.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t think about it too much. People had just fallen asleep. It’s possible that there are some people who are still up. We can’t risk being discovered at this time. Let’s wait, then we make our move.”

Bingya nodded and didn’t speak anymore. However, he was still somewhat restless as he walked back and forth. Zhao Hai gave him a glance a few times before he said, “Just calm down. At this time, the one who has a weaker heart would take the bigger blow. In any case, we’re already here, they cannot run no matter what they do.”

Bingya and the others’ faces turned red as they turned speechless. Their mood was totally different from Zhao Hai’s. In the past, they were always the ones being attacked by the Divines. Now, it was the Divines who were going to be attacked.

After waiting for about an hour, the shores finally became completely peaceful. Seeing that there were less lights, Zhao Hai knew that the time has come. He turned to Bubble and said, “Bubble, let’s go up.” Bubble complied as they ascended towards the river’s surface.

Bubble went up until he finally separated from the river. Bit by bit, he went towards the sky. Due to being small, it was close to impossible to spot Bubble. Because of this, he managed to attract no attention.

Upon reaching the skies, Zhao Hai immediately made Bubble withdraw. After that, he increased the Hell King’s ship’s size.

At the same time, they were also flying horizontally along the Central Continent. They were heading towards a place with red lights. Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t the sky being red. Instead, it was a reflection coming from the city with no evenings, Central City.

In less than an hour, Zhao Hai arrived outside the city. This city was incredibly big. Zhao Hai looked dumbfoundedly at its size, he couldn’t even estimate how many people were inside such a settlement.

After some time, Zhao Hai recovered. Then he looked at the city and bitterly smiled. It was because he can see huge letters on the city’s gates that spelled, Central!

With these letters, nobody would suspect that this was Central City. However, what made Zhao Hai surprised was the construction of the city. There were broken walls, and there were places with no walls, disconnecting the line altogether. It looked more like a cultural site than a completely defendable establishment.

Such a city was both good and bad news. It was good because there were no walls to block them. But it was bad because there definitely were key place that needed to defended in this city. It was only hard to spot because of the city’s structure.

But before long, Zhao Hai managed to find his target. In the center of the city was a very high mountain. On the mountain were palaces. Of all the sectors in Central City, this area had the most magnificent lighting, it looked like the Imperial Palace of the Central Continent.

While Zhao Hai was pondering over this, Bingya suddenly exclaimed, “Central Continent’s Connecting Heaven Palace!”

Zhao Hai turned to Bingya and said, “Connecting Heaven Palace?”

Bingya nodded, his two eyes shining as he said, “There was no mountain there in the first place. But later on, the people of the Central Continent used a lot of experts to build that mountain there. The mountain symbolizes that the palace can connect to the heavens.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Connecting Heaven Palace, interesting. Let’s attack that place today. Binyga, get ready. I’m afraid we’ll be spotted as soon as we enter the city. We’ll go with the fastest speed and head directly to the mountain. I want to lay waste to that palace.”

When Bingya and the others heard Zhao Hai, they immediately got up and got excited. Connecting Heaven Palace was the face of the Central Continent. Thinking about that place being ruined would naturally make them feel excitement.

Zhao Hai also made his preparations as he took his staff out and called Cai’er over. He didn’t dare treat this matter lightly. The last time, Zhao Hai was separated from Cai’er. Thinking about this made Zhao Hai wipe a cold sweat. He needed to be ready for any encounter.

Zhao Hai didn’t send Bubble back to the Space. Bubble was now resting on top of his head.

Inside the Hell King’s ship, there were also massive amounts of undead prepared. If the other party uses another method to disconnect him from the Space, then the undead on board would at least provide him with some support.

After everything was prepared, Zhao Hai began to lead the Hell King’s ship to move forward. When the ship crossed the city’s walls, the word ‘Central’ began to make grating squeals. Along with the squeal were red lights flashing all around the city, warning the populace of an incoming danger.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the cities defenses to be this good. Although the walls were torn down, the warning system was actually still this sensitive. Moreover, the range of this alarm encompasses the whole torn down wall. Immediately after an intruder passes the walls, the alarm would immediately blare up.

However, what happened next made Zhao Hai confused. In Zhao Hai’s mind, since Central City’s alarms were this developed, then it meant that its citizens and soldiers were similarly as alert. But instead, the reaction of the people inside the city was very strange. All of them wore their clothes as they went out with expressions of confusion and anxiety. They were looking around blankly while the alarm was sounding out.

Aside from the residents, the army also disappointed Zhao Hai. Their response was too slow. Zhao Hai had noted several garrisons around the city. However, he didn’t care much about them. His present target was Connecting Heaven Palace. These military compounds were not his priority.

After the alarm sounded out, the soldiers actually had the same response as the commoners. They were somewhat at a loss upon hearing the alarm. Even the senior officers had the same response.

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai was shocked. The army that would protect this city was actually this incompetent. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel disappointed at the Divines.

However, this was a good thing for Zhao Hai. He didn’t care about them anymore as he led the Hell King’s ship towards Connecting Heaven Palace at the quickest speed.

Compared to before, the Hell King’s ship’s speed was much greater. The commoners could only feel a flash of shadow above them as it passed by. Even if they wanted to look for it, their eyes wouldn’t be able to catch up.

Although Central City was very big, the Hell King’s ship managed to quickly arrive by Connecting Heaven Palace. The army stationed inside Connecting Heaven Palace actually had a faster response compared to those soldiers outside. Because of this, the palace’s defenses have been established. Their magic cannons were also at the ready.

During his fights back at the Taurus Continent, after crashing into the Divine Race’s base, Zhao Hai discovered that he really preferred to destroy his enemy in the most violent and simple way. He felt like it was more satisfying that way.

The troops inside Connecting Heaven Palace soon discovered Zhao Hai’s ship. Naturally, since the ship was very fast, the moment the troops decided to make an attack was the moment the ship hit their magic shield. While the troops were dumbfounded, the Hell King’s shp proceeded to bulldoze the shield defending the palace.

The protective shield around Connecting Heaven Palace can be said to be the most firm defense in all of the Divine Race territories. The defense uses God-rank magic beast cores as power while other cities only used 9th rank cores. The disparity on both was naturally clear.

However, this firm defense was actually treated by the Hell King’s ship as mere paper as it broke through with little to no difficulty. After that, the Hell King’s ship hit a wall and drove through it. The wall didn’t even scrape the ship as a huge hole bore into it.

And the Hell King’s ship didn’t stop there. After boring a hole through the wall, the ship kept advancing. Everything in front of it was demolished, houses, walls, people, it didn’t matter. The Hell King’s ship was like a bullet being shot through a watermelon. The ship headed forwards and continued on towards the mountain where Connecting Heaven Palace was. It was intent on going through it!

Chapter 912: They Should’ve Thought About It Long Ago!

Boom! A heaven-shaking sound was heard, shaking the entire Central City. The people who were awoken by the alarm and had come out saw their holy place being penetrated by a golden light.

These people didn’t know what just happened, they were dumbfounded for some time. What was going on? Was the Deity punishing them?

While they were puzzled, that golden light made a turn-around, heading towards Connecting Heaven Palace once more. This time, people were able to see it clearly. It was actually a huge golden ship!

What made the Divines dumbfounded was that this ship was like a child that had found a new fun toy to play with. It hit the Connecting Heaven Palace again and again. It started at the top of the mountain and gradually went down. Their prided mountain was being smashed to pieces.

Every Divine had lost the ability to think. They didn’t know what was happening. They didn’t know what the ship was doing and why was it attacking the palace.

At this moment, the soldiers of Central City finally responded. All Divine soldiers took their weapons and went towards the palace with the quickest speed they could muster.

These soldiers knew what the destruction of the Connecting Heaven palace meant. Losing the palace meant losing the dignity of the Central Continent. It would be a huge blow to the Central Continent.

At this point, the Divine soldiers had gone mad. They all rushed towards the palace and tear apart the one who dared to make an attack.

However, the soldiers had no opportunity to do so. Connecting Heaven Palace was not a natural mountain, it was artificially made. In terms of strength, it was still inferior to ones made by nature. After being hit by the Hell King’s ship multiple times, the mountain finally couldn’t withstand it and just collapsed.

But Zhao Hai wasn’t finished, he didn’t intend to let anybody go. He commanded the ship’s cannons to shoot towards the palace’s direction. All the Divines who flew out of the mountain were killed on the spot.

This time, Zhao Hai can finally see how the improved magic cannons performed. If the previous cannons of the ship were to be ordinary magic cannons of the Ark Continent, then the improved cannons were like the huge cannons of the Divine Race.

The Hell King’s ship’s cannons weren’t just a bit more powerful. In fact, in the ship’s recent upgrade, the cannons received the greatest improvement in power.

First, the cannons’ materials have changed. The magic cannons that Zhao Hai used were made by iron, making them useless after being used for some time. However, the magic cannons of the Hell King’s ship were now made from specially synthesized materials. Its strength had increased by a lot. Even if they were used for a long time, they would still remain undamaged.

Second, the raw power used by the cannons. Zhao Hai’s cannons used magic crystals as a power source. On the other hand, the Hell King’s ship’s cannons used the yin-yang pond as a power source. The energy contained inside the yin-yang pond was much greater compared to the energy inside magic crystals. With this, it was natural for the Hell King’s ship’s cannons to be more powerful.

And third, the magic armors that Zhao Hai gained helped a lot. Although Zhao Hai didn’t have the time to study the magic armors and just handed them over to Karen, the magic formations on those armors were still used to improve the Hell King’s ship. The magic formations on the magic armors helped the cannons to increase their output. Among the three improvements, this one was the one that benefitted the cannons the most.

At this time, Zhao Hai was confident that as long as the cannons hit a God-rank expert, then that expert would certainly die. If ten magic cannons combine their power, then even Supreme Elders in their ultimate weapons wouldn’t be able to block them.

Zhao Hai had the ship circle around the rubble that was Connecting Heaven Palace. Every Divine they discovered were immediately attacked and killed. Even if there weren’t any people in sight, the cannons were still firing. Everything that was the Connecting Heaven Palace was destroyed, nothing good was left.

This process might look like it took a long time, but everything had just happened in less than an hour. In this one hour, Central City’s soldiers had slowly encircled the Hell King’s ship.

After Zhao Hai saw that the Connecting Heaven Palace was almost destroyed, he decided to leave. He turned the ship and went straight to the Divine Race Soldiers.

When the troops saw that Zhao Hai was heading towards them, instead of retreating, they actually proceeded to clash. They took up their arms and charged towards the Hell King’s ship. They were like warriors carrying swords and spears charging towards an enemy tank.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about these soldiers. He wasn’t planning to fight with these people as he just drove the ship through them. The golden streak of light vanished from the horizon soon after, leaving the maddened soldiers with nothing to do.

At this time, the commoners started to respond. They wept and wailed as they ran towards the Connecting Heaven palace. The palace was too important for the people living in the Central Continent. This was their source of energy, their pride. But under their gazes, it was mercilessly destroyed. Nothing noteworthy was left.

The Divines began to congregate towards the place where the palace was located. The majestic structure was destroyed, not even a tile was left. All of the Divines in the capital cried. There were even some soldiers who couldn’t bear the thorn in their hearts and committed suicide.

The symbol of the Central Continent, the pride of the Central Continent, the strength of the Central Continent, the Connecting Heaven Palace has been destroyed. And the culprit was Zhao Hai!

After Zhao Hai’s assault on Central City, he got rid of the pursuers before returning to Divine Gift River. Then he had Bubble surround the ship and sank to the bottom of the river without coming out.

The duration of the assault was too short. It only took an hour or so from beginning to end. To be honest, Bingya and the others weren’t expecting Zhao Hai to use this method to deal with the palace. Before they could even move their hands, Zhao Hai had already made an attack and the battle was over.

Actually, it wasn’t only Bingya’s team, Laura and the others weren’t expecting Zhao Hai to do this as well.

In fact, Zhao Hai didn’t think that this was what he would be doing too. After he heard Bingya mention the Connecting Heaven Palace, he was suddenly struck by an idea.

Connecting Heaven Palace was a symbol of the Central Continent’s strength. If it was destroyed by him, then it would certainly be a huge blow to the Central Continent. Even if Elder Star was quite the schemer, he would still be compelled to return to the Central Continent to handle this matter. Otherwise, the Central Continent would be sunk into chaos.

The Divines were proud, and this was even more true for those who lived in the Central Continent. With how resounding the slap that Zhao Hai gave them, nobody could blame the Central Divines if they were to go insane.

In this case, if Elder Star didn’t make a move, then the Central Divines would meet their end. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to demolish the Connecting Heaven Palace. With this, Elder Star should be forced to return to the Central Continent.

After Bubble sank to the bottom of the river, Zhao Hai finally gave out a sigh of relief. He was really afraid that the Divines would use a special weapon to deal with him. But now, it seems like his worries were unnecessary.

Bingya’s team, as well as Laura and the others stood by Zhao Hai’s side. When Laura saw Zhao Hai sighing in relief, she smiled and said, “Brother Hai, were you really that nervous?”

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and smiled bitterly, “Really nervous. It’s natural, we’re in the Central Continent, a place known as the most formidable in the Divine Realm. Moreover, we are attacking its capital city. How can I not be nervous? However, it’s great that they weren’t as formidable as we thought.”

Bingya looked at Zhao Hai, his eyes shone as he said, “Mister, did you know how important the Connecting Heaven Palace was? Not only in the Central Continent, but the entire Divine Race looked up to it. Connecting Heaven Palace was the Divine Race’s symbol of authority and strength. Now that Mister destroyed it, then it meant that Mister has announced his eternal enmity against the Divine Race.”

When he heard Bingya, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly, “When the Divines attacked the Ark Continent, they should’ve known that our enmity is irreconcilable. This is just the start!”

Bingya didn’t know what to say. Zhao Hai surely had the strength to back up his words. If those words came out from another person’s mouth, then people would just laugh at them. Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Bingya suddenly felt that the Divine Realm might have no Divines left in the future!

After seeing that Bingya had stayed silent, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “Bingya, tell your people about what just happened. Remind them to be extra alert. After knowing what we just did, it’s possible that all the Divines would go crazy. If they couldn’t find us, then they might shift their rage to your clans. Have your people tread carefully.”

Bingya’s expression changed, then he made a nod. He knew that Zhao Hai was telling the truth. After knowing this information, the Divines would surely go mad. They will rush to the Central Continent to look for Zhao Hai. And if they failed to find Zhao Hai, then they would shift their attention to the foreign races, given that Zhao Hai was allied with them. The foreign races might have a bad time coming.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Alright, go take a rest. Have your people help us in paying attention to the Divine Race’s response. The more details, the better.”

Bingya nodded before returning to his room along with Ryder and Yehta. They immediately relayed the information to their clans, telling them about the event that happened in the Central Continent. They instructed their people to be ready at all times.

After seeing Bingya and the others leaving, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Inform Fei’er about this as well. Tell them that they might suffer for a while.”

When Laura heard Zhao Hai say this, she paused for a moment before her eyes shone, “Brother Hai, are you ready to make a move on the three clans?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s about time, isn’t it?”

Chapter 913: Elder Star’s Plan

Elder Star quietly stood on the balcony of his room. He was currently in the Leo Continent’s Imperial Palace.

The structure of this Palace was very grand, but compared to Connecting Heaven Palace, it still had some shortcomings. However, Elder Star didn’t care. Although he lived in Connecting Heaven Palace, he settled on a small side residence. He didn’t involve himself in politics, he just stayed in cultivating. He was waiting to ascend one day.

At this time, if it wasn’t for Jie Yu’s letter asking for his help, he wouldn’t have come out. He knew that he was required this time.

Zhao Hai’s strength was something that surpassed his imagination. In the past, Elder Star wouldn’t have even thought that a person would be able to escape an attack made by five Supreme Elders. They made ample preparations for the ambush. The enemy was even captured inside Sealing Star Disk. However, the enemy was actually able to come out! Moreover, after withdrawing, he even managed to destroy their base.

This person was too dangerous! After clashing with Zhao Hai, Elder Star understood how terrible Zhao Hai was. Elder Star believes that if Zhao Hai keeps being in the Divine Realm, then the entire Divine Race would be endangered.

Not only was Zhao Hai strong, he was also vicious and merciless.

The people of the Taurus Continent has been slaughtered by Zhao Hai. It was startling even for Elder Star.

Naturally, Elder Star knew about what the Taurus Divines did back in the Ark Continent. However, Elder Star was a member of the Divine Race, and he had the pride of a Divine. In his view, the people of the Ark Continent were lesser beings. It didn’t matter how many of those people were slaughtered. It was just like how people from the Ark Continent didn’t treat slaves as equals. The Divines didn’t look at the people from the Ark Continent as beings that were on the same level.

But after Zhao Hai’s slaughter, Elder Star began to feel a sense of dread.

If Zhao Hai wasn’t dealt with soon, then more Divines would fall.

There were two reasons why Elder Star decided to eliminate Zhao Hai. First was the rebellion of the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus , and second was the alliance with the foreign races.

The rebellion of the three clans had caused the large scale rebellion of the Divine Realm’s vassal races. This effect can still be felt up to this time. There were still people from the other continents that were yet to deal with their vassal races. The Divines were caught unprepared.

Next was the alliance with the foreign races. The battle between the foreign races and the Divine race had lasted for tens of thousands of years. Their hatred for each other has been engraved on their bones. In this case, if Zhao Hai cooperates with the foreign races and succeed, then what would happen to the Divines?

Because of these reasons, Elder Star has to cooperate with the other Supreme Elders in order to eliminate Zhao Hai.

Just like what Zhao Hai guessed, Elder Star and the others’ deployment of the troops was a ploy. Zhao Hai had fought with Gold Ben before and the Taurus Divines also clashed with Zhao Hai back in the Ark Continent. Therefore, they already have some sort of information about Zhao Hai. They had discovered that Zhao Hai was a sly person. If the Divines were to really attack the foreign races, then Zhao Hai definitely wouldn’t help. Instead, Zhao Hai would just go to the Divine Race continents and cause trouble. And when the Divines retreat, they would also need to watch for their backs.

Because of this, Elder Star needed to make advance preparations. After studying Zhao Hai, he found out that Zhao Hai was a person who didn’t like taking risks. He would carefully plan things out before making the first step. Elder Star knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t support the Foreign Races if the Divines were to attack them. So Elder Star decided to speak his words back in the Taurus Continent. However, it can be said that it wasn’t a planned act. Only Elder Star was pretending, the others weren’t.

Elder Star only thought about this plan when he was on his way to the Taurus Continent so he didn’t have time to discuss it with the others. Because of this, he could only act by himself. Only after they retreated from the Taurus Continent did he reveal his plan to the others.

Elder Star did all of these because he discovered that Zhao Hai seemed to be one step ahead of them at all times. Therefore, Elder Star suspected that Zhao Hai might have a method to monitor them.

This thought stemmed from what happened with the second supply transport. Although they wanted to deal with Zhao Hai, they still decided to change their course. Delivering the supplies was much more important than facing Zhao Hai.

However, even if they changed their route, Zhao Hai was still able to encounter them. If Zhao Hai didn’t have means to monitor them, then this outcome wouldn’t have happened.

Elder Star didn’t know how Zhao Hai did it, but he still didn’t dare to take it lightly. In the end, he chose a conservative approach and deceived everyone. It wouldn’t be too late to discuss things when they return to their territory.

Therefore, Elder Star and the others only discussed after reaching the Leo Continent. The reason Elder Star dared to do his current plan was because he has a treasure in his hands.

Without this treasure, Elder Star’s plan would’ve been impossible to accomplish. One can say that they were already on the path of defeat from the very beginning. Of the 13 Continents in the Divine Realm, three of them belonged to the foreign races while one has been conquered by Zhao Hai. This left nine continents for the Divine Race. And the Divines were also left with 9 Supreme Elders. The Scorpio Supreme Elder had already fallen into Zhao Hai’s hands. This loss also informed Elder Star about Zhao Hai’s strength.

1 or 2 Supreme Elders wouldn’t be a threat to Zhao Hai. Instead, it would be a gift to him. Because of this, Elder Star decided that everyone would move as one. With the strength of 9 Supreme Elders, Zhao Hai would surely be destroyed.

However, an issue had arisen with this arrangement. With nine people going together, this meant that all of them could only stay in one continent. If Zhao Hai chose to attack a continent besides where the Supreme Elders were, then the Supreme Elders wouldn’t be able to do anything.

In the end, when Elder Star presented his treasure, the other Supreme Elders began to feel relief. The treasure that Elder Star had was known as the Seven Star Heaven Lock.

This treasure was actually several formation disks. It looked like the Star Sealing Disk but has inferior offense. The Sealing Star Disk can injure the enemy while the Seven Star Heaven Lock can only trap them.

If one talks about killing the enemy, then the Sealing Star Disk was naturally very formidable. Moreover, with more Ultimate Weapons, the disk would become more powerful.

But if one wanted to seal a person, then the Sealing Star Disk was actually inferior to the Seven Star Heaven Lock. The Seven Star Heaven Lock was divided into eight formation disks; the seven stars and the core.

And these eight disks can be used separately. Even if they were used individually, as long as the Seven Star Heaven Lock formation was established, the effects would manifest. Moreover, its might wasn’t low.

Elder Star took this set of formation disks and gave one to each continent. The continents would house these disks and as long as they use it to surround Zhao Hai for several days, then the Supreme Elders can rush over and deal with him.

The reason why Elder Star was confident that these disks can surround Zhao Hai was due to the testing that he did before. These formation disks have their own characteristics. Once one was trapped inside a Seven Star Heaven Lock formation, then one would be trapped inside for seven days. Elder Star had tried it before, no matter if it was a Supreme Elder or an ordinary person, one could only be trapped for seven days, and nobody was able to break the formation. If two formation disks were used, then the trap would last 14 days. If three, then 21 days, and so on. If one uses eight formation disks, then the victim would be trapped for 56 days. After 56 days, whether the victim was dead or alive, the formation would unravel. Only when the formation was set up once more could it be used again.

Elder Star used this formation one time to trap the three Foreign Race Supreme Elders for 56 days. That was the time where the foreign races suffered the heaviest loss. If not for Elder Star being unsure of eliminating the three Supreme Elders, then the foreign races would have surely been slaughtered.

Because of the Seven Star Heaven Lock, Elder Star was assured that they could deal with Zhao Hai. In his opinion, no matter which continent Zhao Hai attacked, he would still be surrounded and trapped. Seven days was enough for the Supreme Elders to travel to any continent and eliminate Zhao Hai.

And just to be sure, in addition to the true Seven Star Heaven Lock, Elder Star also made imitations of the treasure. However, these imitations weren’t very useful. If these imitations were to trap Zhao Hai, then they would only last a short time.

However, a short time was a huge factor when it came to the battlefield. If Zhao Hai was trapped inside an imitation, then the one who held the true formation disk would be able to go to where Zhao Hai was and trap him. After that, Elder Star and the others would soon arrive to kill Zhao Hai.

This plan was very good. Naturally, there was a Seven Star Heaven Lock disk in the Central Continent. However, whether they be an ordinary Divine or Elder Star, nobody expected Zhao Hai to attack the Central Continent. This was because it was very far from where Zhao Hai was. Zhao Hai wanted to solve the attack on the foreign races, but attacking the Central Continent was the slowest method. Because of this, nobody expected Zhao Hai to target the Central Continent. Instead, he would choose a continent that was much closer to the Taurus Continent.

Besides these arrangements, Elder Star also informed all of the Fishmen to thoroughly monitor the seas. As soon as they spot Zhao Hai, they would immediately make a report.

The Fishman Race’s news was the quickest in the Divine Realm. Therefore, Elder Star was confident in his plan to deal with Zhao Hai.

However, despite all of these, Elder Star still couldn’t help but feel uneasy. Their army had already departed and had clashed with the foreign races. Yet there still weren’t any news about Zhao Hai. This caused Elder Star to feel restless.

He reviewed his plan carefully once more and there shouldn’t be any flaws. This allowed him to loosen up a bit.

At this time, the sound of rapid footsteps can be heard.

Chapter 914: Maddened Divine Race

Naturally, Elder Star was able to hear those footsteps. Judging by the cadence on each step, it should be Gold Ben. Gold Ben was now a stray dog. His strength was inferior to Elder Star, and now he had become the Elder’s faithful subordinate. This was because Gold Ben knew that if there was someone that can help him take revenge in the Divine Realm, then it would be Elder Star.

This didn’t pertain to Elder Star’s strength, instead it was because of his identity. Elder Star was the Supreme Elder of the Central Continent, he was a Supreme Elder that held more power compared to the other Supreme Elders. Because of this, the Supreme Elders have him as their center. If Gold Ben wanted to have his revenge, then he can only depend on Elder Star to organize the other Supreme Elders. Only Elder Star had this ability.

Gold Ben was a decisive person. He was very willing to be Elder Star’s subordinate in order to make Elder Star move.

Because of this, when Elder Star heard that it was Gold Ben, he went back to standing in the balcony. He thought that since Gold Ben has come, then Zhao Hai should have appeared.

Gold Ben entered the room. When he saw Elder Star just posing there, he didn’t know whether he should laugh or cry. In the past, Gold Ben didn’t know about Elder Star’s temper since they didn’t have much contact. But now, Gold Ben discovered that Elder Star wanted to make poses in order to highlight his extraordinary points. Elder Star was doing that same thing right now.

“I don’t know if he can still make a pose when he hears this news.” Gold Ben thought of this as he walked towards Elder Star.

Elder Star didn’t wait for Gold Ben to open his mouth as he asked, “What happened? Did you find any traces of Zhao Hai?”

Gold Ben nodded and said, “Yes, Zhao Hai has appeared. He attacked the Central Continent and ruined the Connecting Heaven Palace. The mountain was knocked down by his ship. From what I had heard, nobody from the palace survived.”

Elder Star just stood there and quietly listened. Seeing little reaction from Elder Star, Gold Ben actually started to admire him.

But at this moment, Elder Star turned around, fierce expression plastered on his face. He glared at Gold Ben and said, “What did you just say? Zhao Hai attacked what?”

Gold Ben couldn’t help but scold his heart. He really thought that Elder Star had a good control over his emotions. As it turns out, he was just too stunned to respond.

Although he had unspoken criticisms, Gold Ben repeated his report. Although it was already his second time hearing this, Elder Star stood there, looking at Gold Ben. Then Elder Star muttered, “This, how can this be possible? Didn’t the Connecting Heaven Palace have a Seven Star Heaven Lock disk? How can this happen?”

Gold Ben shook his head and said, “At present, we still don’t know everything. But this matter has already been spread outside. We need to head to the Central Continent to have a look.”

When Gold Ben said this, Elder Star looked at him and said, “Yes, you’re right. We have to go and have a look.” After that, Elder Star’s figure disappeared. Gold Ben saw Elder Star flying out of the balcony and headed directly towards the Central Continent.

Gold Ben didn’t immediately follow Elder Star. Instead, he quickly went to inform the others. The other Supreme Elders couldn’t sit still too. Although Zhao Hai didn’t attack their continents, Connecting Heaven Palace was the pride of the Divine Race. They couldn’t just let Zhao Hai go after he destroyed it.

The news didn’t only arrive at the Leo Continent. It didn’t take long before the entire Divine Realm got wind of what happened. When the Divines heard this, they couldn’t help but turn crazy.

Those who’d gone mad first were the citizens of the Central Continent. They couldn’t believe it, someone actually dared to attack them. Moreover, under their gazes, their sacred palace was destroyed. This was without a doubt a slap on the face of the Central Continent. It would be strange if they didn’t go insane.

However, the worse thing about this situation was the fact that the crazed residents of the Central Continent were left with no leader. The members of the Central Continent’s Imperial family lived in the palace. Now that they had been eliminated, the Central Continent became a headless dragon. Nobody had the authority to lead the angry mob of Central Divines. At the same time, their reason has already been burned by the anger that they felt.

A person’s anger was a terrifying thing. This was especially true for people with great strength.

With the Central Continent in its current state, the first to lose their reason were the capital city’s soldiers. They started to destroy everything around them and murder people. The entire capital city was soon plunged into chaos.

After that, the entire Central Continent turned insane. When evening neared, the Central Continent had long lost its peace.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the result to be this drastic. He just destroyed a structure in the Central Continent, yet the entire continent had gone to chaos.

Zhao Hai blankly stared at the monitor, dumbfounded at what was happening. Laura and the others had the same thought. This scene was far from their imagination.

After some time, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and forced a smile, “It seems like we’ve stirred a hornet’s nest.”

Laura smiled bitterly and said, “How can it turn into this? Can Brother Hai ask Bingya and the others?”

Zhao Hai smiled and shook his head, “There’s no need to ask. Didn’t Bingya already tell us the answer? The ruined palace seems to be really important for the Divines. Otherwise, the the Divines wouldn’t have this much reaction. However, this result if good for us. If the Divines start to go mad at the Foreign Races, then wouldn’t that be great? What do you think?” Laura smiled and said, “That is truly good news. But to be honest, this has been too cruel to the Divines.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “This situation isn’t about us being cruel to them. But them being cruel to us. Alright, no matter what, if Elder Star is really planning to make a move, then I think he would arrive very soon.”

Laura nodded and said, “I think Elder Star had also gone mad. He should already be heading here at the fastest speed. What do we do next?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Us? How about we pay a visit to the Leo Continent? If they come to the Central Continent, then we’ll go to the Leo Continent and make a mess there. The Leo Continent is also the best place to contact the foreign races.”

Laura nodded, “That is a good idea. But did the Leo Continent make any preparations? What are we going to do about that?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then wouldn’t it be better if they were prepared? What do we need to fear? First we make a mess of the Leo Continent and then we see what kind of reaction the Divines would have.” Laura frowned and said, “With this current situation, the Divines would surely attack the Foreign Races. Maybe they’ll even attack the Thunder Clan and the others, or even eliminate the vassal races.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “They will certainly make a move on the Thunder Clan and the others. They know that those three clans are our earliest allies. If those three clans were to be in trouble, we certainly couldn’t just ignore it. Moreover, compared to the foreign races, the three clans are much easier to deal with.”

Laura stared, then she nodded. But Lizzy frowned as she said, “If I’m a Divine, then I would deal with the vassal races first. Eliminating any disturbances behind.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then it’s a pity that you’re not a Divine. This time, we had truly hit a sensitive nerve of the Divine Race. What they want to do right now is to deal with us. From what I can see, the vassal races had yet to make a result even after a few days. For the Divines, as long as we are dealt with, going for the vassal races would be very easy to do. I reckon they will come to us first.”

Lizzy nodded, she thought that Zhao Hai was correct. These vassal races truly weren’t a big threat to the Divine Race. Even if the Divine Race army didn’t attack them, as long as a Supreme Elder was sent in, then the vassal races wouldn’t be able to resist.

However, Zhao Hai’s group was different. They had the strength to contend against ultimate weapons. In this case, Zhao Hai’s demise would need to be prioritized.

It can be said that using ultimate weapons required a certain price to pay for the Supreme Elders. If they waste this opportunity and deal with the vassal races, then what would they do in order to face Zhao Hai? In this case, they can only wait for their deaths, and the end of the Divine Race. Because of this, the Divines would want to find Zhao Hai and compel him to a decisive battle.

After thinking about this, Lizzy immediately said, “Big Brother Hai, I think we should tell Fei’er and the others about this as soon as possible. If they are unprepared, then their losses would be very big.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We certainly need to inform them. However, the three clans won’t listen to us, there’s nothing much we can do. Forget it, let’s just have fate decide. I hope that after they eat some losses, they would come to trust me and agree to enter the Space.”

Lizzy and the others smiled bitterly. They knew that this won’t be easy. The Thunder Clan and the others were very tenacious people. It was close to impossible for the the three clans to trust Zhao Hai completely. It would take quite the effort to have them move to the Space.

But as the matter stands, the three clans  would surely lose big after facing the Divines. This wasn’t something that Lizzy and the others wanted to see, this caused them to be in a dilemma.

To be honest, Lizzy and the other didn’t intend to push the three clans to a corner when they attacked the central continent. This development was just not under their control.

Chapter 915: Destruction and Regret!

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately tell Fei’er about what he had speculated. After all, these were just his guesses. Moreover, Zhao Hai wouldn’t let the Divine Supreme Elders to easily deal with Fei’er and the others.

Currently, Zhao Hai was able to equip more and more Devil Legion Soldiers with combat suits that were grown in the Space. To be honest, even if the Supreme Elders were to gang up on him, Zhao Hai could just mobilize the Devil Legion. He wasn’t really afraid of the Divine Race.

However, that would also cause huge losses to the Devil Legion. This wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to see. Zhao Hai hoped to preserve the Devil Legion as much as possible.

If Zhao Hai didn’t plan to use the Devil Legion to deal with the O’Neal family, then it was the same for the battle against the stronger Supreme Elders.

Although it can be said that the Devil Legion was under the command of the Great Demon King, the Great Demon King has slowly undergone a change. And this change was something that Zhao Hai hoped for.

The Great Demon King’s change began when Zhao Hai gave the Devil Legion the combat suits. After giving the combat suits, Zhao Hai actually didn’t give them anything to do. The Great Demon King thought that Zhao Hai gave them combat suits in order to command them, instead it was actually to give help. Because of this, the Great Demon King began to look at Zhao Hai in a different light.

Further down the line, with the Space’s help, the Great Demon King would look favorably towards Zhao Hai. But now, the Great Demon King was still at a crucial moment. Zhao Hai didn’t want to move the Devil Legion at this time lest he waste all of his previous efforts.

Besides the Devil Legion, Zhao Hai also took great care towards the people from the Ark Continent. At this moment, Zhao Hai had already raised a lot of people into God-ranks using his potions. Moreover, Zhao Hai also selected some of them and had them sent to the hell background for some tempering.

However, it would be impossible for to form an army out of the Ark Continent’s people in a short period of time. Their strength was still not up to par. Forget about Supreme Elders, none of them had even fought against other God-rank experts. Even if they had combat suits, they still didn’t have the ability to join the fight in the Divine Realm.

Besides the Ark Continent and the Demons, the other army that Zhao Hai can use was his undead. At this time, Zhao Hai had collected a large quantity of God-rank undead. These undead were mostly Demigods, but there were still a lot of them who had reached true God-rank strength.

But Zhao Hai found a problem. After equipping the combat suits, the undead couldn’t actually use 100% of their strength. The combat suits were completely unsuitable for the use of the undead. This worried Zhao Hai.

Of all the combat suits made by the Space, save some for Zhao Hai, everything was given to the Devil Legion. If Zhao Hai wanted to equip the entire Devil Legion with combat suits, then it would take him a very long time. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to give combat suits to his God-rank undead, further improving their strengths.

However, Zhao Hai was left disappointed. After putting the combat suits on, these God-rank undead did improve in strength, but compared to Supreme Elders, they were still vastly inferior. Moreover, these undead would move awkwardly inside those suits. This might not look serious, but in a real combat situation this was fatal. Forget about improving their strength, the undead would be hindered by the combat suits. This forced Zhao Hai to abandon his plan.

Because of these reasons, if Zhao Hai wanted to fight the Supreme Elders, then he would have to make a move himself. But the issue with this was that Zhao Hai couldn’t make a lot of moves.

Just like how the Supreme Elders couldn’t use their combat weapons for a long time, Zhao Hai also couldn’t move a lot or else he would be kicked out by the realm and ascend with no way of coming back. To be honest, Zhao Hai still didn’t want to leave. The Divine Realm still had a lot of good things that were yet to be taken. At the very least, Zhao Hai wanted to get the Sealing Star Disk that was in the hands of Elder Star.

…..

Zhao Hai resumed to watch the Divines. They were still in chaos. At this time, not only the Central Continent, the other continents went insane as well. Even the continents of the foreign races were affected.

When Bingya and the others told their clans that Zhao Hai destroyed the Connecting Heaven Palace, their clans thought that this was a joke. But when they noticed that the attacking army retreated quickly, even discarding their supplies, they understood that it was real. This caused an uproar among the foreign races.

There were a lot of people from the foreign races that haven’t seen Zhao Hai. They allied with Zhao Hai entirely because they thought that he was competent. Being able to destroy the Taurus Divines was an evidence to this.

But Zhao Hai was actually able to destroy the Connecting Heaven Palace. Although the Connecting Heaven Palace wasn’t a sacred landmark of the Foreign races, the foreign races knew what the palace represented for the Divine Race. The Foreign Races’ three Supreme Elders immediately convened in order to discuss how to deal with this matter.

In their opinion, this was an opportunity but at the same time it may become a maelstrom. It was an opportunity because of the accident with the Connecting Heaven Palace. At this time, the Divines were in chaos so the foreign races might be able to use this to make an attack.

However, it may become a maelstrom because this event was just too huge. The degree of randomness in this situation was quite high. It wasn’t even sure if the Divines were to continue being chaotic or if they were going to band together. The foreign races weren’t sure if they were to gain from this maelstrom or if they would be flattened.

The ordinary members of the foreign races didn’t have these complicated thoughts. They hated the Divines because the Divines always bullied them. Now that the Divines were having a disaster, it was natural if they were happy. These ordinary members weren’t stupid. They were also able to think that the Divines were in chaos. Because of this, they unanimously demanded to send troops to the Divine Race territory.

But the biggest beneficiary of this matter would be the vassal races. With what has happened, the Divines didn’t have the time to deal with the vassal rebellion. As long as they don’t taunt the Divines, then the Divines wouldn’t care about them. This made the vassal races, who had been suppressed by the Divines, feel strange. They didn’t know what happened. They even thought that the foreign races had sent troops in order to help them break through.

Three days after Zhao Hai destroyed the Connecting Heaven Palace, Elder Star arrived in the Central Continent. At this time, the Central Continent was a land of chaos. All the cities were almost in ruins. In the past, the Central Continent was very lively, but now it was reduced to this state. This made Elder Star pale.

Elder Star’s expression was dark. On the road, he managed to see Divines fighting and carrying out meaningless massacres. Those people seem to have lost their minds.

Although Elder Star wanted them to stop, these people simply couldn’t hear anything. Their eyes were blood red, the only thing they knew right now was murder. They were already beyond help!

After the destruction of the Connecting Heaven Palace, these people went crazy. Some of them even killed their own families. After the anger in their hearts was quenched and they realized what they had done, they turned insane once more.

When he saw this situation, Elder Star knew that the Central Continent had come to its end. Restoring the continent to its former state would be almost impossible. Moreover, the economy and cultural situation of the Central Continent has been turned back at a minimum of 200 years.

Of course, Elder Star wasn’t without harvest. He still met people who were sober. These people were weak and didn’t dare to stay in the cities. They were afraid of those madmen to they could only run to the wild. They haven’t eaten, nor they had any change of clothes. They were having difficulties getting by.

Elder Star couldn’t help but feel helpless when he saw this. In the end, he arranged these people to settle on one of the cities. As for the madmen that were in that city, Elder Star had to steel his heart and kill them all.

Following close behind Elder Star were the other Supreme Elders. They were startled at what the Central Continent had become. They didn’t think that the Central Continent would turn into this wasteland. Their hearts bled for the people, and they were also scared!

The plan was set-up by Elder Star. And although Elder Star was the one who proposed it, it was discussed repeatedly and the Supreme Elders thought that it was perfect. And it wasn’t only because of the Seven Star Heaven Lock, it was also because of the arrangement of the Divines and the Fishmen as well.

The Divine Realm’s Fishman Race survived in the sea for a long time. Moreover, they can command their magic beasts to defend each continent. One could say that there was no way for Zhao Hai to escape their eyes.

However, Zhao Hai actually managed to slip through, and even destroyed the Connecting Heaven Palace. Such skill was something that the Divines didn’t have. Facing this mysterious enemy that was able to appear and disappear at will, the Supreme Elders couldn’t help but feel frightened deep inside.

Zhao Hai only managed to see Elder Star five days after Elder Star arrived at the Central Continent. The reason for this was because Elder Star had been gathering refugees and killing those who had gone insane.

Upon seeing Elder Star, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but jump. The last time he saw Elder Star, the elder still looked like a lordly middle-aged person. He spoke clearly and had a great demeanor.

But now, Elder Star’s appearance was completely different. His hair had almost turned white, his clothes were ragged. He had two blood red eyes and looked thin. He looked crazy and didn’t have his lordly look anymore.

However, Zhao Hai can understand Elder Star’s mood. Elder Star was a native of the Central Continent. After becoming the Supreme Elder, he regarded everyone in the Central Continent as his juniors, his children, his family members. Now that his home has been turned to this, he found it hard to accept it.

Zhao Hai lightly sighed. He didn’t really expect the Central Continent to turn into this. He only attacked the Connecting Heaven Palace because it was the Central Continent’s Imperial Palace. Moreover, Bingya also said that the place was an important landmark. Zhao Hai only wanted to cause panic in the Central Continent, compelling Elder Star to come back. Then Zhao Hai would hide in some place, waiting for a convenient time to make a move.

However, the situation had turned into something that exceeded his imagination. Zhao Hai didn’t expect the reaction to be this severe. The entire continent actually turned frantic upon the destruction of their Connecting Heaven Palace.

Take Divine Gift City for example. When Zhao Hai arrived here, the city was still a bustling hub. But in the past few days, the city basically destroyed itself under Zhao Hai’s watch. Zhao Hai saw the city’s residence destroy their homes bit by bit. They killed their family members, then went insane before killing each other. Even if Zhao Hai had a heart of stone, he still couldn’t look at this calmly. If one compares these people to the captured Taurus Divines, the Taurus Divines would look to be the happy ones.

Although there were Taurus Divines who were killed, only a small number of commoners died. There were still people among the Taurus Divines who had the capacity to hate, and those who can still think about revenge.

On the other hand, the people from the Central Continent were different. They hated Zhao Hai, yes, but after becoming sober, they hated themselves even more. They hated themselves for ruining their homes and killing their families. They couldn’t bear this shock as they just turned insane once more.

Afterwards, Zhao Hai managed to see the other Supreme Elders. These Supreme Elders appeared distressed. However, their complexion was still better compared to Elder Star. After counting nine Supreme Elders, Zhao Hai felt relief.

Laura and the others had also seen what happened. Every time they see a Divine turn crazy, they also couldn’t help but lose a bit of their sanity.

Zhao Hai felt that this wasn’t good, so he sent Laura and the others to the Space. He told them to do something else in order to waste time. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai stayed and looked at the monitor.

When he discovered Elder Star, Zhao Hai immediately called Laura and the others back. But before they arrived, Zhao Hai turned the monitor off.

When Laura and the others came out, they saw Zhao Hai sitting in the living room. There was a bottle of liquor in front of him, the bottle only had half of its contents left.

Zhao Hai was someone who drinks minimally. This was something that Laura and the others knew. After seeing this, they understood that Zhao Hai was also feeling ill. This caused the group to feel bad. Meg immediately went to the kitchen and prepared some good food that would go great with wine. Meanwhile, Laura and the others sat down with him.

Chapter 916: Don’t Offend A Dark Mage!

One couldn’t always do what one likes. There’s always a consequence in every action!

This statement was in Zhao Hai’s mind at this time. He knew that he was in an irreconcilable situation with the Divine Race now. Even if he was willing to give up, the Divines wouldn’t let him off.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t care about murder. But after seeing the current state of the Divines, Zhao Hai was shaken.

Laura and the others were able to understand Zhao Hai’s thoughts. Zhao Hai wasn’t a stone hearted person. Although he was indifferent towards the enemy, he would still have a soft heart for ordinary people.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was sad regarding the current situation. Laura and the others didn’t say anything and just accompanied Zhao Hai. They wanted to let Zhao Hai feel that he wasn’t alone.

At this time, Meg arrived with the side dishes and then placed them on the table. After taking a sip of his wine, Zhao Hai said, “Elder Star and the others have arrived. It seems like the Central Continent would start to calm down soon. Moreover, it seems like they really did have a plan to deal with us. We thought that they had a teleportation device but we were wrong. We still don’t know what method they had prepared for us.”

Laura and the others slightly frowned. The appearance of the group of Supreme Elders meant that they had confidence and means in dealing with Zhao Hai. But what was their plan? It was still a mystery.

Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, aren’t we going to attack the Leo Continent? How about we go through with that plan? If we attack the Leo Continent, then we would be able to see what methods they had prepared. No matter what, they need to use that method sooner or later. When the time comes, wouldn’t we be able to find out?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It seems like that is the only way. Alright, now that Elder Star and the others are here, I guess it’s time to go to the Leo continent.”

The next moment, they already appeared inside the Leo Continent’s Lion River, the continent’s largest river.

Zhao Hai and the others arrived here with the help of the Space. In the past, they entered the Leo Continent through this river. Because of this, the Space already recorded the place down.

After arriving at Lion River, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go and attack the Leo Divines. He knew what his goal was, and that was to attack the place that the Leo Divines hold dear. Only in this way would the Supreme Elders be moved, and only then could Zhao Hai find an opportunity to defeat them.

Zhao Hai and the others walked along the river while observing the situation with the Leo Continent. What Zhao Hai saw was something different from what he imagined. Zhao Hai thought that it was only the Central Continent who had a chaotic result. After all, the attack was made in the Central Continent. Other places shouldn’t be affected.

However, there were some troubles in the Leo Continent as well. But the situation here was much better compared to the Central Continent. Although there were still people who caused trouble, they were still able to be controlled.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai wasn’t sure if he should make a move. It was clear that if he acts now, then that would be the spark that would light a fire on the Leo Continent. At this time, the Leo Continent was like a barrel of gunpowder with a fuse. As long as a spark came in, the barrel would explode.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and frowned. Lizzy and the others looked at the screen as well. After a few moments, the group turned their gazes towards Zhao Hai.

Feeling everybody else’s gaze, Zhao Hai clenched his teeth and said, “We go through!”

Then after that, Zhao Hai went outside and said, “Bingya, come here.”

Bingya and the others stayed inside their room in the past few days. They contacted their clans from time to time, so they knew that the Divine Race army had retreated. This allowed them to feel relief.

Bingya and the others were unable to see the situation outside, so they weren’t aware about what the Central Continent turned into. However, when they saw Zhao Hai’s state, they chose the right decision and just stayed in.

Now that Zhao Hai called him over, Bingya, as well as Ryder and Yehta, immediately ran out. They knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t call them out for no reason. After seeing Zhao Hai, the three couldn’t help but stare. Zhao Hai’s expression was heavy, this caused their hearts to sink. They didn’t know what caused Zhao Hai to be like this.

Zhao Hai looked at the trio and said, “What is the most important place in the Leo Continent? Where should we attack?” Bingya was stunned. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s question. However, Bingya carefully gave his answer, “Mister, did something happen? Isn’t it too risky to attack the Leo Continent? Did Elder Star and the others go to the Central Continent?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Correct, they already arrived there. We’re now in the Leo Continent. Tell me which place to attack.”

Bingya thought for a moment and said, “The Leo Continent is quite special. From what I learned from the family, their most important landmark isn’t their Imperial Palace, but Lion Rock!”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Continue”

Bingya gave a nod, “Lion Rock is a giant tomb where the Leo Emperors are buried as well as the warriors who died for the Continent. It is a place where the spirit of the Leo Continent resides in.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown. He wasn’t a grave digger. However, this target only comprised of dead people, so there weren’t so many murders but in exchange they could plunge the Leo Continent into chaos.

Bingya saw Zhao Hai’s expression and then said, “Aside from Lion Rock, the Imperial Palace is also quite important. However, the palace is heavily guarded. At least, an army is stationed there.”

Zhao Hai looked at Bingya and said, “Where is Lion Rock?”

Bingya responded, “It is 50 kilometers east of Lion Palace. The name of the rock came from how it looks like a Lion lying on the ground. I heard that the Leo Royals bury their Emperors there. At the same time, that is also the place where they bury the brave warriors who defended the Leo Royals.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Where is Lion Palace’s specific location?”

Bingya answered, “Lion Palace is on the east bank of the Lion River. It isn’t close to the River, but there is a satellite city nearby called Thirsty Lion City. If we don’t plan to go to Lion Palace, then we can just continue going along the River to reach the head part of Lion Rock. Its position makes it look like the Lion is drinking by the river.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, “Good, then let’s go and destroyed Lion Rock later today.”

Bingya and the others didn’t dare to say anything. They knew Zhao Hai’s way of doing things, and they also wouldn’t oppose to the idea. Their hatred towards the Divines was too deep. They couldn’t wait to destroy the Divine Race’s grave.

What Zhao Hai and the others didn’t know was the fact that Elder Star and the others were in the Leo Continent during the time they went astray. Luckily, Zhao Hai didn’t think of making a move at that time.

Bingya saw that Zhao Hai’s expression didn’t go any better. On the contrary, Zhao Hai looked distant. In the end, Bingya couldn’t help but ask, “Mister, did something happen?” Zhao Hai looked at Bingya and smiled, “Don’t worry, nothing is wrong. The situation is greatly beneficial to us.”

But Bingya was still confused, “But why is Mister’s expression heavy? I just couldn’t help but think that something bad has happened. Is Mister really fine?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s fine. Go and prepare, we’ll arrive at Lion Rock soon.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Bingya couldn’t help but stare, then he asked, “Mister, we’re nearing Lion Rock? That quick?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course we’re fast. Don’t worry, even if we arrive at Lion Rock, we won’t begin immediately. We’ll do the same as before, we attack at night. This time, I’m planning to turn all the Leo Emperors into undead!”

As soon as Zhao Hai said this, Bingya and the others couldn’t help but shiver in fright. Zhao Hai’s means were too ruthless. It was at this time where they understood why the clan didn’t want to offend Dark Mages. One shouldn’t offend a Dark Mage.

Before long, the Hell King’s ship stopped. Zhao Hai turned to the three and said, “Alright, go and take a rest. We’ve reached Lion Rock. We make our move this evening.” After saying that, Zhao Hai went to return to his room.

Bingya and the others looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. They didn’t know why Zhao Hai was in a bad mood today.

When Zhao Hai returned to his room, Laura and the others immediately went to welcome him. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, will we really turn the skeletons in Lion Rock into undead? Those undead wouldn’t be that strong, they’re quite useless. Even if they are transformed by the Space, their strength could only be as strong as ordinary undead.”

Zhao Hai steeled his heart and said, “Yes, we’ll turn every skeleton there into undead. Moreover, we won’t have the Space improve them and just let them attack the Leo Continent. In any case, the Divines are now our enemy. We need to refrain from showing pity. We need to deal with the Divine Race. After that, there’s still the O’Neal family and the Underworld. Perhaps, we can even use the Divines in the future.”

As soon as they heard this, Laura and the others gawked. Then they began to understand Zhao Hai. It was indeed like what Zhao Hai said. Maybe they can save more people this way.

Chapter 917: This Also Costs Money?

Just like what Zhao Hai said, more people would be saved if the Divines were dealt with much sooner. Zhao Hai was very clear that the Underworld was still encroaching. Although the O’Neal family was present, it would be impossible for them to stop its advance. In this case, the Dark mist would reach the Divine Realm, and that day wouldn’t be too far.

From the moment the Underworld appeared to the present, about one year has passed. But these days, the Dark Mist had already spread towards the Aksu Empire. This speed was nothing short of quick. It would be soon before the O’Neal family would clash with the underworld.

Judging by the speed, the Dark Mist would surely reach the Divine Realm. When that time comes, more people would certainly die in the Divine Realm..

Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting the Divines to deal with the Underworld. The Dark Mist’s expansion was like the law of the heaven and the earth. The Dark Mist suppresses all light while darkness was strengthened by it. In this case, it would be hard for the Divines to deal with the Underworld.

If the Divines fail to deal with the Underworld, then the Divines would get exterminated. With this eventuality, Zhao Hai might as well finish the war as soon as possible. Perhaps he can rescue the Divine commoners and send them to the Space.

After expressing this thought, Laura and the others didn’t speak anything. Attacking Lion Rock at this time was indeed the better choice. This method might have some unexpected effects.

Zhao Hai kept silent and just sat down as he looked at the monitor. Bingya and the others returned to their rooms. They went on to contact their clan for updates. They wanted to find out why Zhao Hai’s mood was terrible.

When Bingya got the result, he finally found out how messed up the Central Continent had become. The vassal races even used this opportunity to grab some territory. However, the Divines didn’t do anything about it.

After knowing this result, Bingya couldn’t help but get shocked. He never expected it to be like this. He immediately called Ryder and Yehta over to his room and told them about the information he received.

When Ryder and Yehta heard Bingya, they were stunned. Then Ryder whispered, “The Central Continent is now under chaos, but why is Mister unhappy?”

Yehta also frowned, she was similarly confused about this matter. Normally, with this outcome, the one who would be the happiest would be Zhao Hai. Instead, Zhao Hai was actually not.

Bingya thought for a moment and said, “I thought of one possibility. It’s possible that Mister is thinking that it’s too excessive. Remember, back in the Taurus Continent, Mister only killed those who dared to rebel. As for the commoners, Mister would just send them to another place using his ability. In the past, I thought Mister just killed them. But now, I realized that he just sent them to another place. This time, the Central Continent’s chaos not only included the soldiers, it affected the commoners as well. It’s possible that Mister didn’t want to see this. Therefore, Mister had a bad mood.”

Yehta and Ryder nodded, they thought that this explanation was reasonable. However, Ryder suddenly saw Bingya frown. He couldn’t help but feel puzzled as he said, “Bingya, what’s wrong?”

Bingya frowned and said, “I always thought that Mister came to the Divine Realm in order to exact revenge. However, with Mister strength, he should have already caused a big mess to the Divine Realm. Why is this the case?”

Ryder and Yehta couldn’t help but frown as well. They had followed Zhao Hai for some time already, so they were very clear about Zhao Hai’s strength. Zhao Hai’s abilities exceeded their explanation. Even if the Supreme Elders were sent in, he still wasn’t compelled to use all of his strength. This was a completely different conduct for someone who wanted revenge. They didn’t think about it before since Zhao Hai had killed a lot of Divines. But after Bingya said this, they also thought that Zhao Hai’s actions were a bit strange. It didn’t look like he was out for revenge.

Zhao Hai wasn’t paying attention to Bingya and the others. After he saw Bingya and the others return to their rooms, Zhao Hai made his move. He commanded his ship and drilled underneath Lion Rock.

Drilling underground wasn’t an easy task, but Zhao Hai was able to find a method.

He used the magic cannons of the Hell King’s ship to shoot at the river, vaporizing the rocks and allowing him to pass through.

Zhao Hai took Bubble back, but the Hell King’s ship didn’t become bigger. Because of this, even if Zhao Hai had disturbed the bottom of Lion River, he didn’t attract any attention.

Zhao Hai slowly moved forward as it penetrated the ground under Lion Rock. Then Zhao Hai stopped, he was waiting until night comes.

The reason why Zhao Hai had the ship go under Lion Rock wasn’t just because he wanted to stage an attack. He also wanted to see if there were any defenses in the vicinity.

Zhao Hai soon discovered that he did the right thing. Although there weren’t a lot of Divines here, there was a huge magic formation surrounding the rock. At the same time, there was an army of 10 thousand Divines stationed at one corner. As soon as there was little movement, they can react immediately.

Moreover, Zhao Hai found out that every other hour, the army would send out 1000 soldiers to survey the area around Lion Rock. One could say that the defense was quite strict.

This place was very deep into the Leo Continent. For the Leo Divines to arrange an army in this place only shows how important Lion Rock was.

But this only caused Zhao Hai’s idea to destroy Lion Rock to be strengthened. With the current atmosphere, the destruction of Lion Rock would surely push the Leo Divines to insanity.

When the Leo Divines go mad, Zhao Hai would benefit no matter which party they decide to attack. If they attack the foreign races and cause the foreign races to be in a dangerous position, then perhaps Zhao Hai can use this opportunity to send the foreign races to the Space.

If the Divines act on the Thunder Clan and the others, then Zhao Hai would choose to entangle them in the Taurus Continent. After that, Zhao Hai could use the Divines to pressure the Thunder Clan and the others. This way, they might be compelled to move into the Space. No matter which move the Divines make, Zhao Hai’s move this time would be worth it.

After knowing about the defense situation of Lion Rock, Zhao Hai moved on and carefully examined the defensive formation. When Zhao Hai saw this formation, he couldn’t help but pause. This magic formation didn’t follow the convention used by the other formations of the Divine Race.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t skilled in magic formations, he had a lot of interactions with them in the past few days. In this case, he had some understanding with regards to them. Moreover, defensive formations were the most commonly used formations, making Zhao Hai even more familiar.

And even if there were a lot of defensive formations in the Divine Realm, Zhao Hai found out that those defensive formations were the most basic types. At the most, there were more complicated ones but they can still be readable.

Meanwhile, the magic formation on Lion Rock was something that Zhao Hai had never seen before. This formation comprised of several formation disks. From what Zhao Hai counted, there were eight disks in this formation.

Zhao Hai looked at the eight positions carefully. He found that their placement seemed to be very new and was arranged not too long ago.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get curious. He immediately made Cai’er record the formation and sent it to the scanner to be analyzed.

When the formation went out of the building, the scanner immediately issued a sound, “Because formation is higher than Host’s level, asking Host to pay 1 million gold coins!”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. He didn’t think that the scanner would have this ability, moreover it also asked for payment.

Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, how does this work? Why does the scanner require money? If the formation is higher than my level, then wouldn’t it just say nothing? Just like the combat suits?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, it seems like you didn’t read the Universal Scanner’s description. The scanner can also improve itself. And since you are the host, the scanner would cater to your convenience. You are level 85 now, as long as the item is less than 50 levels above you, then you can spend money in order to analyze it.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect it to be like this. He nodded and said, “So it’s like that. I didn’t read the description properly. Good, then scan it immediately!” In any case, Zhao Hai wasn’t short on money. One million gold coins was only a small number to him. Naturally, he wouldn’t want to miss this opportunity.

After the scanner has been ordered, it immediately deducted 1 million gold coins from Zhao Hai’s account. It didn’t take long after that for a response to come out, “The original formation is a Cultivation Civilization trap. Formation has eight disks altogether, one main disk and seven sub-disks. If someone unknowingly enters the formation, then they would be trapped for up to 56 days. Host can print the formation and methods of cracking it. Suggesting host to find the genuine formation disk and combine it with the Hell King’s ship in order to oppose the enemy!”

Chapter 918: Strange Undead

Valuable!

Too valuable! Spending those 1 million gold coins was extremely worth it!

This was the only thing that was booming in Zhao Hai’s mind this time. He never imagined the scanner to be this powerful. It even gave the method to break the formation. For Zhao Hai, this was too important.

The information about the formation and the method to break it was too precious for Zhao Hai. At this time, he didn’t have too much knowledge regarding the Cultivation Realm, especially formations.

From Lu Wei’s fragment, Zhao Hai learned that formations were very important in the Cultivation Realm.

It was almost impossible to leave a formation. Moreover, the magic formations of the Cultivation Realm were fundamentally different compared to the ones that Zhao Hai had seen before. If Zhao Hai ascends to the Cultivation Realm, then the enemy could surely use magic arrays in order to deal with him.

This formation’s appearance was an absolutely good thing for Zhao Hai. This would allow him to better understand the formations of the Cultivation Realm.

In the past, Zhao Hai was able to gain items from the Cultivation Realm. Both the Pagoda and the Hell King’s ship were items that Zhao Hai stole. They also had formations inside them, but they were too complex, Zhao Hai had no way to use them. It was like having a primary school kid write a university level thesis.

But this time, the magic formation wasn’t that complex. It could be said that this formation was a very common one. Most importantly, the Space was able to give the method to set it up as well as how to break it. This information were very useful in studying formations.

Additionally, the scanner also mentioned that this formation had formation disks, which were made from Cultivation Realm materials. For these materials to combine with the Hell King’s ship was good news for Zhao Hai. The Hell King’s ship wasn’t all-powerful. Once Zhao Hai arrives at the Cultivation Realm, he would need to survive. This was something that Zhao Hai cared the most about.

Zhao Hai quickly said, “Print it, immediately print it out.”

The Space’s prompt wasn’t only heard by Zhao Hai, Laura and the others were able to hear it as well and they were glad. They had been with Zhao Hai for a long time, naturally they knew what would be good for him.

Lizzy quickly turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, do you think that this is the method the Divines prepared for us? It’s obvious that the formation is quite new. Even if they can only hold us for a few days, Elder Star would be able to come and kill us.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “That seems to be so. But how could they be sure that the formation would be able to trap us? This newly made formation seems to be unable to do 100% of its strength.”

At this time, Cai’er came in and said, “Young Master, here are the printed pages.” Held in her arms were a stack of papers.

Zhao Hai quickly received the stack of papers and carefully examined it. When he saw that the formation could be used separately, he immediately confirmed that this formation was prepared for him.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Lizzy and smiled, “Lizzy, it seems like you’re correct. This formation is a set called the Seven Star Heaven Lock. It’s certain that the Divines had prepared this for us. What a pity, back when we attacked the Connecting Heaven palace, we didn’t look carefully. Perhaps we might be able to find a Seven Star Heaven Lock formation disk.”

After saying that, he handed the stack of papers over to Lizzy. Lizzy looked at it and nodded, “It seems like this formation was given by Lu Wei to Elder Star.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “But now these formations are useless to us, they might as well be decoration. Later on, we can get the disks and integrate them into the Hell King’s ship.”

Laura faintly smiled, “I think there should be an original disk in the Leo Continent. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be able to make full use of the formation. We should look for it here.” Zhao Hai thought about it but he shook his head and said, “Forget it, our main goal now is to cause chaos to the Divines. If we take too long in the Leo Continent, it’s very likely that Elder Star would be able to react. In any case, with those things in Elder Star’s hand, we should be able to get them soon.”

Laura nodded and said, “That is also a good idea. Tonight, we’ll give the Divines a good surprise.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. However, his expression turned ice-cold. Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about the Divines right now, instead, he was thinking about Lu Wei.

The Divines have Lu Wei as their backer. If Lu Wei couldn’t stop Zhao Hai here, then he would surely make his move in the Cultivation Realm.

The skies slowly went dark. Just like before, Zhao Hai was very patient and didn’t immediately make a move. At the same time, Zhao Hai wanted to see how the army acts when night came.

It didn’t take long for Zhao hai to discover that the army’s situation was also quite good at night. While they would send a patrol every hour during the day, during the night, they send patrols twice every hour. Other than that, everything else was the same.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the Hell King’s ship. But at the same time, he ordered the ship’s cannons to begin firing up towards Lion Rock.

During the daytime, Zhao Hai saw that the Lion Rock was a mountain covered with a forest on top. This made Lion Rock look like a green lion.

Unlike what Zhao Hai imagined before, the tomb wasn’t built on top of Lion Rock. Instead, the tomb was made inside a cavern carved out inside the mountain.

Lion Rock was quite special. Although it was on water, the flow just stopped outside. The cavern that was carved out was very dry. After the Leo Divines carved the mountain up, they proceeded to build the tomb inside. The tomb was decorated luxuriously, it was like a palace inside. Inside the tomb were a few coffins. The coffins were made out of fine white stone. Zhao Hai knew that this stone was a kind of radiant mineral, completely suitable for light attribute magic. In the Divine Realm, it was quite a precious mineral.

In the middle of the tomb were two coffins made out of this radiant stone. These two coffins were made of big and small stones. One looked sharp and angular, giving one a strong and hardened aura. The other had rounded corners, giving a soft feeling. These two coffins were in the very center of the tomb. The two coffins were propped up by a platform made entirely out of radiant stone. The platform was carved beautifully, making it the the main structure of the tomb.

Below these two main coffins were the other coffins. These coffins revolved around the two coffins.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai could deduce that inside the two coffins were the two most respected members of the Leo Imperial Clan. The other coffins were their children.

Outside the Imperial tomb were more coffins. The materials of those coffins weren’t as good. Some of them were made of gold, some were silver, while some were bronze. There were also more coffins further out made from iron and wood. The materials probably referred to the owners’ status.

Because of this, it took Zhao Hai quite a long time before reaching the the tomb. Zhao Hai had the ship fire as he made a passage leading to the tomb.

Making the passage wasn’t for Zhao Hai. He had the passage made in order for his magic to go through. Zhao Hai planned to send the underworld’s dark mist into the passage and see what the result would be.

The Underworld’s dark mist had the ability to turn dead people into undead. Zhao Hai wanted to see how long the dark mist would turn these skeletons into undead.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t planning to go all out with his cannons. That would make too much sound, alerting the people outside. Zhao Hai didn’t want to make his presence known. Because of this, Zhao Hai adjusted the power of his cannons to be low, just enough to drill a hole while making the least sound.

At around 9 pm, the magic cannons finally made a connection to the tomb. This passage wasn’t very big, it could only allow a big mouse to go through.

Zhao Hai immediately fed the dark mist into the passage. He had the dark mist enter the passage and go into the tomb.

The Dark Mist entered the passage and began to get thicker and thicker. Before long, the wooden coffins rocked slowly as each skeleton got up. After that, the iron coffins were next, then the bronze coffins, then the silver coffins, and the the gold ones.

But when the dark mist met the tombs made out of radiant stone, it began to experience difficulties. The radiant stone seems to have a resistance towards the dark mist. When the dark mist met the coffin, the radiant stone began to light up pushing the dark mist away.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he frowned. He didn’t expect that the radiant stones were able to block the dark mist of the Underworld. If this was the case, then the Divines might be able to defeat the Underworld.

While he was thinking about this, Laura suddenly said, “Brother Hai, quick, look!”

Zhao Hai quickly turned to look at the monitor. What he saw made him shocked. The dark mist seemed to be irritated. It rolled and smashed towards the radiant stone, causing it to become weaker and weaker. Before long, the repelling light disappeared and the dark mist surrounded the coffin.

Soon after that, the coffins shook as skeletons came out one by one. These skeletons were quite tall and the clothes they wore were very magnificent.

However, there were also some differences on the clothes they wore. Although some were wearing white robes, there were some who wore armor and some just wore ordinary Divine Race clothes.

What made Zhao Hai surprised were the two coffins in the middle of the tomb. It seems like they weren’t affected by what was happening around them. They remained motionless, not moving at all.

As Zhao Hai was thinking that the two skeletons were already turned into dust, the two coffins began to move. The rocking became more and more violent until the cover of the two coffins flew out and smashed into the ground.

After that, four pure white bony hands extended from the coffins as two people slowly sat up. It only took one glance for people to see that the two skeletons were of a man and a woman. Both of them wore beautifully made white long gowns. Embroidered on their gowns were golden lions. The man had a lion on his gown while the woman had a lioness.

Then something out of Zhao Hai’s expectation happened. After the two skeletons sat up, they simultaneously stood up and walked together hand in hand.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai and the others were dumbfounded. But regardless of what they were thinking, the two skeletons continued to move.

One must know that Zhao Hai didn’t use any magic. Instead, he just released the Underworld’s Dark Mist. From what Zhao Hai can remember, although the Dark Mist had formidable abilities, it couldn’t grant wisdom to the undead. In other words, the undead would be just like puppets.

However, from what Zhao Hai could see, this doesn’t seem to be the case. Not only were these undead quite strong, they seem to have awareness. What was the meaning of this?”

As Zhao Hai was puzzled, another event happened. After seeing the two skeletons that were holding hands, the other undead suddenly bowed down. It was as if they had seen their king!

This startled Zhao Hai and the others once more. Then Zhao Hai’s expression changed. It can be said that it was Zhao Hai who turned them into undead. If they were able to give respects, then it should be towards Zhao Hai. So how could these undead bow down to the two skeletons? Were these undead not under the control of Zhao Hai?

Chapter 919: Heart Bond!

The undead can overthrow their masters. Such matters had occurred even back in the Ark Continent. If the Undead was stronger than its master, then it could wrestle control even if they were bound by some law.

When Zhao Hai saw the undead act like this, he couldn’t help but think about this situation.

However, Zhao Hai still felt a bit strange about this. He didn’t understand how this could happen. The Dark Mist of the Underworld could turn people into undead, but the undead wouldn’t be smart. Undead were divided into different kinds. The most common undead were the ones that Zhao Hai was using. They were just people being turned into undead. Since these people haven’t died for a long time, their flesh and blood can still be absorbed into their bones. Because of this, the undead were still able to preserve most of their strength.

The second type of undead were those who had died for a long time. After a long time, the corpses would decompose, only leaving the bones behind. At this time, there wouldn’t be any blood and flesh left to absorb, causing the skeleton to be weak. Therefore, these kinds of undead became the weakest types.

Since Zhao Hai was only using the undead in Lion Rock to cause chaos, he didn’t care if they were strong or not. Zhao Hai wanted to let the Leo Divines know that he had desecrated their Lion Rock, causing them to be mad.

But now, the situation caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled. However, when Zhao Hai was beginning to calm down, he understood that the undead didn’t break his control. This was because every time the undead wanted to leave the control of their masters, the master would immediately suffer injuries. One of the more severe cases were the masters completely losing their senses, directly turning into people with no sense of self.

Zhao Hai discovered that he wasn’t harmed at all. One should know that Zhao Hai was the one who released the Dark Mist. Although it was the Dark Mist of the Underworld, it was a dark mist that was reformed by the Space. The dark mist carried Zhao Hai’s imprint, which essentially meant that it was Zhao Hai’s dark mist. If these undead really got out of Zhao Hai’s control, then Zhao Hai would have been injured; but he wasn’t.

Zhao Hai looked at the undead and then appeared inside the tomb. He wanted to see what was going on.

While Laura and the others were still startled at the scene, they suddenly discovered that Zhao Hai appeared on the monitor. This caused their expressions to change. They were afraid that the undead might attack Zhao Hai.

However, the matter actually went opposite to what they expected. When Zhao Hai appeared inside the tomb, the two skeletons immediately turned towards Zhao Hai and proceeded to kneel.

Zhao Hai loosened up and waved his hand, making the two undead stand up. Then Zhao Hai tested the two undead with his spiritual force to see if they can communicate.

This communication allowed Zhao Hai to know the identity of these two people. These people weren’t simple, they were the first generation monarchs of the Leo Continent. Additionally, they have another status, cultivators from the Cultivation Realm.

However, they weren’t especially strong cultivators. They were young trainee pharmacists in their own sect. In the Cultivation Realm, each sect would have their own Pill Divisions. Pill-making always went hand-in-hand with martial cultivation. Almost every cultivator would take pills in some point in their lives. There were a lot of pills in the Cultivation Realm, but the most common of them were pills that increase cultivation.

Each sect would find children who were skilled in pharmacy and teach them simple refining methods. After that, the sects would provide them with medicine furnaces and give them some pill-making knowledge. When those children grew up, they would become qualified pharmacists.

The two skeletons studied pill-making at a very young age. When they were about ten years old, an enemy sect  suddenly went to attack their sect. While the two groups were fighting, the two ten year olds were spectating them inside the Pill Division. Then all of a sudden, the two sides made a huge attack on each other, causing a spatial crack to appear. Naturally, the strong experts were fine. But the two weak ten-year olds actually fell into the crack, ending up in the Divine Realm.

When they arrived in the Divine Realm, the place where they fell into was the Leo Continent. Later on, they were rescued by an old soul, a wealthy merchant. They also found that the Divine Realm was very different compared to the Cultivation Realm. Therefore, they didn’t dare to reveal their true identity.

The two were young pill-makers. Their refining talents were very good, but their cultivation talent wasn’t.

However, after arriving in the Divine Realm, they had found out that they were very rare cultivation talents. Moreover, Battle Qi and Magic that was practiced here wasn’t too different to the most basic skills that a cultivator would learn. Therefore, the two just went to cultivate according to what they learned and then ended up as the rulers of the Leo Continent.

But although their cultivation was quite good, they didn’t get too far in their cultivation since the heaven and earth aura of the Divine Realm wasn’t sufficient. In the end, the two weren’t able to ascend to the Cultivation Realm and finally passed away in the Leo Continent.

At the same time, the two were also able to find out that the Divine Realm was ruled by a cultivator. However, they didn’t dare to reveal their identity. They knew that if their identity as cultivators were to be known, then they would be hunted down and killed. Because of this, they brought this secret with them to the grave.

At that time, their descendants and most trusted people were able to learn some cultivation methods of the Cultivation Realm. These methods of cultivation placed great importance to one’s own body. This caused these people to have bodies that were more formidable compared to the other Divines in the Divine Realm.

And before the two died, they also arranged for this tomb to be built. There wasn’t much on this tomb other than an array that would keep a physical body intact for a very long time. In general, a body would survive here for a millenium without rotting. At the same time, the flesh and blood would also slowly integrate with the bones, leaving a skeleton that was much stronger compared to others.

Now, Zhao Hai turned them into undead. Although Zhao Hai used the Underworld’s Dark Mist, this dark mist was improved by the Space. This allowed the dark mist to preserve an undead’s wisdom.

If it was any ordinary person, then their spiritual wisdom might have already dissipated. However, the people on this tomb were different. Since their bodies had united with their skeletons, their wisdom got preserved. This explains why, after being turned into undead, the skeletons still had the mind to kneel upon seeing the two undead cultivators. They were still aware that the two were their ancestor kings.

Although the two were already turned into skeleton and couldn’t be identified using their faces, their garments alone described their status. Most importantly, the division between undead were very strict. Therefore, the undead immediately bent their knees upon seeing the two.

After coming to know about this, Zhao Hai relaxed. Although these undead were able to preserve their wisdom, they were still loyal towards him.

However, there was still one thing that made Zhao Hai quite confused. There should be no feelings between undead creatures. Even if they stood in front of their parents or children, their sentiment towards each other should have ended after they died.

So this begs the reason why the two undead immediately held hands together after being resurrected?

Zhao Hai asked the two undead about this and immediately got his answer. The answer made Zhao Hai stare. The two undead casted a spell on each other when they were still alive, and the spell was called ‘Heart Bond’!

This spell wasn’t a Divine Realm spell, it came from the Cultivation Realm. They unintentionally learned this spell back when they were young. But due to their small age, they didn’t know what the spell represented. However, when the two became married, they realized what Heart Bond really was.

Heart Bond was a spell that manifests all throughout the caster’s life. The casters needed to be a man and a woman, and they need to be in love with each other otherwise the spell would not work. This spell was quite special. Once one party became injured and was about to die, the other person can use this technique in order to make the injured recover in an instant. However, this action would cause the healthy party to lose half of their life force. It was a very overbearing spell.

Actually, the two had a chance to ascend. However, the woman was injured in a fight once. In order to treat his partner, the man used Heart Bond’s effect.

The woman recovered but this reduced the man’s life force. After this event, neither of the two were able to ascend.

In addition to healing, Heart Bond also had another feature. Once one of the casters die, the other cannot live. Moreover, even after they died, the two were still affected by the spell. Never in their whole life, and death, would the two be separated.

After hearing this spell, Zhao Hai became very curious. He immediately asked the two for the spell’s details. Since the two were now Zhao Hai’s subordinates, they immediately told him everything. Not only the spell, they also divulged some pill-making information as well as things about the Cultivation Realm.

Chapter 920: Too Hateful!

Zhao Hai sat inside his room and looked at the monitor. He took a token from his staff and handed it over to the two undead cultivators. The two were already famous in the Divine Realm, however, Zhao Hai wanted to know them by their names in the Cultivation Realm, Qing Feng, and Mingyue!

At this time, Qing Feng and Mingyue were bringing the undead to head out of the tomb. Zhao Hai increased their strengths while turning their coffins into weapons. The bronze and iron coffins were made into weapons while the silver and gold coffins were stored in the Space.

Zhao Hai was a frugal person, so how could he just waste silver and gold. Because of this, the weapons equipped by the undead were all iron and bronze weapons.

As Zhao Hai got stronger and stronger, his control over metals became greater and greater as well. HIs divergent ability was actually good for combat. However, since the weapons of the opponents were always covered with battle qi, using metals to fight was generally useless.

Zhao Hai spectated the undead as they attacked the military encampment. The undead inside was beyond what Zhao Hai expected. Inside the tomb were nearly 100 thousand undead, all of them powerful experts when they were alive. The weakest of them were at full god-rank. Moreover, there was Qing Feng and Mingyue, two ascendant-level experts back when they were alive.

And with the formation that Qingfeng and Mingyue used in the tomb, the flesh and blood of the undead were integrated into their skeletons. This allowed them to preserve their strength. This caused the near 100 thousand undead to have incredible strength.

Qing Feng and Mingye were now at the foot of the mountain, getting ready to attack the army. But as they got close, the camp’s alarm suddenly activated, alerting the entire army camp.

Because of what happened in the Central Continent, the nerves of the other Divines were quite tight. Now that the alarm had sounded out, the soldiers immediately jumped up at the fastest speed, they grabbed their weapons and ran out without even wearing their armors. They didn’t have time to.

The soldiers in the compound were getting extremely alert. The magic lamps in the compound were now being lit up, allowing them to see the scenery inside and outside. What they saw startled each and every one of them.

They were all soldiers, elites at that. They could see the number of their enemies in just a glance. Therefore, upon heading out of their camp, they immediately knew that they were surrounded by no less than ten thousand undead.

While the soldiers were stunned, the undead were already rushing over. The soldiers were surprised because they felt that the clothes the undead wore were quite strange.

A lot of these undead were dressed like noble Divines. Moreover, some of them were wearing ancient robes. Nevertheless, the undead looked gorgeous, causing the soldiers to feel very strange.

Just as the soldiers were preparing to clash with the enemy, the undead’s strength surprised them once more. All of the undead were God-rank.

Carvalho stood in the center of the compound as he inspected the undead. The clothes on these undead seemed to have been worn for a long time, and their style was very old. However, the weapons that they were using looked newly made, this puzzled him.

Then suddenly, Carvalho noticed where these undead were coming from. They could be seen coming out of Lion Rock.

Carvalho looked at Lion Rock as his expression changed. He looked at the undead carefully before he suddenly spotted an armored undead. Carvalho’s eyes focused even more before it flashed an ominous light. He immediately turned to his subordinates and commanded loudly, “Brothers, join me, we need to kill our way out!”

Carvalho’s command made the others soldiers stare. These people weren’t Carvalho’s subordinates for a day or two. They knew Carvalho and were very loyal to him. However, his order this time was not something they expected to come out of his mouth.

One must know that guarding Lion Rock was an important matter for the Leo Divines. Moreover, the Leo Clan had an order that was specifically directed at the troops guarding Lion Rock. Fleeing during battle is punishable with nine generations execution!

This meant that once you are assigned to Lion Rock, you will die in battle there. Once you flee, then 9 generations of your family would be killed.

This was the order that caused the soldiers to feel confused at Carvalho’s order. Upon seeing the strength of the undead, the soldiers were already prepared to die here. They understood that if they retreat, then their families would be implicated. But if they die here, then their families might be protected.

Carvalho immediately knew what the soldiers were thinking, after all, they were long time friends. However, Carvalho commanded once more, “Brothers, I couldn’t promise anything, but we need to head out of this place. This matter is related to the fate of our Leo Continent. Quick, gather together!”

Zhao Hai sat on his room and looked at Carvalho. He knew that Carvalho had already guessed what was happening. But instead of impeding Carvalho’s escape, Zhao Hai wanted to release him in order to spread the information regarding what happened to Lion Rock.

Carvalho’s men chose to believe in him, so they immediately grouped up and proceeded to rush out.

But when Carvalho’s group went on to clash with the undead, they suddenly discovered that the undead weren’t as powerful as they thought. Although Carvalho lost about half of his people, they still managed to escape.

After the clash, Carvalho quickly rushed towards Thirsty Lion City. Carvalho knew that Thirsty Lion City was a satellite of Lion City. Because of that, there were a lot of defenders there that could block the undead. Moreover, he also needs the city to send a signal back to Lion City, asking for reinforcements.

At the thought of this, Carvalho’s mood improved. He turned his head and glanced coldly at the slowly retreating undead.

At this time, an aide beside Carvalho said, “General, where did those undead come from?”

Carvalho smiled bitterly, he didn’t know how to answer. He was very clear that those undead were their buried ancestors inside Lion Rock. If this news was spread to the continent, then its effect would be resounding. Since he knew what the outcome would be, he thought twice about informing his men.

Carvalho’s aide looked at him and said, “General? What’s wrong?”

Carvalho sighed, he didn’t have the guts to hide the truth from his brothers, so he whispered, “Those undead came from Lion Rock. I’m certain that this is Zhao Hai’s doing.”

The aide froze for a moment, then he said, “Lion Rock? Why would they come from Lion Rock? General, you mean, Zhao Hai is here? The one we are at war with?”

Carvalho looked at his subordinate and sighed, “I’m 80% sure. Remember the clothes that those undead wore. Although we still wear robes up to this time, our style changed a lot. However, the robes worn by those undead seem to be from ancient times. Additionally, they appeared near Lion Rock. I’m quite sure that Zhao Hai went to Lion Rock and turned our ancestors into undead!”

Upon hearing this, the aide’s eyes turned blood red, “Zhao Hai went too far! I will tear him to pieces!”

Carvalho calmly replied, “Zhao Hai is truly an archenemy of the Divine Race. If we don’t deal with him, then the Divines would be in peril” At this time, flames suddenly flashed outside Thirsty Lion City, the reinforcements have come. Carvalho immediately went forward and said, “May I meet the general? This one is Lion Rock’s General Carvalho.”

The opposite party gave way before a voice was heard, “Carvalho, you brat, you want to die do you? How dare you run away from the camp! Tsk, tell me what happened.” As the voice came in, a huge figure appeared in front of the reinforcing army.

Upon seeing this person, Carvalho began to loosen up. He quickly replied, “Kale, you old fatty. Don’t waste any time and come over to help us. I have an important matter to see his Majesty. This is a matter of the Leo Continent’s life and death. We need to be careful.”

It’s clear that the opposite party was a friend judging by the jokes they threw at each other. The reinforcing army immediately planned to head towards Lion Rock to surround it. At the same time, scouts were also sent in to see the situation at Lion Rock.

As the reinforcing general reached Carvalho, the latter turned his head and said, “Kale, let your people retreat, it’s useless. Come with me to Lion City, we need to report this matter to His Majesty.”

It’s obvious that Kale trusted Carvalho’s decision, so he looked at him and said, “Alright, let’s go immediately.” After that, he commanded his people to stay put while also recalling the scouts.

At this time, Carvalho’s aide reminded him, “General, we need this to be hidden from as many people as possible. It’s best to have an encirclement around Lion Rock just to make sure nobody goes there.”

When he heard this, Carvalho stared for a moment before he nodded and said, “Alright, go send people to surround Lion Rock. Make sure nobody approaches the area. However, make sure to keep a safe distance.”

Chapter 921: A Change In Temperament!

Although Kale didn’t fully understand everything, he still decided to trust Carvalho.

The order was passed, but the reason why he believed Carvalho was because Carvalho managed to save his life during the time they were in a unit together. This allowed Kale to give Carvalho his unconditional trust.

After giving the order, Kale looked at Carvalho and said, “Carvalho, what happened to Lion Rock? How could it be this serious?”

Carvalho turned to Kale and said, “Zhao Hai is here!”

Kale stared, then he said, “Zhao Hai? What is his relationship with Lion Rock?…. Wait, the undead! Are those Zhao Hai’s doing?”

Carvalho nodded and said, “Right, I’ve seen the undead. They’re from Lion Rock!”

Kale’s eyes turned blood red. He looked straight at Carvalho and said, “I remember that your family’s ancestors have been buried in Lion Rock. Are they among the undead?”

Carvalho’s eyes turned ominous as he nodded and said, “I have seen the ancestor, but he doesn’t know me.” The volume of the two wasn’t that small, allowing those around them to hear. When they heard Carvalho, they were astonished before their expression was changed to anger. But Kale and Carvalho didn’t care about it.

It was just like what Zhao Hai said, the emotions of the Leo Divines were like a barrel of gunpowder. As long as a small spark comes, then it would immediately blow up. Even the calm soldiers would have a change of expression, much less anybody else.

Carvalho wanted to restrict the spread of this information. But just as he was made to tell Kale, other people would have to tell other people as well. In the end, it wouldn’t take long before Lion Rock’s matter would spread throughout the Leo continent.

Meanwhile, Qing Feng and Mingyue led the undead to enter the Hell King’s ship and occupy the undead cabins. There were plenty of other undead here, but Zhao Hai sent them to the Space in order to make room.

Qing Feng and Mingyue’s group of undead were the most powerful ones that Zhao Hai had. Naturally, Zhao Hai would have them follow him to enhance his own strength. Zhao Hai couldn’t use his full power, and Qing Feng and Mingyue’s appearance just supplemented that shortcoming..

At this time, Carvalho and Kale were heading towards Lion City. They wanted to inform the Leo Emperor about Zhao Hai’s presence in the Continent as soon as possible. Their aim was to solve this issue as quickly as possible.

Zhao Hai wasn’t finished, after he took care of the undead, he directed the Hell King’s ship to go under Lion Rock once more. He must destroy Lion Mountain and make it known to the Leo Divines that he was the one who did it. He wanted to make sure that this matter wouldn’t be hidden.

Shaking the foundation of Lion Rock wasn’t difficult for Zhao Hai. He had plenty of undead as well as numerous iron armor beasts. If he wanted to destroy something, then that would be an easy matter.

Just as Zhao Hai was about to begin demolishing Lion Rock, the Leo soldiers also began to surround the place. Naturally, they wouldn’t be able to enclose the entire mountain. They just stationed themselves at crucial points to make sure that nobody enters the area.

The soldiers were still clueless about what happened in Lion Rock since they weren’t given much information other than the Carvalho’s order.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite, he immediately released a large number of undead and iron armor beasts to begin excavating Lion Rock. They dug holes in the mountain in preparation for collapsing it in one go.

Presently, Zhao Hai had hundreds of millions of undead. It wouldn’t be hard for these undead to dig up a huge mountain. Moreover, these undead were God-rank, they could just use Earth Element magic in order to excavate quickly.

At this time, Zhao Hai was sitting inside the Hell King’s ship. He was looking at the ongoing excavation that was happening in Lion Rock. It was only after a while did he call Qing Feng over in order to tell him about his cultivation method.

Although Qing Feng and Mingyue studied the most basic cultivation method, it was still much better compared to magic and battle qi. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to learn it for himself.

Laura and the others were also by Zhao Hai’s side, looking at the cultivation method. After taking a glance at it, Zhao Hai said, “Really mysterious. It’s more delicate compared to battle qi and magic. If we practice according to this method, then we could control our strength more freely. Moreover, our abilities would get a huge increase.”

Laura nodded, “Right, I can’t believe that this is  just a basic cultivation method. Currently, we could still fight with the strongest people in the Divine Realm. But if we face people who used this cultivation method, then we might encounter a few problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, I’ll leave you to observe the undead. As long as the excavation is done, topple Lion Rock. Meanwhile, I will try to practice this cultivation method. I want to see what effects it may have.”

When Laura heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but look at him and said, “Brother Hai, are you sure? Practicing those methods seem to be risky. You should wait.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’ll be fine. Sooner or later, we’ll be entering the Cultivation Realm. The situation there is different from what we have right now. A good basic cultivation method can give you a good foundation. I have already asked Qing Feng, he said that their sect was quite famous in the Cultivation Realm. Their basic cultivation methods are quite well-known as well. Therefore, there shouldn’t be any risks practicing their cultivation method. I’ll practice this first to gain some experience. Later on, you’ll cultivate as well. Also, Cai’er will be with me, there’s no need to worry.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura knew that any further persuasion would be useless. Therefore, she just nodded and said, “Alright, but you need to be careful.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he nodded at the women and proceeded to enter his room.

Inside his room, Zhao Hai immediately sat cross legged and went along with the instructions stated in the cultivation manual. The instructions weren’t that complex, but Zhao Hai still had some difficulties. The cultivation method was harder to practice than any battle qi manual that Zhao Hai has ever seen.

However, Zhao Hai was still confident that he would be able to practice well. One shouldn’t forget, Zhao Hai was already on the boundary. His strength had already reached a stage where he would have to ascend to the Cultivation Realm. This cultivation method would just serve to refine his own energy.

To Zhao Hai, practicing this cultivation method was just like perfecting a half-completed work, not adding something new.

And even if the cultivation method wasn’t able to perfect Zhao Hai’s strength, at the very least  it could still chisel his strength into a more appropriate form. As for what his strength would turn into, then it was up to Zhao Hai to find out later on.

It didn’t take long for Zhao Hai to practice the cultivation method. He was now going along the routes that the method had described.

Upon completing one cycle of the cultivation method, Zhao Hai was suddenly startled. The cultivation method actually managed to stabilize his strength, making Zhao Hai tranquil, calming his mental state.

At the same time, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get startled at how his strength became more formidable. Because of this, the heaven and earth’s suppression on him began to strengthen. This might be dangerous for average people. But for Zhao Hai, it was still within controllable range. Moreover, Zhao Hai knew that after ending his cultivation his strength would begin to calm down, lessening the pressure on him.

When he was finished practicing the cultivation method, Zhao Hai felt that his body start to become calm, even the laws had lessened their rejection. Zhao Hai let out a sigh of relief, he finally felt how profound the cultivation method was.

Zhao Hai slowly opened his eyes and let out a long breath. It can be clearly seen that his temperament had undergone a change. It can be said that Zhao Hai had no presence before, he was just like an invisible person. But now, his presence had become very clear.

Zhao Hai was like an envoy of peace as he just stood there. He gave people the feeling of meeting a gentle breeze, soft, warm, and amicable. His magic robe also accentuated this image.

Although the robe was black, there was no evil feeling emanating out of Zhao Hai. Instead, it gave a sense of maturity and stability. A sage-like person!!

If someone were to describe the Zhao Hai right now with four words, then it would be ‘A sage-like person’ These four characters described Zhao Hai’s current appearance.

Zhao Hai’s two eyes looked very peaceful and distant, evoking a sense of mystery about him. Once you stare at them, one would be lost. His skin looked like radiant stones. Just by standing there, Zhao Hai looked like he was one with the world.

Zhao Hai didn’t know the changes to his temperament. He just felt like he was never as calm as this in the past. The laws around him seem to calm down as well and wasn’t rejecting him as much before.

Zhao Hai knew that this was because of how his energy has been transformed. As soon as he begins to use his powers, then the laws would heavily reject him once more. This was because his strength was something that shouldn’t exist in this realm.

But even if Zhao Hai’s temperament had calmed down, this didn’t mean that his judgement has been affected. He still had matters to attend to, people to kill. He wouldn’t be lenient. His temperament was only changed because of the cultivation method.

Zhao Hai looked at the time, one hour had passed. He smiled faintly as he walked out of his room. Upon heading out, Zhao Hai saw Laura and the others staring at the screen. Lion rock was seen on the screen. At this time, Lion Rock was already turned to dust, thoroughly collapsed.

Zhao Hai saw this and smiled, “We’re almost done here.”

When they heard this, Laura and the others immediately turned their heads. When the saw Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but get stunned, every single one of their expressions was shock.

Zhao Hai found their expressions strange, so he asked, “What’s wrong? Did something happen to me?”

When Laura heard this, she couldn’t help but laugh. Then she went to Zhao Hai and grabbed his hand, “Brother Hai, there’s nothing wrong. But you seem to look better compared to before.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. Then he smiled and said, “Look better than before? Why, was I ugly? Or did I become more attractive?”

Megan chuckled as she ran to Zhao Hai and grabbed his other arm, “You looked good before. But you also didn’t become more handsome. Your temperament just changed, you seem more mature now compared to before. Brother Hai, we need to make an agreement. You’re not allowed to see women outside alone anymore. Otherwise, those women would be swept up by you.”

When Lizzy and the others heard Megan, they couldn’t help but chuckle as well. Zhao Hai loudly laughed and said, “Is that so? Did my charisma improve? Alright, you go practice the cultivation method as well. When you’re all done, you will become the same as me.”

Meg smiled and said, “It looks like the cultivation method is very good. How did the cultivation go, Brother Hai? Did you have problems? Is it difficult?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It wasn’t too difficult. The cultivation method is very easy. All of you should be able to succeed. Alright, no need to stare at me. After you finish, go to the Space and give the cultivation method to Grandpa Green and the others. I reckon it would be helpful for them.”

Laura and the others nodded before they took a copy of the cultivation method and went to practice. Zhao Hai knew that the cultivation method would be good for Grandpa Green and the others because he noted that the method was of Daoist origin. Moreover, it was a moderate and peaceful method.

This kind of method wasn’t quick, but Daoist practices generally had the most benefits. People who practice this method would not be possessed by Devils and would generally have more life force.

Chapter 922: The Lion King

Although Green and the others were God-rank experts, they were already quite old and their lifespan was limited. They only practice magic and battle qi, so even if it had a help of increasing their strength, it won’t increase their lifespan that much. Compared to a Daoist method’s means of preserving life, it still fell a bit short.

Green and the others were Zhao Hai’s family members. Back when Zhao Hai was on Earth, he didn’t have a family, he never felt the warmth of home. It was only after arriving at the Ark Continent did Zhao Hai know the feeling of family, the feeling of being home.

Zhao Hai treasures this feeling very much. No matter what he does, he would always put his family members first. If he gains any benefits, he would always think of his clan.

Back in the Ark Continent, Zhao Hai was a rich person, and his family was always full. But now he was different, he was a family Patriarch and also had a lot of people inside the Space. He had to be responsible for all of these people. Therefore, he had to look for benefits all the time. If he wanted to achieve his goals, he can only do this.

Zhao Hai was sitting inside his room while looking at the monitor. There was a dust cloud over where Lion Rock was. The people of the Leo Continent should know about this before long. Hiding such a huge sound would be very difficult.

At this time, Zhao Hai wanted to see the response of the Leo Continent. At the same time, he also knows that the Leo Continent’s reaction wouldn’t be as severe as the Central Continent.

The reason Zhao Hai was able to cause that much reaction to the Central Continent was because he also eradicated the Central Continent’s Imperial Clan. This turned the Central Continent into a headless dragon. Nobody was able to suppress the populace, contributing to how chaotic everything became.

Like Zhao Hai thought, chaos had arrived at the Leo Continent. The mood of the Leo Divines haven’t been that great lately. They felt that, as Divines, they shouldn’t have suffered a loss against someone from the Ark Continent.

All these years, Connecting Heaven Palace had always been the spiritual pillar of the Divine Race. How could these people bear the damage of their holy place being destroyed.

And now, Lion Rock, a sacred place for the Leo Divines, has been ruined. At the same time, the remains of their ancestors have been turned into undead. It didn’t take a long time for the Leo Continent to explode.

Although the scale of the Leo Continent’s reaction wasn’t as worse as the Central Continent, the chaos was still out of Zhao Hai’s imagination.

It wasn’t only Zhao Hai whose expectation were surpassed, the Leo Divines didn’t expect it as well. Fights among the civilians happened frequently, some fires also began to appear. After that, the army joined the chaos. The matter became bigger and bigger, in the end it couldn’t be controlled anymore.

However, the chaos in the Leo Continent was somewhat different from the chaos in the Central Continent. In the Central Continent, the chaos stemmed from people completely losing their sense. On the other hand, the Leo Continent’s chaos came from the population’s suppressed emotions.

The arrogance of the Divine Race had exceeded Zhao Hai’s expectation. In their view, Zhao Hai’s attack on Connecting Heaven Palace and now on Lion Rock was completely because of the incompetence of those in power. Not being able to find and deal with Zhao Hai was the biggest insult. The people could only vent their emotions in this way.

Most importantly, this sentiment didn’t only exist among the commoners, the soldiers thought the same as well. In the end, this caused the trouble in the Leo Continent to be more uncontrollable.

Zhao Hai went to Thirsty Lion City in order to take a look. He wanted to see how chaotic the Leo Continent had become. However, he didn’t relax on observing Lion Rock. He knew that the powerful Leo Divines would surely go and see the situation.

The reason Zhao Hai wanted to keep his attention on Lion Rock was because he wanted to obtain a genuine Seven Star Heaven Lock disk. The disk can be installed on the Hell King’s ship, so Zhao Hai needed to obtain them.

Although the chaos in the Leo Continent had become uncontrollable, and some opportunists had used this to gain benefits, the Leo Royals still didn’t take it too seriously. This was because they already reported this matter to their Supreme Elder. They believed that as long as the Supreme Elder comes back, then this unrest would immediately die down.

Because of this, the Royal Family sent people without bringing a Seven-Star Heaven Lock disk. Not that they didn’t, but they couldn’t because they didn’t have one.

The eight disks of the formation was sent to the other eight continents. Since Elder Star and the others were staying in the Leo Continent, there was no disk present here. This was something that Zhao Hai didn’t take into account.

However, the person that went this time was someone special. It was the Leo Continent’s Lion King! Lion Rock was equivalent to the Imperial tomb of the Leo Clan. Now that their ancestral grave was dug out, how could the Lion King not go to investigate.

Although the Leo Continent had gone chaotic, the Leo Clan still controlled quite a number of troops. This army comprised mostly of the Royal Clan’s juniors. They’re quite numerous and were very loyal. It was because of this army that the Leo Royals weren’t afraid that someone would make a move on them.

Lion City wasn’t very far from Lion Rock. It didn’t take long before the Leo Clan was able to arrive. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai calmly observed the situation at Lion Rock.

After seeing the Leo Royals, Zhao Hai knew that their identity wasn’t simple. At this time, Laura and the others were training, so Zhao Hai didn’t plan to bother them. However, Zhao Hai didn’t think about giving up this time. He wanted to use this opportunity to deal with the Leo Royals. Therefore, he released Qing Feng and Mingyuan out. Then he ordered them to attack the Royal Clan.

This might me cruel, but it wasn’t. Although the Leo Royals were descendants of Qing Feng and Mingyue, their blood has been extremely diluted after many generations. This allowed Zhao Hai to have the confidence to send the two powerful undead out.

The Lion King’s expression was ugly as he looked at Lion Mountain. To be honest, the other Royals didn’t care much about the destruction of Connecting Heaven Palace. They weren’t from the Central Continent. And even if the effort the ten Continents did to build the palace wasn’t small, it was just to the point of sending average God-ranks to help.

For the Lion King, that matter was already too long ago. If the palace was destroyed, then it was destroyed. For him, it wasn’t a very important event. Zhao Hai slapped the face of the Central Continent, it had nothing to do with him.

But now that Lion Rock was destroyed, the slap was on the faces of the Leo Divines. In this case, how could the Lion King just remain calm?

Most importantly, the Lion King understood what the destruction of Lion Rock meant. Lion Rock was their ancestral grave. Even a small damage to the grave was a stain on the Leo Royal Clan’s reputation.

The man wearing a helmet next to the Lion King had an even uglier expression. This person was the highest ranked military person in the continent, a Leo Royal Prince, the younger brother of the Lion King. He was called the War Lion.

War Lion’s expression was very ugly. He thought that this matter was his responsibility. He was the most decorated general in the continent, and the defensive plan was arranged by him. However, under his own gaze, the Lion Rock was silently destroyed by Zhao Hai. This was the greatest shame that he had experienced.

At this time, the two suddenly heard sounds of disturbance. The Lion King and War Lion turned to see a group of undead. Upon seeing these undead, the expression on the faces of the two immediately turned uglier.

War Lion and the Lion King were members of the Royal Family, so they were more acquainted to the members of the Royal Clan due to the portraits that were made. On those portraits, the members wore their Imperial Robes of which they also wore to their graves. Because of this, War Lion and the Lion King both recognized Qing Feng and Mingyue. Judging by their clothes, their thought shouldn’t be wrong.

After understanding this, it’s natural that the two would be extremely angry. However, the two suddenly had a headache. It was because attacking these undead would be the same as attacking their ancestors. They didn’t know how to go about this situation. Even if they managed to destroy the undead, this meant that their ancestors’ skeletons would be ruined. On the other hand, how could they just receive the attack without retaliating? This made War Lion and the Lion King frown at the same time.

War Lion turned to the Lion King and said, “Brother, what should we do?”

The Lion King frowned, he still couldn’t make up his mind. After some time, the Lion King said, “We fight. We’ll clash with them sooner or later. We cannot just wait for Zhao Hai to release them.”

War Lion couldn’t help but sigh. To be honest, he really didn’t want to fight. But in this case, they didn’t have a choice. War Lion wanted to disagree with the Lion King, but he hated Zhao Hai more.

Along with the Lion King’s order, the army began to move and head towards Qing Feng and Mingyue. Following the Lion King were his personal guards. They were quite strong, and they numbered about a hundred thousand.

But when the personal guards rushed over, they suddenly discovered their mistake. Every undead suddenly established their Domains as they proceeded to attack.

The guards didn’t expect the undead to be this formidable. The undead were actually God-ranks, and they were even able to use their Domains. For the Personal Guards, this was a disaster.

Although the personal guards weren’t weak, they were only God-rank experts. On the other hand, the other party were peak God-ranks. The guards were surely to be pressured by the undead.

Chapter 923: Is This The End Of the Divine Race?

However, the guards weren’t necessarily unable to counter-attack. These people were among the best of the Leo Continent’s soldiers. And considering Domain Weapons, the group had about twenty, this number wasn’t small.

On the other side of the battle, the Lion King was protected inside his Domain Weapon. It wasn’t as if he didn’t have the strength to fight, after all he was also a God-rank expert. However, in the end, he was the King, he couldn’t be put into any danger.

The Lion King’s guards were already fighting against Qing Feng and Mingyue. One was strong while the other wasn’t afraid of death. Although one side was a bit weaker because of their weapons, the two sides were still equal.

At this moment, the Hell King’s ship suddenly appeared beside the Lion King’s carriage. The Lion King’s domain weapon was also a carriage known as Lion Chariot. It had the appearance of a lion with the tail being the handle.

The Leo Divines didn’t expect the Hell King’s ship to appear. Just after going out, the Hell King’s ship immediately fired its cannons towards the Lion Chariot. The chariot didn’t even have time to block. It was immediately vaporized along with the Lion King that was inside.

The current strength of the Hell King’s ship’s cannons were already far from the original. No domain weapon would be able to block its attacks. And since the Lion King wasn’t prepared, he didn’t have any chance of defending against Zhao Hai.

Despite  eliminating the Lion Chariot, Zhao Hai didn’t stop. He immediately released a large number of undead and attacked the Lion King’s personal guards. Zhao Hai didn’t release 10 or 2 million undead, he released 5 million. 5 million undead against 100 thousand guards, with the latter being surrounded at all sides. In this case, the guards had no hope of escaping. In less than an hour, the battle was over. Nobody from the side of the Leo Divines survived, even War Lion fell.

After the fight ended, Zhao Hai immediately began to take all of the Domain Weapons and handed them over to Qing Feng and Mingyue’s group. Zhao Hai intends to have their group be the second Devil Legion.

The reason for Zhao Hai’s confidence was his discovery about Qing Feng and Mingyue’s group. Their increase in strength was much more than the other undead.

Although undead were strong beings, their weakness lies in increasing their power. Compared to ordinary people, their cultivation speed was much worse.

However, Qing Feng and Mingyue’s group were different. It’s possibly because of the formation in Lion Rock, preserving their blood and flesh, unifying it with their skeletons. Because of this development, they weren’t able to turn into zombies like the other undead. But this also caused them to be stronger and be more talented when it came to cultivation. They were the strongest undead units that Zhao Hai had in hand.

Upon this discovery, Zhao Hai immediately paid special attention to them. He even tried to equip them with combat suits to see if they were compatible with it.

However, this experiment ended up disappointing Zhao Hai. Even if these undead were stronger and more talented than the others, they still weren’t able to utilize the abilities of the combat suits.

Zhao Hai would still need to find a suitable weapon for the undead. If Zhao Hai can find something good to equip them with, then the power of his undead would improve by at least a few layers.

The undead were different compared to other people when it comes to weapons. Other people would need to train and would be affected by whatever they experience in the battlefield, weakening their overall strength. On the other hand, as long as an undead’s summoner was good, then their abilities wouldn’t fall short against a competent army.

After taking care of Qing Feng and Mingyue’s group, Zhao Hai returned to Thirsty Lion City. He wanted to see how the Leo Divines would act upon knowing that their King was killed.

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai saw the reaction. It was chaos. Originally, the Leo Divines were still able to suppress the chaos because of the presence of their King. But now it was different, the Lion King was dead. The final dam was gone, drowning the continent in chaos.

Zhao Hai also found out that the chaos here was different compared to the Central Continent. In the Central Continent, the chaos was due to overwhelming emotion. In the Leo Continent, however, it seems like there were some social issues that had accumulated to a certain degree. It was through Zhao Hai’s action that the issue began to burst out.

Zhao Hai can only shake his head regarding this situation. He had already achieved his goal in the Leo Continent. At this time, the only thing left to do was to wait for the Leo Supreme Elder to appear. If the Leo Supreme Elder came back without the other Supreme Elders, then Zhao Hai would use the opportunity to deal with him.

At this time, Laura and the others came out of their room. They practiced longer than Zhao Hai, but had gained less from the method. Moreover, the refinement of their energy wasn’t as good as Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai turned and observed them. Their temperament had subtly changed. They were currently wearing home clothing from the science and technology background. The clothes look like sportswear, and it was colored with bright tones.

Wearing these clothes would make one feel lively. And when Laura and the others wore it, it makes one feel a noble gentleness, an elegant atmosphere.

After seeing the group, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. Their change made them even more beautiful. And with the education they learned since childhood, they look even more eye-catching. If they were stars in the sky before, they had now become moons.

Upon seeing his wives like this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but heat up. Laura and the others had some understanding of Zhao Hai. Upon seeing his expression, they immediately understood. All of their faces couldn’t help but turn red.

Laura turned to look at Lizzy and the others, they also looked at each other before seeing the teasing smiles on their eyes. Then they turned to look at Zhao Hai and slowly went forward.

Before long, Laura and the others arrived by Zhao Hai’s side. Then suddenly Laura said, “Sisters, hold him!” Then the women grabbed Zhao Hai, lifting him up.

Zhao Hai struggled and said, “What, what are you doing? Let me go. Help!” Laura sneered and said, “Save your voice, calling until you have a  broken throat wouldn’t even help..” But Zhao Hai continued to yell, “Broken throat, broken throat, you there? Help me quick!”[1]

When they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others chuckled and then pinched him in the waist. However, they didn’t let go of him and just brought him to the hot spring. After that, boundless spring arrived…

The Leo Supreme Elder, Sinlea, was currently standing on the ruins of Connecting Heaven Palace. The entire mountain had been completely crushed, not even a single tile went undamaged. Although Sinlea wasn’t from the Central Continent, his heart still felt heavy upon witnessing this.

Even without the Seven Star Heaven Lock, the defenses of Connecting Heaven Palace was still very formidable. Otherwise, it wouldn’t have become a sacred land. However, Zhao Hai was actually able to demolish it within an extremely short period of time. Add this to Zhao Hai surviving five Supreme Elders, destroying the Taurus Continent base, and completely eradicating the Taurus Divines, all of these only expressed how formidable Zhao Hai was.

Zhao Hai was so powerful that he was actually a great threat to the Divine Race. At this point, his enmity with the Divines was irresolvable. The stronger he was, the more trouble the Divines would be in. And now, they still had no way of finding out where Zhao Hai was. It can be said that they were completely beaten by Zhao Hai. Moreover, Zhao Hai can attack them at any place and at any time. This made the Supreme Elders very unhappy.

Most importantly, Sinlea and the others were worried since they didn’t know what Zhao Hai’s next target would be. It’s probable that when they arrived at the Central Continent, Zhao Hai was already elsewhere. They were always slower than Zhao Hai.

After thinking about this, Sinlea’s heart couldn’t help but turn heavy. He looked at Elder Star who wasn’t that far away. Elder Star had gone senile, he had become skinny to the point of skin and bones. He looks like he would fall over at any moment. His state was made worse by the fact that his whole family has been killed.

Upon seeing this situation, Sinlea couldn’t help but sigh. In the past, Elder Star was a high-spirited and vigorous man. Since he was the Central Continent’s Supreme Elder, he held the highest status among the Supreme Elders. Because of this, his appearance seemed always amicable, but still held some arrogance within.

But now, that person had turned into this appearance. Everybody who saw this change couldn’t stop themselves from sighing.

At this time, Elder Star suddenly said, “Do any of you have any ideas on how to deal with Zhao Hai?” Sinlea and the others frowned. They didn’t have any good idea. Because of this, Elder Star’s question made them feel embarrassed.

Perhaps because he didn’t hear a reply, Elder Star spoke after some time. He sighed and said, “Is this the end of the divine race?”

At this time, Gold Ben spoke, “I have a way to deal with Zhao Hai. But the sacrifices needed for this method would be very huge.”

* * *

Maybe a Chinese language structure thing. Can’t seem to get the context to English.

Chapter 924: Can’t Decide

Everybody turned to look at Gold Ben. They were aware that Gold Ben was the earliest one who had fought with Zhao Hai. Moreover, Gold Ben had lost the entire Taurus Clan to Zhao Hai. Because of this, Gold Ben had the lowest status. Now that he decided to talk, the group couldn’t help but be curious.

Elder Star looked at Gold Ben. This caused Gold Ben to unconsciously turn his eyes away. It wasn’t that he felt guilty, but it was because he didn’t want to see the face of Elder Star.

Elder Star was now too thin, his body looked like a skeleton covered by a layer of skin. It gave people a very terrible feeling. Additionally, he had an ominous look in his eyes. He was like a skeleton, but was actually a person. This caused Gold Ben to be uncomfortable, making him look away unconsciously.

Elder Star didn’t care about this, he still looked straight into Gold ben and said, “Elder Gold Ben, if you have anything to say, please say it.”

Gold Ben nodded and said, “At this moment, Zhao Hai has the ability to cause trouble wherever he wants in the Divine Realm. Our previous plan is obviously not working. Instead of being slowly killed by Zhao Hai, we might as well think of another way. As long as we’re willing to make some sacrifices, then Zhao Hai will definitely come to us.”

Elder Star looked at Gold Ben and said, “What is your plan?” Gold Ben replied, “We can begin now. We’ll directly fly towards the Taurus Continent, all the way with no stopping. No matter which continent gets ruined, we still go on. When we arrive at the Taurus Continent, we will immediately deal with the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus. No matter what happens, we attack the three clans. Zhao Hai will certainly come over and help them.”

As soon as Elder Star and the others heard this, they immediately gawked. This idea was similar to Elder Star’s, but with a different target. Moreover, they would give priority to the task and just sacrifice the other Divines. Attacking the Thunder Clan and the others means that the Divine Race territory would be left with no defenses. When the time comes, who knows how much damage Zhao Hai would cause.

The group hesitated somewhat. Elder Star looked at Gold Ben and said, “How sure are you with this plan?” Gold Ben said, “I’m certain that it will work. Although the Taurus Continent has been annihilated by Zhao Hai, this didn’t come out without the assistance of the Thunder Clan and the others. Their alliance gave Zhao Hai the means to deal with us. But at the same time, since Zhao Hai wanted to save some face for the three clans,  the battle also caused the three clans no small amount of loss. Because of this, the three clans are now in their planes, healing. Zhao Hai’s relationship with the three clans is surely more than simple. Without the three clans, the Taurus Divines wouldn’t have fallen this quickly.”

Elder Star and the others nodded. They knew that what Gold Ben said was right. Although Gold Ben’s Taurus Continent wasn’t the strongest, they also weren’t the weakest. Nobody would believe it if someone said that Zhao Hai’s side had no losses after dealing with them.

After seeing the group agree to him, Gold Ben continued, “Because of this, we will go and attack the three clans. We wouldn’t care if Zhao Hai attacks the Divine Territory. If we don’t go back, then the ball would be in Zhao Hai’s hands. If he didn’t help the three clans, then his relationship with the vassal races would have problems. If that happens, then the vassal races would not cooperate with Zhao Hai wholeheartedly. This way, we can deal with the vassal and the foreign races one by one. Zhao Hai will surely come to help the three clans. And when that time comes, we can have a decisive fight against him. We wouldn’t have to find him, he would be the one who needs to come to us.”

Upon hearing this, Elder Star and the others couldn’t help but nod. Truthfully, the Divines didn’t have any means to hold Zhao Hai down, his escaping skill was just too good. Although they would suffer some losses on several continents, Gold Ben’s method was their only choice. If they don’t do this, then Zhao Hai would grind them down until nothing was left.

Elder Star looked at the other Supreme Elders and said, “I agree with Gold Ben’s suggestion. Does anyone have other ideas? From what I can see, the Central Continent is already finished, it would be impossible for the continent to recover even in a hundred years. If we don’t deal with Zhao Hai, then your continents will become the same as the Central Continent. When the time comes, the foreign races will also make their move, causing us even more losses. I ask everyone to think this matter carefully through.”

Sinlea and the others silently ruminated about the idea. To be honest, they already knew that this was the best plan to deal with Zhao Hai. But this loss was something that they didn’t want to see.

Suddenly, a person came running in. This person was from Central City’s garrison troops. Although the city was seriously damaged, there were still some people who stayed sober all this time. Because of these people, Elder Star made a refugee camp inside the ruined city. Officers have also been assigned to some of these people in order to maintain public security.

This person’s expression was quite ugly as he kneeled in front of Elder Star and the others, “Reporting to the Supreme Elders. We’ve just received a report. Zhao Hai attacked the Leo Continent and destroyed Lion Rock. The Leo Divine ancestors have also been turned into undead. The Lion King and Sir War Lion has been killed. The Leo Clan is inviting the Leo Supreme Elder to return in order to stabilize the situation.”

This report made Sinlea and the others turn blank. They knew what Lion Rock represented to the Leo Divines. But now, Zhao Hai actually destroyed it and even turned their ancestors into undead. Most importantly, the Lion King and War Lion were killed. The entire Leo Continent have been plunged into chaos.

Sinlea’s face was pale as he looked at the person and said, “This report, is this accurate?”

The person immediately replied, “This report has been sent by the Fishman Race. They said that the Leo Continent is now a mess. They ask the Elder to return and stabilize the situation.”

With clenched teeth, Sinlea growled, “That brat, he went too far!” Then he turned to Elder Star and Gold Ben, “I agree with Elder Gold Ben’s plan. After stabilizing the Leo Continent, we should head to the Taurus Continent and deal with the three clans!”

After Sinlea said this, the other Supreme Elders looked at each other before agreeing as well. From what happened to the Central Continent and the Leo Continent, they could see how heartless Zhao Hai could be. If they don’t go with the plan, then they would be killed by Zhao Hai sooner or later. Instead of being killed, they might as well fight!

When Elder Star saw the other Elders agree, he immediately said, “Good, we still have time. We will immediately leave for the Leo Continent. But before we do that, we should look for the Seven Star Heaven Lock disk. With our strengths and the Seven Star Heaven Lock, we should be able to kill Zhao Hai on the spot.”

The group nodded before they looked through the ruins. Elder Star held the Seven Star Heaven Lock formation for the longest time, so he had the most understanding about it. Because of this, after looking at the ruins, he gave a rough location of the disk. After digging for a few times, they finally recovered the formation disk.

After digging the formation disk out, the group immediately set off for the Leo Continent. Just as planned, they would take care of the matter with the Leo Continent before heading to the Taurus Continent. But before going to the Taurus Continent, they took a short trip in order to recover all of the other Seven Star Heaven Lock disks.

…..

Zhao Hai was currently sat in his room. He looked at Laura and the others and couldn’t help but sigh. He thought about how charming they were back in the hot spring, but now they had this gentle and noble look. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but lament how fickle women were.

However, after thinking about the hot springs, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at it fondly. Although Zhao Hai had been squeezed in by several people, he still believed that not many men were able to experience that.

Laura and the others were also able to notice Zhao Hai’s gaze. The group couldn’t help but go red in embarrassment. To be honest, they had been impulsive that day. If they were to think about it again, they definitely wouldn’t do it.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled. He didn’t say anything about his thoughts as he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, do you think that the Leo Supreme Elder would come back alone? If he does, then we would be able to deal with him.”

Laura shook her head and said, “I think the other Elders would follow him. Moreover, they will certainly make adjustments and find ways to solve their current situation. They can’t go on like this. Otherwise, they would be killed by us sooner or later.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the others and said, “What do you think they will do?”

The group frowned, but after some time Lizzy said, “I think they will head to the Taurus Continent and deal with the three clans.”

Zhao Hai became stunned for a moment, then he frowned and said, “Is that so? But if they deal with the Thunder Clan and the others, aren’t they afraid of me attacking the other continents?” Lizzy shook her head and said, “If I were them, I wouldn’t care about the other continents anymore. I will focus on dealing with the three clans so that you would have to go back and help them. When that time comes, they would get what they want, a direct fight with you.”

Zhao Hai frowned. He felt that Lizzy was correct. Now he wanted to think about ways in order to deal with the enemy.

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and knew what he was thinking about, so she said, “Big Brother Hai, it seems like we won’t be able to think of a way to escape from this. In any case, we need to save the three clans, otherwise our relationship with the vassal races and the foreign races would be affected.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’m aware of this, but I’m still unwilling. If we do go against them, then I’m afraid the fight wouldn’t be short. After all, I still can’t go at full force. It seems like we have no way to deal with the other Divine Race continents.”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “Brother Hai, how could you forget about our allies? We managed to drag the nine Supreme Elders to the Taurus Continent. This will allow the foreign races to make a move. The Divines wouldn’t be able to do much when their Supreme Elders aren’t present. The Foreign Races could also send their own Supreme Elders to clean each continent as well as help the vassal races.”

When he heard Lizzy, Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he patted his head and said, “Right, right. That’s good. We can bind the Supreme Elders in the Taurus Continent while the foreign races go and deal with the Divines. Without the Supreme Elders, the Divines would find it hard to defend.”

Laura looked at the two and smiled, “Brother Hai, don’t celebrate too early. We still don’t know if the Supreme Elders did intend to do this. If they don’t, then wouldn’t our plan be wasted?” Zhao Hai thought about Elder Star and then shook his head, “No, I think the Divines will certainly do what Lizzy said. They had been pushed to a dead end. It’s just a pity that as the matter stands, we won’t have a way bring the Thunder Clan and the others to the Space.”

At this time, Megan smiled faintly and said, “Elder Brother Hai, I don’t think so. This depends on what Brother Hai wants to do. If you can bear with it, we can still push the three clans into the Space.”

Zhao Hai looked at Megan and said, “What do you mean?”

Megan smiled and said, “Didn’t Lizzy just say it? The Supreme Elders are going to deal with the three clans in order to lure us in. In return, they will ignore whatever happens to the Divine Race territory. So why can’t we pretend to be blind for a moment? While the Supreme Elders are in the Taurus Continent, we shall linger in the Divine Race Continents for some time. Only when the Supreme Elders discover that we are only pretending should we go and confront them. The nine Elders should be furious right now, so they would certainly cause quite some losses to the three clans. When that time comes, we can ask the three clans to move to the Space. But when they are inside the Space, we will tell them that the O’Neal family had attacked again as well as the growing threat of the underworld. We can use that opportunity to have them settle inside the Space. That wouldn’t be difficult to do right?”

Chapter 925: Another Angle

Zhao Hai carefully listened to Megan’s words. Although her method was quite black-hearted, Zhao Hai could see how it would work.

If Zhao Hai did what Megan said, then the three clans would suffer losses again. And along with the pressure brought by the O’Neal family, it’s very likely that they would agree if Zhao Hai asked them to move to the Space.

Additionally, there wouldn’t be any flaws in this plan. After all, he was helping the foreign races to break through. This way, nobody would have any suspicions.

However, this plan would cause huge losses to the Thunder Clan and the others. One must know that Zhao Hai had turned the Supreme Elders mad. They will certainly be impolite to Zhao Hai’s allies. When the time comes, a lot of people from the three clans would die, there was no doubt about this.

Just as Megan said, this can only be done if Zhao Hai can endure. Zhao Hai wasn’t a black-hearted person. Although he had goals he needed to be done, he did so in a reasonable manner. But this time, the three clans will encounter a calamity because of him. Megan and the others were clear about this, and Zhao Hai as well. Because of this, Megan only brought this idea up.

Laura understood Megan’s point, because of this, everybody looked at Zhao Hai in order to reach a decision.

Zhao Hai frowned as he sat. He can understand Megan’s plan. Naturally, he also knew the consequences. Because of this, he couldn’t help but hesitate.

Zhao Hai wanted to get the three clans to move to the Space. But if he achieved it through Megan’s method, the losses of the three clans would be great. They were even in danger of being destroyed.

Zhao Hai was afraid of the three clans being exterminated. This outcome would be unfair to them. This troubled Zhao Hai’s heart.

At this time, Meg suddenly said, “Young Master, I’d like to express my opinion. Young Master, I don’t know if you’ve already thought about this, but have you thought about what would happen to the three clans after we ascend?”

When he heard Meg, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. He looked at Meg with a confused expression. Meg looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, don’t forget that even if we defeated the Divine Race, this plane is still under Lu Wei’s control. Lu Wei can definitely support another race to replace the Divines. No matter where we are, the Thunder Clan and the others still offended Lu Wei. When the time comes, what would happen to them? Could they block Lu Wei’s attack?”

Megan and the others were also stunned. To be honest, they never examined this matter in this angle. They always thought that if they defeated the Divine Race before they ascend, then Lu Wei would just let their allies go. Zhao Hai and the others thought that it was them who would be unlucky.

After staring at Meg for some time, Zhao Hai suddenly laughed and said, “Meg, I haven’t thought about that but you actually noticed it. Right, if we ascend one day, then the Thunder Clan and the others would be the most unfortunate. They would be eliminated by Lu Wei. People as petty as Lu Wei would certainly do it. We might as well do our best to relocate the three clans to the Space.”

Megan turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Then we should go with the plan. We’ll monitor the Supreme Elders first. If they go and deal with the three clans, then we’ll rampage throughout the Divine Race territory. If the Supreme Elders don’t retreat, then that’s when we provide support. I believe the three clans would come to the Space. Besides this, we should also send a letter to the foreign races. While we support the three clans, the foreign races would deal with the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll do that. We wait for the Supreme Elders first. Don’t tell Bingya and the others about this yet. Only reveal the matter when we head back to the Taurus Continent.”

Laura understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do. If they told this matter to Bingya and the others prematurely, then Bingya and the others would know about Zhao Hai’s plan for the three clans. When the time comes, their relationship with the foreign races would surely be affected.

Zhao Hai wasn’t a person who easily backs out of plans. Upon reaching a decision, he will immediately do his best to accomplish it. Now that everything has been planned out, Zhao Hai stopped worrying. He just quietly waited for the Supreme Elders to arrive in the Leo Continent.

Zhao Hai didn’t go too far and was just right by Lion Rock. he believed that if the Leo Supreme Elder were to return to the Leo Continent, then he would certainly come and inspect Lion Rock. If he was alone at that time, then Zhao Hai would be impolite.

Zhao Hai and the others were already used to staying inside their rooms. But this time, Laura and the others were inside the Space. They wanted to give the cultivation method over to Green and the others.

Sinlea didn’t let Zhao Hai wait too long. Soon, his figure was seen in Lion Rock. However, he wasn’t alone, the other Supreme Elders were with him.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai knew that he wouldn’t be able to make an attack. Because of this, he just looked at Sinlea’s pale expression as he looked at Lion Rock. Lion Rock was his clan’s imperial tomb, not only was it destroyed, the Leo Divines weren’t even able to protect the skeletons of their ancestors.

Sinlea slowly fell to the ground and walked over to where Lion Rock was. Then he slammed his head to the ground multiple times before he straightened up and loudly declared, “Ancestors! This unfilial Sinlea swears to completely destroy Zhao Hai and offer his soul to you.”

The other Supreme Elders didn’t kneel down. They just looked at Sinlea as he handled his matters with Lion Rock. To Sinlea, this attack was quite huge.

After doing his respects, Sinlea stood up and turned to the other Supreme Elders, “Everyone, we’ll stabilize the Leo Continent first. Then we’ll carry out our plan.” The group nodded before flying away with Sinlea.

The Supreme Elders flew towards the center of the continent. Although Zhao Hai didn’t follow them, he still managed to guess what Sinlea and the others planned to do. They wanted to stabilize the Leo Continent first. As for their other plan, Zhao Hai still didn’t know. However, Zhao Hai wanted to use the following days to map the Leo Continent’s coastline as he waited for Sinlea and the others to leave. Only then would Zhao Hai know what the Divines were planning.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately had Bubble lead him to map the Leo Continent’s coastline, allowing the Space to monitor the continent’s border.

Sinlea held a high position in the Leo Continent. So when he came back, the situation with the continent stabilized very quickly. Moreover, since the Leo Imperials weren’t completely exterminated, Sinlea was able to appoint a new Lion King. With that, the Leo Continent quickly went under control.

Five days after Sinlea and the others returned to the Leo Continent, their traces were found in the southeastern coastline of the continent. Only the nine elders were travelling as they went out of the continent and headed towards the southeast direction.

Zhao Hai immediately had Bubble go up. At this time, Laura and the others came out of the Space. They entered the Space not only to teach Green and the others about the cultivation method, they also selected some talented Goblins to be sent to Karen’s laboratory in Wild Dragon Island.

At this moment, Karen’s laboratory had Beastmen, Dwarves, Goblins, Elves, Humans, and even some Demons selected by the Great Demon King. At the same time, there were also Fishmen sent by the Mermaid Queen. It can be said that aside from the Divines, Karen’s laboratory had every race present inside Zhao Hai’s Space.

Naturally, in addition to the Goblins, there were also other races who decided to settle in the island. The laboratory had long been built, it only needed people to occupy it.

Laura and the others proceeded to sit down and look at the screen. The monitor showed Elder Star and the others flying in the sky. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was following behind them, matching their speed.

Zhao Hai also saw that Elder Star and the others didn’t immediately go to the Taurus Continent. This made Zhao Hai somewhat puzzled. Don’t they want to deal with the three clans? Was Megan’s guess wrong?

However, in order to determine what the Supreme Elders were doing, Zhao Hai decided to continue following behind them. When they entered a continent, Zhao Hai proceeded to map its coastline. Attacking the continent at this time would be risky even for Zhao Hai. He only wanted to see what the Supreme Elders were planning to do.

Fortunately, Sinlea and the others didn’t let Zhao Hai down. After inquiring the situation with of the continent, he realized that this was the continent of the Supreme Elder that he just killed, the Scorpio Continent.

After the Scorpio Continent, Sinlea and the others went to continent after continent. This almost turned Zhao Hai dizzy. In the end, Zhao Hai discovered that after circling through the nine Divine Race continents, the Supreme Elders  finally proceeded to head towards the Taurus Continent.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t know why Sinlea and the others went in a roundabout way, he can affirm that the Supreme Elders were planning to deal with the Thunder Clan and the others.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately took his messenger fish out. This messenger fish was used to converse with Fei’er.

Chapter 926: Fei’er’s Worry

Fei’er was currently at the defensive line. He didn’t know about what happened outside nor was he aware of the O’Neal family’s movements.

On the other hand, the defensive line was very good. The undead were skilled at using the magic cannons. Although the O’Neal family had sent several attacks, none of them yielded any results.

But even then, Fei’er didn’t dare to underestimate the O’Neal family. They were yet to send a substantial amount of troops, all recent attacks were scouting runs.

Moreover, the scouts that were sent forth were very difficult to deal with. Besides the time where Zhao Hai was present, no magic armors have fallen.

They used to send out some cavalry to deal with the scouts, but the scouts have already made some plans to deal with them. Because of this, carrying an attack on the scouting parties had become useless.

Fei’er was currently having headaches about the defensive line. He wasn’t a fool. They were already having difficulties with the O’Neal family’s scouting runs. If they decided to attack aggressively, would the defensive line be able to hold on? This caused Fei’er to worry.

At this time, his messenger fish suddenly voiced out, “Fei’er, Fei’er, are you there? It’s Zhao Hai.”

Fei’er stared, then he immediately took his messenger fish and said, “Mister, it’s me. What’s the matter?”

Zhao Hai’s voice replied, “Fei’er, I have something important to tell you. I went out last time because the Divines are going to deal with the foreign races. In order to solve the problem, I went to the Central Continent and destroyed their Connecting Heaven Palace. I also went to the Leo Continent to ruin their Lion Rock. The Divines have already retreated while the Central and Leo Continents are in chaos. However, this also caused the Divines to hate me.”

After hearing Zhao Hai, Fei’er gawked. He had followed Thunder Yun in the past, so he had some understanding about the Divine Race. Connecting Heaven Palace and Lion Rock were sacred sites. Because of this, Fei’er knew how important they were.

Now that he heard Zhao Hai, Fei’er was able to vent his frustrations but he also became worried. His frustration came from the constant oppression the vassal races had received all these years. Their hatred towards the Divines had been inscribed into their blood and bones. Zhao Hai destroying the Connecting Heaven Palace as well as Lion Rock allowed Fei’er to vent.

However, Fei’er was also worried precisely because he knew how important those two places were. Destroying those two places might allow him to vent, but this will also turn the Divines mad. Fei’er was worried about Zhao Hai, so he quickly said, “Mister, are you alright? Those two places are too important to the Divine Race. After losing those, the Divines would surely go for Mister. You should be careful from now on.”

When Zhao Hai heard Fei’er say this, his heart couldn’t help but warm. He actually thought about giving up on his plan. However, he steeled his heart as he said, “Fei’er, there’s no need to worry about me. I’m fine. It wouldn’t be easy for the Divines to deal with me. However, I’m afraid that the Supreme Elders would go and deal with your three clans in the Taurus Continent.”

Fei’er’s expression quickly changed, “Mister, are you sure?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Almost certain. At this point, the Supreme Elders are heading towards the Taurus Continent. I think they want to deal with you instead in order to lure me in.”

Fei’er was startled at this news, “Mister, what can we do? The Supreme Elders are very strong. If they use their ultimate weapons, then we would have no chance to resist.”

Zhao Hai’s voice turned serious, “I know this. However, I can’t fight them now. I’ll go and attack the other continents . I just hope that they’ll retreat once more.”

Fei’er thought for a moment and said, “Mister, what if the Supreme Elders don’t go back? If they decide to seriously attack us, then what do we do then?”

Zhao Hai turned silent for some time before he said, “Fei’er, I’ll present these facts to you. The people from the Ark Continent and the Demon Realm have been sent to another place by me. That place belongs entirely to me, everyone there needs to listen to my commands. I haven’t said this to you before because I’m afraid that you would misunderstand. However, the current situation is critical, I couldn’t afford to withhold this information from you. I hope that you can go to that place to seek safety.”

Fei’er was silent. He completely understood the elders of his clan. These people were very hard to move and wouldn’t want to be under someone’s control. This was the precise reason why they decided to go against the Divine Race. The elders would certainly disagree being under Zhao Hai’s command.

Zhao Hai was aware of Fei’er’s difficulty, so he said, “Fei’er, in a moment I’ll have an undead deliver three command tokens to you. You can bring those tokens to your clans. The command tokens are able to open spatial rifts so that your people can enter the place. If your people agreed, then you can send them in. If they don’t agree, then it’s fine. If the Supreme Elders are really intent to eliminating the three clans, then I will immediately return to the Taurus Continent. However, I’m afraid that you cannot withstand the Supreme Elders. I won’t say anything more, time is tight. Wait for the undead to send you the tokens before returning to your clans.” After he said that, Zhao Hai no longer made a sound.

Fei’er can hear the indignation from Zhao Hai’s words. But Fei’er knew that Zhao Hai was right. In the past, he thought that it was strange for Zhao Hai to not worry about the people from the Ark Continent. As it turns out, the people of the Ark Continent have already moved.

Afterwards, the Demons actually dealt with the Divines along with Zhao Hai. This made Fei’er confused. Why would the Demons listen to Zhao Hai? But now he knew, the Demons have already submitted to Zhao Hai.

If the Demons and the people from the Ark Continent surrendered to Zhao Hai, then why can’t they do the same? During the war, the Ark Continent and the Demons hardly lost any people. Meanwhile, the three clans suffered a lot.

Even if they had the right of equal dialogue with Zhao Hai at this time, was it worth sacrificing that many people? If they made the same decision with the Ark Continent and the Demon Realm, then wouldn’t they have lost less?

Looking at the Demons, Zhao Hai didn’t treat them the way the Divines treated their vassals. Zhao Hai was always respectful to the Great Demon King. Even if he made an order, he still had a polite tone. This was also the reason why Fei’er wanted the Thunder Clan to submit to Zhao Hai.

Now, Zhao Hai had overturned the skies of the Divine Race. Being the first allies of Zhao Hai, the three clans would definitely be targeted by the Divines.

The nine Supreme Elders of the Divine Race were stronger than a Divine Race army. Under such circumstance, how could the three clans resist? The Divines surely wouldn’t be merciful to them. They were the main influence of the vassal race rebellion, the Divines would surely eliminate them.

In the past, Zhao Hai knew that they didn’t want to surrender to him, so he gave them the right to have equal dialogue. But now, the situation was related to the life and death of the three clans, so Zhao Hai could only present this proposition. Fei’er believed that Zhao Hai would surely save them and have a decisive battle with the Supreme Elders. If the time comes and Zhao Hai was defeated or killed, then the three clans would meet the retaliation of the entire Divine Race. When that time comes, they definitely wouldn’t be able to resist.

Fei’er knew that the best way to solve this situation was to go to the place that Zhao Hai presented. But will the Elders agree?

Fei’er can understand Zhao Hai’s indignation. Zhao Hai had looked after the three clans for a long time yet the three clans were still guarded against him. Think about, if you give unconditional help to a person and they still feel threatened against you, then wouldn’t you be angry?

Besides these things, Fei’er was also worried about the O’Neal family. If Zhao Hai was defeated, putting the Divine Race aside, what would happen to the O’Neal family? If Zhao Hai and the Divines manage to injure themselves heavily, then who would be able to fight against the magic armors?

One must know that the ones who managed to hold the O’Neal family off were the undead. These undead were from Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai was defeated, then the undead would definitely vanish. When the time comes, with both the O’Neal family and the Divine Race attacking them, the three clans would surely be done for.

After thinking about this, Fei’er couldn’t help but feel a cold sweat. At this time, an undead came to Fei’er’s side. The undead had three blood red command tokens on its hand. These command tokens had the Wild Dragon insignia on one side while a picture of a skeleton on the other. There were no characters on the token, only the marks and some decorations, it looked very refined.

Fei’er didn’t have time to admire the tokens as he quickly took them from the undead and immediately went to see Ding and Shan. He knew that they would have similar thoughts as himself and wanted to discuss the matter. No matter what, their clans couldn’t afford another huge loss. Otherwise, the clans wouldn’t be able to recover even after a hundred years. Most importantly, the clans were in risk of extermination. This matter was of extreme importance.

Chapter 927: The Might of the Taurus!

Zhao Hai calmly put away his messenger fish. However, his expression was quite ugly. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and comforted him, “Brother Hai, don’t think about it too much. At the worst, we could just abduct the three clans and go.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, I’ll be fine.”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “Brother Hai’s performance was very good. If we didn’t know, we would’ve believed that you were really angry.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, let’s not think about that anymore. What we need to think about is how to deal with the Divines. Right now, the Divine Race territory is completely undefended. I think the reason Elder Star and the others went to the continents was to take the other Seven Star Heaven Lock disks. It seems like the disks have been divided among the other continents in order to deal with us. Now that the Supreme Elders decided to deal with me in the Taurus Continent, they decided to take the disks with them.”

Laura nodded and said, “So what does Brother Hai plan to do?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We’ll begin with the Central Continent. At this point, the Central Continent had just been pacified. There’s close to no defenders left there, the ones that survived are the children and the elderly. We can turn the Central Continent into another Taurus Continent.”

Lizzy nodded and said, “That’s good. But Brother Hai, there are also vassal races in the Central Continent. Do you want to contact them?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Forget it. Those vassal races will be handed over to the foreign races to manage. We can’t just approach them at this time, they still don’t trust us.”

Lizzy agreed, “Alright, so do we start now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Yes, let’s begin right now.” After he said that, Zhao Hai commanded the Hell King’s ship to appear in Central City.

Central City had just calmed down. But after they saw the Hell King’s ship, the people were immediately shocked before their expressions changed. A lot of people from Central City were familiar with the Hell King’s ship. This ship was the cause of their current nightmare.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and immediately released large numbers of undead in order to capture the populace. Just like Zhao Hai said, the people of the Central Continent had lost their ability to resist.

When the Central Divines saw the Hell King’s ship, they were reminded about the horrible things that happened in Central City. This caused them to collapse and completely lose their strength.

Zhao Hai was successful in abducting the citizens. It took almost no effort to do so. After grabbing all the Divines, he proceeded to the next city.

Zhao Hai’s operation in the Central Continent went easier compared to the Taurus Continent. This was because in the past, the Taurus Divines still had their city defenses as well as their central government. Meanwhile, the Central Continent almost lost all of their soldiers, this made it too easy for Zhao Hai to capture the citizens.

The Central Continent was very big, it was much bigger than the Taurus Continent. However, Zhao Hai was very swift, it was as if he was catching sheep. Upon arriving at a city, he would quickly capture everyone. The process was very fast that it only took three days before he managed to wipe the entire Central Continent clean.

Bingya and the others followed every procedure. Zhao Hai didn’t hide everything from them as well. He also told Bingya and the others that the nine Supreme Elders have already decided to attack the Thunder Clan and the others. At this time, Zhao Hai was attacking the Divines in order to compel the other Supreme Elders to head back.

Bingya and the others didn’t object to Zhao Hai’s move. They thought that Zhao Hai was doing a very good job. Zhao Hai also used this method when the Divines were attacking the foreign races. Because of this, Bingya and the others didn’t even think that Zhao Hai would have plans for the three clans.

After cleaning the Central Continent, Zhao Hai didn’t proceed towards the Leo Continent. Although the Leo Continent had also experienced chaos, they weren’t actually that easy to deal with. It can be said that the Leo Continent didn’t suffer any major damage. Their main forces were still left basically untouched. Additionally, the Leo Divines hated Zhao Hai to the bones due to what he had done with Lion Rock. If Zhao Hai attacked the Leo Continent, then the Leo Divines would surely go all out in resisting him. Because of this, Zhao Hai opted to leave the Leo Continent alone for now. Instead, Zhao Hai went on to attack the Scorpio Continent.

The Scorpio Continent’s Supreme Elder was already dead and the Scorpio Divines were already aware of it. This had a huge effect on their morale. Although the Continent wasn’t chaotic, their motivation to battle was at an all-time low.

Moreover, in order to deal with the Scorpio Continent, Zhao Hai had come up with a good idea. Zhao Hai had turned the Scorpio Continent’s Supreme Elder into an undead. He plans to used that Supreme Elder and his Ultimate Weapon to attack the Scorpio Continent. He would also send the Devil Legion. He believed that once the Scorpio Continent’s soldiers see their Supreme Elder using his ultimate weapon to attack them, their confidence would immediately be gone. This way, it would be very convenient for Zhao Hai to capture them.

Zhao Hai followed Elder Star and the others when they went to the other continents. Because of this, Zhao Hai only used the Space to reach the Scorpio Continent. He didn’t waste any time being on the road.

Elder Star and the others didn’t have the same ability. They can only hurry along, flying from continent to continent. Even if they were Supreme Elders, they still needed to use two days for travel. When Zhao Hai attacked the Scorpio Continent, only then did the Supreme Elders arrive at the Taurus Continent.

In these several days, Fei’er and the others returned to their own clans. They sought an audience with their Patriarchs and relayed Zhao Hai’s words. Moreover, Fei’er and the others reached an agreement. They would urge their Patriarchs to have their people enter Zhao Hai’s Space.

Fei’er knew that this matter wouldn’t be easy. However, he didn’t think about how difficult it would be.

Upon returning to his clan, almost everyone opposed to Zhao Hai’s idea, they thought it was just Zhao Hai’s scheme. It was impossible for nine Supreme Elders to unite just to deal with them. No matter how Fei’er urged his people, they remained unmoved.

Fei’er’s time with Zhao Hai was quite long. So Fei’er understood that Zhao Hai wasn’t the type to joke around with these matters. Because of this, Fei’er and the others completely believed Zhao Hai’s words.

Fei’er still had quite a reputation in his clan. So even if he wasn’t permitted by the Patriarch and the Elders, he still talked to his family as well as those close to him and have them prepare for relocation. At the same time, Fei’er also called Zhao Hai on his messenger fish, asking for permission to use the command token.

Zhao Hai knew the situation with the three clans, this was how much Fei’er and the others trust him. Naturally, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to not give Fei’er any face. Because of this, after being contacted, he immediately opened a spatial rift. Those who were willing to move were immediately allowed passage.

Since Fei’er was also well-known among the youth of his clan, some of them were willing to follow. There were also some women as well as some elderly people who moved.

However, Fei’er wasn’t able to move that many people. This was because Zhao Hai just told them that the nine Supreme Elders would soon arrive.

Fei’er immediately directed those who wanted to move to enter the Space. Fei’er never entered the Space before, so he was trusting Zhao Hai’s word. But when he arrived inside the Space, he couldn’t help but get stunned. The environment inside was very good. There were even some picturesque mountains and rivers inside. And as it turns out, Zhao Hai prepared this place for the three clans to settle in.

This was an ordinary background that Zhao Hai bought before. Inside this background were a lot of houses as well as bread trees and bamboo rice. Because of this, the three clans wouldn’t have to worry about survival once they move in. Even if there were a lot of them and some weren’t able to stay inside the ready-built homes, there was still no problem. The Space’s environment was just too good, it far surpassed Fei’er’s imagination. Even if they were to lie down outside, the grass was soft and fragrant. It was actually more comfortable to lie down on the grass than to stay indoors.

The actions of Fei’er and the others managed to anger the patriarchs and elders of their clans. This caused them to be more strict, forbidding people to relocate. In the end, they even sent an army to stop this.

At this time, the total number of people who moved inside the Space was still less than 100 thousand, it was too small. Fei’er and the others had no way to fight against the Patriarch’s decision. In the end, they had to close the spatial rift, and Fei’er, Ding, and Shan were imprisoned. They weren’t even allowed to come in contact with the outside world.

During all of this, Zhao Hai attacked the Scorpio Continent. Zhao Hai had the Scorpio Supreme Elder head the attack. Along with the Devil Legion’s help, they went to deal with the Scorpio Divines.

Upon seeing their dead Supreme Elder as well as the Scorpio ultimate weapon, the Scorpio soldiers collapsed immediately. With only a thought, Zhao Hai took them into the Space.

While Zhao Hai was absorbing the Divines into the Space, Elder Star and the others had set foot on the Taurus Continent. Gold Ben didn’t even hesitate as he led the group and headed towards the spatial rifts of the three clans.

The Thunder Clan and the others weren’t vassals for a day or two. Because of this, Gold Ben was completely clear about their location. With no effort, Gold Ben found the spatial rifts.

The spatial rifts of the three clans were close together. However, the first spatial rift that Gold Ben and the others came upon was the one that belonged to the Thunder Clan.

Although the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch didn’t believe that the Supreme elders would attack them, he still had some precautions. He arranged a large army to the spatial rift and reinforced their defensive line.

When Gold Ben arrived at the spatial rift, this was the scene that they witnessed. The nine Supreme Elders went into a formation before slowly pressing towards the Thunder Clan’s spatial rift

The Thunder Clan’s garrison troops were also able to see Gold Ben and the others. Although the soldiers didn’t know who Gold Ben was, they could still see that the nine people were here with evil intentions. Someone from the defensive line loudly said, “To the people in front. You have entered the Thunder Clan’s defensive zone. Please retreat immediately or else we will identify you as an enemy and we will proceed to attack.”

Upon seeing the Thunder Clan’s people, Gold Ben’s anger quickly flared up. He gave a menacing smile as he laughed and said, “You Thunder Clan slaves. You aren’t this unyielding in the past. Who gave you such courage? You actually dared to drive us away. I really don’t know whether you want to live or die.”

When the garrison troops heard Gold Ben’s words, their expression changed. The name ‘Thunder Clan slaves’ rang too familiar. In the past, the Taurus Divines always called them by this name. Therefore, the troops quickly knew that Gold Ben wasn’t here to be friendly.

At this moment, the garrison commander immediately said, “Prepare the javelins for attack! Don’t let them get close!”

Upon seeing this situation, Gold Ben turned to the other Supreme Elders and said, “Everyone, these people are my Taurus Continent’s slaves. Although the Taurus Clan no longer exists, please leave the punishment to me!”

Elder Star and the others nodded. They didn’t oppose Gold Ben’s method. With this defensive line, there was no need for any one of them to make a move.

After seeing that the others agreed, Gold Ben turned to look back at the Thunder Clan. The Thunder Clan’s reinforced defensive line simply wasn’t a threat to him. Because of this, Gold Ben immediately equipped his Taurus Combat Suit and slowly headed forward. Then he pulled his fists towards his waist before launching a punch with his right arm and shouting, “Taurus Charge!” Upon launching his attack, a huge bull appeared in front of his fist and directly soared towards the defensive line.

The golden bull rushed forward. It grew bigger and bigger as though it was absorbing the surrounding energy. When the golden bull appeared in front of the Thunder Clan army, it was already 20 meters high.The golden bull slammed towards the defensive line, causing a large explosion. The defensive line wall which was nearly ten meters tall was torn apart like paper.

At this time, Gold Ben’s left fist punched out. The second golden bulls tore another part of the wall. Now, the Thunder Clan’s defensive line had a huge 60 meter-wide gap.

Elder Star was standing right behind Gold Ben. He gave a nod and said, “Gold Ben’s two punches seem to be three times more powerful than before. His emotion really allowed his power to soar.”

The other Supreme Elders couldn’t help but agree. They could also see that Gold Ben was fiercer that before. The reason he was like this was naturally the extermination of the Taurus Continent. In addition to his raw power, Gold Ben’s fists now carry his resentment towards his enemies.

Chapter 928: You Think The Divines Are Stupid?

Two fists, it only took two fists before the Thunder Clans’ reinforced wall to collapse. Dozens of people were killed as well, a cruel death by being smashed to paste by a fist.

Besides the destroyed wall, the construction around and behind it was razed completely. The support troops that were there, about a hundred soldiers, were also killed.

The might of just two fists, nobody thought that this would happen!

But although the two fists killed dozens of people, the garrison commander managed to survive. The commander quickly made some adjustments, removing all Thunder Clan troops from the wall.

The Thunder Clan’s defensive line was made in stages. This meant that even if one wall collapses, not everything will be turned to waste.

Naturally, Gold Ben can see the onion-like construction of the Thunder Clan’s walls. When he entered the broken walls, he was immediately met with a rain of javelins.

Gold Ben didn’t dare to neglect these attacks. He knew that these javelins could explode and their strength might compare to blood lightning beads.

Gold Ben always thought that it was strange. The Divines were the ones who used blood lightning beads first. However, Zhao Hai actually managed to learn how to make them. Additionally, Zhao Hai’s blood lightning beads were much better than the ones made by the Divines.

Gold Ben waved his hand, forming a crouching bull that blocked the javelins. When the javelins exploded, Gold Ben moved his two arms to support his shield.

It can be said that the Thunder Clan’s defensive line was made magnificently, and it was even layered. However, Gold Ben’s strength was terrifying. After exerting more attacks, Gold Ben managed to destroy the entire defensive line. Gold Ben received his ultimate weapon before flying towards the Thunder Clan’s plane.

As Gold Ben attacked the Thunder Clan’s defensive line, the defenders also sent the news back to the Thunder Clan. In the past, Zhao Hai dealt with the Taurus Divines with the cooperation of the three clans. During that time, Zhao Hai provided them with messenger fishes. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t take them back, so the messenger fishes were still in their possession.

Although the Thunder Clan’s people didn’t know any Supreme Elders, Gold Ben’s strength alone was a testament to his status. And with Zhao Hai’s earlier reminder, the Thunder Clan was able to affirm who Gold Ben and the others were.

After confirming that it was Gold Ben, the Thunder Clan couldn’t help but get flustered. The strength of the Taurus Supreme Elder was known to be world-shaking. Now, he was here to attack them. How could the Thunder Clan resist?

It was at this time that the Thunder Clan’s people discovered that they didn’t have the qualifications to be treated as Zhao Hai’s equal. Zhao Hai managed to defeat a Supreme Elder. Moreover, in order to deal with him, the nine Supreme Elders actually united. On the other hand, the whole Thunder Clan wasn’t even a match to one Supreme Elder. If Zhao Hai wanted to ruin the Thunder Clan, then that would be too easy to do.

In this situation, the Patriarch had no choice but to release Fei’er. Upon hearing the present situation, Fei’er’s expression couldn’t help but turn difficult.

Fei’er looked at the Patriarch and said, “Patriarch, we can only find a way to constrain the nine Supreme Elders. We need our people to enter Mister’s Space. I think we should select 100 thousand people to do the sacrifice ritual. Use the thunder net in order to block the nine Supreme Elders. We need time to transfer everyone towards the Space.”

Upon hearing Fei’er’s words, the Patriarch’s face couldn’t help but change. The Thunder Clan really did have a sacrifice ritual. Almost every Thunder Clan member can use this method. This ritual would allow a person to undergo a massive increase in strength for ten days. However, after ten days, that person would turn to ash. Most importantly, this ritual was irreversible. This meant that as long as someone used this ritual, that person was as good as dead.

The collective strength of 100 thousand people using the ritual would amount to an astonishing amount. Even Supreme Elders wouldn’t be able to deal with them in a short period of time. However, these 100 thousand people would die after ten days. For the Thunder Clan, this was no doubt a huge damage.

The Patriarch looked at Fei’er and said, “Do you have any other methods? Isn’t 100 thousand people too much?”

Fei’er forced a smile and said, “Patriarch, 100 thousand people isn’t a lot. We might even add more people in the future. During the past battles, we witnessed Mister fight with the Taurus Supreme Elder. The Supreme Elder was very strong, his attack strength was formidable. This 100 thousand people might be able to block the Supreme Elder. However, we shouldn’t forget that there are eight other Supreme Elders. Nine Supreme Elders couldn’t be blocked that easily. I’m not even certain that those 100 thousand would be able to block the nine Supreme Elders.”

The Patriarch’s face became quite difficult as he looked at Fei’er. His expression sunk and said, “Is Mister Zhao Hai unable to rescue us?” After hearing the Patriarch say this, it was Fei’er’s turn to have a difficult expression. He looked at the Patriarch and said, “Mister Zhao Hai is currently attacking the Divine Race territory in the hopes that the Supreme Elders would retreat. If the Supreme Elders don’t come back, then mister might come and have a decisive battle with the Supreme Elders. But if mister becomes defeated, then wouldn’t the result the same as the one we’re facing right now? It might even be possible that our escape route would disappear.”

The Patriarch hesitated, he became silent for quite a while. Fei’er looked at the Patriarch’s expression and couldn’t help but feel angry. Fei’er said, “Patriarch, there’s no need to think about it anymore. What duty does mister have for him to die for us? Are we worthy for him to go all out against the nine Supreme Elders? If it was you, would you fight someone powerful for someone who didn’t even have great trust towards you? Will you sacrifice yourself for someone who is always guarded against you?”

Fei’er’s words were very impolite. This caused the Patriarch’s expression to turn uglier. He coldly snorted and said, “Are you really sure that the Supreme Elders won’t let us go? If we go under Zhao Hai’s command, then we might as well surrender to the Divine Race!”

Not only Fei’er, even the some Elders couldn’t help but doubt what they just heard. This statement was just too stupid. Everyone was clear about the result.

Fei’er looked at the Patriarch, disappointment evident on his face, and said, “Is this the Patriarch’s decision? Do you really want to punish our Thunder Clan?”

After hearing this, the Patriarch’s expression worsened. Then he slammed his hand on the table and shouted, “Even if we are killed, we will never be Zhao Hai’s slaves! Come, lock him up for me!”

Several of the Elders who were present didn’t do anything. Among them, the one who was the most unwilling was Elder Zhen. He had cooperated with Zhao Hai before so held some understanding regarding the man.

At the same time, Elder Zhen also discovered that ever since they had defeated the Taurus Divines, the Patriarch had become more and more like a dictator. He started to believe that he was an Emperor. He became a Patriarch that didn’t consider what his people thought.

Elder Zhen looked at the Patriarch before grabbing Fei’er. He couldn’t just stay quiet as he stood up and said, “Patriarch, the situation is already very clear. If we wait any longer, then all of us would only die. Do you really want to sacrifice the entire Thunder Clan like this? If that is the case, then you are no longer qualified to become the Patriarch of the Thunder Clan.”

Elder Zhen was the Thunder Clan’s Great Elder. His status in the clan was very high. Every word he spoke had a certain weight behind it. This was because the Elder’s Assembly had the ability to impeach a Patriarch.

When the Patriarch heard this, his face turned for the worst. He slammed the table with even more force and said, “Elder Zhen, do you know what you just said? Do you want to rebel?”

Elder Zhen looked at the Patriarch and coldly snorted, “Patriarch, are you serious? Rebellion? Don’t forget, the Elder’s Assembly has the right to impeach a Patriarch. You don’t have the capabilities to call me a rebel. I support Fei’er’s plan. We should immediately organize people to do the sacrifice ritual and block the nine Supreme Elders. We don’t have much time left, we need to relocate to mister Zhao Hai’s Space. I’ve met Mister Zhao Hai before, he certainly won’t treat us as slaves. He hates slavery.”

The Patriarch coldly snorted and said, “Who knows if he was just acting.”

At this time, another elder stood up and angrily shouted, “So what does the Patriarch want? Do we just wait for our deaths?”

Then another elder stood up and countered, “And what about you? Is becoming another person’s dog that good? I’d rather die in battle than become someone’s slave.”

Elder Zhen looked at that elder and berated, “You watch your mouth. Who said we would become slaves? And do you really want our clan to perish for this courageous spirit that you have? Mister Zhao Hai will not enslave us. The Demons and the people from the Ark Continent subordinated themselves to Mister Zhao Hai, and they didn’t become slaves. So why can’t we do the same?”

That elder sneered and said, “Zhao Hai didn’t enslave the Demons and the people from the Ark Continent, but did that mean that he didn’t have slaves? If we surrender to Zhao Hai, then we might as well just surrender to the Divines. At the very least, we can still live in our plane without going to a strange place.”

Upon hearing this, Fei’er couldn’t help but sneer, “Surrender to the Divines? Do you really think that you have the qualifications? The vassal rebellion is all because of us. And at this time, you want to surrender? Who do you think we are? Can we just revolt whenever we want to revolt and surrender whenever we want to surrender? When did the Divines become that forgiving? You really think that the Divines are that stupid?”

Chapter 929: Dealing With The Cancer Clan

Both sides were unyielding. Nobody can make anyone change their minds. A brawl almost happened in the hall. In the end, Fei’er could only shake his head as he left the room full of indignation.

After leaving the hall, Elder Zhen immediately called the Elders who were close to him. Then he proceeded to urge their clansmen to leave the clan while also organizing a suicide troop. The troop would perform the sacrificial ritual together in order to deal with the Supreme Elders.[1]

As the Thunder Clan’s Great Elder, Elder Zhen held a high prestige in the clan. And with Fei’er by his side, their influence was not lower compared to the patriarch. Moreover, with Fei’er’s military authority, it didn’t take too long for them to find people willing to sacrifice themselves.

Before when Fei’er was rallying his people, the majority of those who came with him were the young members of his clan. On the other hand, most of those with elderly age weren’t convinced by Fei’er’s words. Because of this, the people who were sent to the Space were very small compared to the Thunder Clan’s total population.

The suicide troop of 100 thousand was quickly organized. At the same time, about five hundred thousand households became willing to enter Zhao Hai’s Space.

Five hundred thousand households was quite a lot. This was equal to an entire province back in the Ark Continent. These people were also the only ones who were convinced by Fei’er despite his best efforts. There were still a lot of Thunder Clan members who didn’t want to leave their ancestral home.

The Patriarch’s group  was also planning to organize their own suicide army. However, their purpose was different compared to Fei’er. Fei’er wanted to organize a troop in order to hold the Supreme Elders long enough for the Thunder Clan clansmen to enter the Space. On the other hand, the Patriarch wanted to organize a troop in order to make the Divines understand that the Thunder Clan weren’t easily dealt with. With this, the Thunder Clan might have more talking power when they surrender.

Fei’er and the others had already separated themselves from the Patriarch’s rule. Fei’er organized his people to move together and headed towards Thunder Valley and opened a spatial rift there. Then the people proceeded to head inside the Space.

Outside the valley, Fei’er personally led the 100 hundred thousand suicide troops to block the entrance to the valley. They would block the Supreme Elders from attacking the migrating households.

All the Thunder Clan members who entered the Space immediately fell in love with the environment. On the other hand, those who were yet to enter started to panic. They knew that their enemies were the nine Supreme Elders. They also knew that their Patriarch was prepared to surrender to the Divines.

After the commoners knew about this information, they immediately ran to Fei’er. If they go with Fei’er, they believed that their future would be safe.

These commoners weren’t stupid. Most of them knew how miserably they offended the Divine Race. Even if the Divines accepted their surrender, what would happen next? If they would return to their past state, then they might as well go to Zhao Hai’s Space.

As the matter stands, more and more people decided to enter Zhao Hai’s Space. It already came to a point where the Patriarch could no longer stop them.

At this time, a problem arose. The nine Supreme Elders had already started to attack the Thunder Clan. Moreover, they seem to be intent in the elimination of  the entire race. They didn’t even try to take captives. This meant that those who went to battle would surely die.

This made the Thunder Clan Patriarch finally realize that the situation wasn’t good. He immediately organized themselves and prepared to use the sacrifice ritual in order to block the Supreme Elders.

However, the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch discovered something. Unexpectedly, nobody in his side was willing to become members of the suicide troop. It was a huge contrast compared to Fei’er’s side.

The Thunder Clan’s Patriarch didn’t have the time to organize a proper army to resist the nine Supreme Elders. After all, he was preparing to surrender and negotiate with the Divines.

This was where the Thunder Clan’s patriarch had forgotten about something. Only those with leverage had the power for negotiation. If you weren’t strong and you were on the side of the defeated, then what right do you have to discuss terms with the enemy?

Naturally, the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch haven’t thought about this. In his opinion, the Divines wouldn’t dare to destroy them. Otherwise, the Divines wouldn’t be able to rule the vassal races.

However, the Patriarch had forgotten the fact that they were the main cause of the vassal race rebellion. If the Divines didn’t eliminate them as a punishment for the others, then they wouldn’t be able to control the other vassal races.

Moreover, Gold Ben and the others only came here because of Zhao Hai. They would eliminate the Thunder Clan first, then the Barbarians, and then the Winged Pegasus. They plan to make Zhao Hai retreat.

Because of this, Gold Ben and the others didn’t even think about getting captives. They intend to exterminate the Thunder Clan. They weren’t interested in surrender, negotiations, and the like. All they want to do right now was to attack and kill.

Although there were only nine of them this time, these people were more terrifying than 90 million people. Even if they numbered only nine, their individual and collective might wasn’t weak. Therefore, the Thunder Clan would certainly eat a huge loss once the battle starts.

But the Patriarch’s group could only resist. At this time, Fei’er was transferring 500 thousand households to the Space, this was more than 2 million people. Moving this number of people to the Space wouldn’t take a day or two. Because of this, Fei’er could only lead the suicide troop to defend the valley’s entrance.

Even if Fei’er and the others were defending the valley entrance, they were still receiving news from the battle between the Thunder Clan and the Supreme Elders. At the same time, more and more Thunder Clan members began pouring towards the valley. This only meant that the situation had worsened to a certain degree.

Fei’er didn’t have the means to solve this. If he went to attack the Divines, then the valley would turn dangerous. If he went out, then the Patriarch might even use them. The Patriarch was still hoping to surrender.

Fei’er already told Ding and Shan about the current situation. Ding and Shan weren’t having good times either. They had met people from their clans and were met with the same outcome as Fei’er. A lot of people were against moving, especially their Patriarchs.

Fei’er wanted them to move as soon as possible. He told them that the Divines weren’t intending to take any survivors. Ding and Shan needed to send their people to the Space at the earliest time.

However, Ding and Shan’s present situation was the same as Fei’er. Those who were close to them and those who respected them were the only ones who agreed to move towards the Space. Ding and Shan could only break out from the cells with no consideration for the clan’s face. They were afraid that it would be too late for their people to move towards the Space. A civil strife began in their clans.

Fei’er felt very awkward regarding this situation. He didn’t want to urge them to revolt. After all, this was a different clan’s matter, it wouldn’t be good for him to meddle.

However, Fei’er was worried about the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus. The population of the two clans was much greater compared to the Thunder Clan. In this case, it would take an even longer time for their people to move towards the Space. Now that the Supreme Elders were mowing through the Thunder Clan, it was the best time for the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus to make their move. If they delay, then they would be risking the lives of their people.

Fei’er didn’t have better means to express this thought towards Ding and Shan. Because of this, he could only tell it to Zhao Hai.

But Zhao Hai was currently attacking the Cancer Continent right now. The Cancer Continent was quite difficult to deal with. This was because their Supreme Elder Jie Yu had some reputation among the Divine Race. Although Elder Star held the highest position among all the Supreme Elders, Elder Jie Yu was the foremost expert of the Divine Race. This caused his clansmen to have a certain arrogance towards their strength. In their opinion, they couldn’t afford to have Elder Jie Yu lose face.

Because of this thought, the Cancer Clan’s defense was quite hard to deal with. But because of the current circumstances, Zhao Hai would naturally be impolite. He released his undead, the Devil Legion, and his Cavalry Army. He sent them to all directions in order to deal with the Cancer clan as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai’s method was very successful. After releasing his army, even the Cancer Divines wouldn’t be able to resist. The Cancer Divines could only defend for three days before they were cleaned up.

Nobody could blame them for falling so fast. Zhao Hai’s undead were as strong as they were. Moreover, there was the much stronger undead troops under Qing Feng and Mingyue. Then there was the Ultimate Weapon equipped Devil Legion. There simply was nobody that could defend against them. And with their Supreme Elder absent, the Cancer Clan’s fall was inevitable.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai’s army outnumbered the Cancer Continent’s troops. There simply was no chance for the Cancer Divines. Zhao Hai also received the news from Fei’er. However, he didn’t immediately return to help. He would wait until Gold Ben attacks the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus before he turns back.

He needed to make the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus be willing to submit. If the two clans still refused, then Zhao Hai would wait for some time.

Up until now, the three clans were still unwilling to trust Zhao Hai. The three clans’ Patriarchs were very ambitious people. If the Space accepts such people, then they would certainly cause trouble. Because of this, Zhao Hai changed his mind. He would use Gold Ben and the others to teach the three clans a lesson. Zhao Hai would make the three clans understand that without him, they would easily fall to the Divines.

Zhao Hai didn’t give Fei’er a concrete answer, he just expressed his acknowledgement of the report. Fei’er couldn’t blame Zhao Hai. To be honest, even Fei’er was disappointed of his people. Because of this, he could only accept this result.

* * *

I’ve been stopping myself from calling it ‘Suicide Squad’ xd

Chapter 930: Sagittarius Clan’s Magic Formation

Although Zhao Hai had conquered the Central, Scorpio, and the Cancer Continents, he didn’t actually touch their Fishman tribes. He wanted the Fishmen to spread the information to the other Divines. He needed Gold Ben and the others to be aware of what was happening.

Gold Ben and the others were now forcing Zhao Hai to fight them by attacking the Thunder Clan and the others. But if Zhao Hai continually eliminates the Divines, would Gold Ben and the others keep being calm? At this time, Zhao Hai and the Supreme Elders were in a battle of who would lose their composure first. The one who returns would be the loser.

After cleaning the defenders of the Cancer Continent, Zhao Hai proceeded to capture any remaining Divines. Zhao Hai couldn’t just let go of this opportunity.

Zhao Hai wanted the Divines to get ahold of his movements. However, he didn’t anticipate that this news would also reach the ears of the foreign races and the vassal races.

After hearing this information, the foreign races and the major vassal races immediately exerted pressure on the Divines. The Divines and the vassal races were now irreconcilable. At the same time, the foreign races wanted to take their revenge for tens of thousands of years. Even if one side wanted to solve this enmity, it would be impossible to do so. Therefore, when they heard that the Divines were being cleaned up by Zhao Hai, they immediately burst with joy.

While the Divines were flustered, the vassal races immediately launched a full force attack towards the Divines.

On the other hand, although the foreign races also sent their armies, they didn’t send their Supreme Elders along. This was because the foreign races were still afraid of Elder Star and the others. They knew that if Elder Star and the others made a move, then they would definitely target the foreign races’ base.

After Zhao Hai dealt with the Cancer Divines, he immediately turned his attention to another continent. This time, Zhao Hai intends to attack the Sagittarius Divines.

The Sagittarius Divines were quite a different type of people. Their archers were trained from a very early age. Because of this, their archery was the strongest among the other Divines.

At the same time, their weapons were also special. What they use for combat was the bow and arrow. However, these bow and arrows weren’t ordinary ones. The bows were inscribed with magic formations, the same was true for their arrows.

The magic formations inscribed on the bows allowed the Sagittarius Divines to condense energy into the arrow. On the other hand, the formation on the arrow increased its lethality.

The energy arrows of the Sagittarius Archers wasn’t their most powerful means of attack. The magic formation inscribed on their bows also allowed them the ability to use energy to bend their arrows. If one had enough energy to charge both bows and arrows, then they would be extremely lethal. However, if one was weak, then their arrows might not even be able to injure anyone.

At the same time, their arrows also had more than one type of magic formation. Wind-element formations could allow the arrow to fly a longer distance. Fire-element arrows would cause a powerful explosion. Wood-element formations would poison the target. Water-element formations made the arrow’s trajectory unable to be predicted. Metal-element formations increased the arrow’s penetrating power. And finally, Light-element arrows made it very hard to evade.

This didn’t mean that the Sagittarius Divines were advanced in terms of magic formations. In fact, almost all of the Sagittarius Clan’s magic formations were passed down from generation to generation. Modifications on these magic formations were practically non-existent.

This was because of the Deity’s order to stop research on magic formations.

Although Lu Wei did forbade them to research magic formations, the Divines didn’t have any interest in researching them anyways. Even if their magic formations were from ancient times, given the skills of the Sagittarius Archers, they were still a terrifying existence in the Divine Realm.

They can augment their archery using their own energy. As long as they don’t use all of their power, they would be able to fire arrows endlessly.. Even if they run out of arrows, as long as they had energy, they could still kill.

Although they were called the Divine Race, this didn’t mean that they were true gods. The items of the Divine Race might not be found in the Ark Continent, but they weren’t unlimited in the Divine Realm either. Because of this, the arrows of a Sagittarius Archer can be exhausted. This discouraged the archers on being be too reliant on their arrows.

As for energy, it belonged to their own. Through the inscriptions on their bows, the archers were able to shoot hundreds to thousands of energy arrows in succession. Because of this, archers would only carry one or two quivers of arrows, and each quiver only had 12 arrows.

Even with these restrictions, nobody in the Divine Realm was willing to provoke the Sagittarius Divines. Not only because of their arrows, but also due to their peak capability for assassinations.

An archer could hide inside a location. And when one let their guard down, the archer would immediately unleash a fatal arrow. This was something terrifying to think of.

In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t have that much understanding when it came to the Sagittarius Divines. But after asking Bingya and the others, he was finally able to have a clear idea. Now, Zhao Hai was curious about the Sagittarius Divines, especially their ancient magic formations.

One must know that these magic formations were strictly hidden so that no outsider would know about them. And even if other people got ahold of their weapons, they still wouldn’t be able to know how to use the formations.

Although the Sagittarius bows and arrows had magic formations inscribed in them, almost all of these formations were deeply hidden. These formations were also wrapped with other magic formations in order to hide their image. Moreover, if one wanted to destroy the bows to see inside, a magic formation inside would activate and blow the weapon. The arrows also had self-destruct functions. As long as an arrow was used, then it was ruined. One would only recover a useless arrow shaft. If one were to open the arrow, it would also explode.

This caused Zhao Hai to be curious about these bows and arrows. He wanted to know what magic formations were inscribed on these weapons. Once he knew about these magic formations, then Zhao Hai’s undead cavalry would be able to display an even more terrifying strength.

Zhao Hai’s attack on the Sagittarius Continent began immediately. This was because he didn’t need to spend time on travelling unlike Gold Ben and the others. After cleaning the Cancer Continent, he immediately teleported towards the Sagittarius Continent.

When Zhao Hai started to attack the Sagittarius Continent, he was immediately faced with a resistance from the Sagittarius Archers. A wave of arrows came crashing down on Zhao Hai. These arrows were really strong, they were actually able to hurt the undead. Zhao Hai didn’t expect this.

However, it was still impossible for the Sagittarius Divines to block the attack. And even if Zhao Hai didn’t have their magic formations, he still had magic cannons and the javelin throwing cavalry undead. This allowed Zhao Hai’s undead to suffer the least amount of damage. Most importantly, even if the undead were hurt, it still wouldn’t affect their combat prowess.

At the same time, the Devil Legion were protected by their combat suits. Even if the Devil Legion’s strength wasn’t able to display a monumental increase, the combat suits were still able to block the Sagittarius Divines’ arrows.

Just as Zhao Hai was attacking the Sagittarius Divines, information about the fall of the three continents reached the ears of Gold Ben and the others. Upon hearing this, the Supreme Elders couldn’t help but be startled. They have yet to conquer the Thunder Clan but Zhao Hai already eliminated three continents. It wasn’t strange for Gold Ben and the others to be surprised.

Originally, Gold Ben and the others wanted to slowly attack the Thunder Clan in order to wait for Zhao Hai’s response. But now, it looks like Zhao Hai was more cruel than them. Naturally, the Supreme Elders could no longer hold back. Nine people fully exerted their powers and attacked the Thunder Clan. In about five days, the Thunder Clan was almost razed to the ground. At this time, the only surviving members of the Thunder Clan were inside the mountain valley where Fei’er and the others were.

At this time, the mountain valley had refugees that numbered to about a million households. These people were the ones who didn’t follow Fei’er early on. When adding this number to the households that followed Fei’er in the beginning, the people that needed to be moved to the Space had numbered 1.5 million households.

It was impossible for this valley to hold 1.5 million households. However, this mountain valley wasn’t small either. Luckily, more than 800 thousand households had already transferred inside the Space. Otherwise, this mountain valley would have already overflowed.

However, Fei’er’s group was now faced with a difficult problem. At this time, there was still about six hundred thousand households inside the valley. And Elder Star’s group was heading towards them.

As Gold Ben and the others were heading towards the mountain valley. Fei’er decided that he would lead the 100 thousand defenders and use the sacrifice ritual. They needed to block Gold Ben and the others in order to give their people enough time to get inside the Space.

Just as Fei’er was about to do the sacrifice ritual, Elder Zhen suddenly appeared and stopped him. Fei’er looked confused at Elder Zhen and said, “Great Elder, why did you stop me? Leave this place to me, go and lead our people into the Space.”

Elder Zhen shook his head and looked at Fei’er, “Fei’er, you go. Guide our people to the Space, leave this place to me.”

Fei’er stared, then his expression changed as he said, “That’s wouldn’t happen. Great Elder, just leave me here. This is my idea, I should be the one who sees it to the end.”

Elder Zhen just calmly replied, “Fei’er, don’t be hard-headed. I’ll defend. You are still young and you have the best relationship with Zhao Hai among us. Go and take our people to a brighter future. I can’t do that, I’m already too old. I’ll leave the clan to you. I should have believed in you from the very beginning, yet I didn’t. This caused us to miss the best opportunity to move towards the Space. Remember, after going inside the Space, never strive to become Mister Zhao Hai’s equal. We’re only his subordinates.” After he said that, Elder Zhen’s body started to shake. Then his aura exploded, surpassing his original one.

After seeing this situation, Fei’er couldn’t help but gawk. This was because he knew that Elder Zhen just performed the sacrifice ritual. Fei’er understood that it was already too late.

Once Elder Zhen used the sacrifice ritual, the other 100 thousand members of the suicide troop also used the ritual. Nobody hesitated, all of them were fearless.

Fei’er looked at his people, already knowing that they were practically dead. Tears started streaming down his face as he banged his head to the ground three times. Then he straightened his body and loudly said, “Brothers, in behalf of the Thunder Clan, this Fei’er expresses our deepest gratitude. Rest assured, this Fei’er will definitely lead our people to a much better future.”

Elder Zhen loudly laughed. Mixed in that laughter was his overwhelming heroic spirit, then he said, “Fei’er, we’ll leave our clan over to you. Don’t let our sacrifice go in vain. Be relieved, we will make those Supreme Elders know that the Thunder Clan wouldn’t easily fall. Go tell Mister Zhao Hai that I apologize. I should have believed in him from the very beginning. Tell him to take revenge for me!”

Fei’er gave a nod, then he said, “Great Elder, rest assured. I will certainly relay your message. I will be engraving everybody’s name down. The Thunder Clan will never forget you!”

Elder Zhen laughed, then he pat Fei’er’s shoulder and said, “Go. Lead our people to leave this place. I’ll be leaving the clan over to you.” Then after that, Elder Zhen took an object and gave it to Fei’er.

Fei’er looked at the item, it was a magic formation plate. Fei’er knew that this was a treasure of the Thunder Clan. Unfortunately this formation plate didn’t have any attacking power. Instead, it had the ability to create a large amount of fog, enough to hide an entire city.

Upon seeing this formation plate, Fei’er immediately understood what Elder Zhen wanted to do. Elder Zhen wanted Fei’er to use this formation plate to block the valley. This would hide the mountain valley from the Supreme Elders. This way, the Supreme Elders would be clueless about what was happening. If the Supreme Elders knew that they were moving to the Space, then they will certainly go all out in attacking. For the Thunder Clan, this wasn’t a good outcome.

Most importantly, Gold Ben and the others were still waiting for Zhao Hai’s response. It’s possible that they were still holding back. Both Fei’er and Elder Zhen didn’t want any other mishap to occur.

Chapter 931: Firm Like A Rock, Unmoving Like A Mountain!

Upon seeing the fog on the mountain, a sneer appeared on a corner of Jie Yu’s mouth. The turned to Elder Star and said, “Elder Star, it seems like these guys still have some courage left inside them. They still want to do a final defense. Then we would have to be impolite. Let’s make them understand what extinction means!” Elder Star, through gritted teeth, replied, “Zhao Hai has already destroyed several Divine Clans. It’s time to make him taste what losing someone feels like. Let’s begin!”

Elder Jie Yu had the same ugly expression as Elder Star. This was because he didn’t think that after dealing with the Central and Scorpio Continent, Zhao Hai would target the Cancer Continent. Moreover, Zhao Hai directly exterminated his clan. This was a huge attack to Jie Yu.

After knowing knowing about the elimination of the Cancer Clan, Jie Yu as well as the other Elders began to be more ruthless towards the Thunder Clan. Besides those who died on the spot, those who didn’t resist were treated miserably by Jie Yu.

Elder Star and the others didn’t say anything about Jie Yu’s actions. In fact, they were also very cruel towards the Thunder Clan. After being beaten by Zhao Hai time and time again, their hearts couldn’t help but feel constricted. Because of this, they could only vent their anger on the Thunder Clan.

As the Supreme Elders flew towards the mountain valley, a troop suddenly flew out.

Naturally, these people were Elder Zhen and the others. Elder Zhen slowly flew to face Gold Ben and the others, his face  was as calm as it can be. At this point, their only wish was to block Gold Ben and the others for ten days so that Fei’er would have enough time to evacuate. Because of this, Elder Zhen and the others held no emotions towards Gold Ben anymore. They needed to buy time. It didn’t matter who they were facing, they needed jusr to do their duty.

Gold Ben and the others didn’t attack immediately. They stopped and observed Elder Zhen’s group. In the past few days, the Thunder Clan members who blocked them were too many to count. However, none were successful. Because of this, Gold Ben and the others were no longer worried. They just wanted to see the desperate expression on these people’s faces.

However, they were left disappointed. Elder Zhen and the others were extremely calm. Elder Zhen only spared Gold Ben a glance before he turned to his 100 thousand troops and said, “Brave warriors of the Thunder Clan. We are the last hope of our family. For the Thunder Clan, let’s do our best!”

All of the Thunder Clan soldiers behind him simultaneously shouted, “For the Thunder Clan!”

Gold Ben couldn’t help but look at Elder Zhen’s troops with disdain. However, he could also note that this Thunder Clan army wasn’t the same as the ones they had met in the past few days. Although those people were also blocking the Supreme Elders, they lacked an imposing manner. However, the ones in front of him right now had very formidable heroic auras.

Gold Ben looked at Elder Zehn and sneered, “Starting this day, the Thunder Clan would no longer exist!”

Elder Zhen looked at Gold Ben and coldly said, “Supreme Elder of the Taurus Clan, Hahaha. Even if the Thunder Clan ends today, the Taurus Clan still perished first. What are you being proud about?”

Elder Zhen’s words hit Gold Ben’s most sensitive spot. Gold Ben clenched his teeth and said, “Enough wasting words. I will personally kill you today!”

A strange smile suddenly appeared on Elder Zhen’s face as he said, “Then try it.” After that, he turned to his troops and said, “Thunder Net formation!”

These soldiers were already waiting for this order since the very beginning. So without any hesitation, they took their totem sticks and went into a formation. After that, they all exerted their strengths into the totem sticks.

As they poured their strength into their sticks, the totem sticks began to shine. Then every Thunder Clan soldier closed their eyes as they held their totem sticks. All of them were motionless, including Elder Zhen.

What made it strange for Gold Ben and the others was the fact that these 100 thousand people only organized themselves into a formation and did nothing else. Aside from their shining totem sticks, there was no other reaction.

Gold Ben and the others looked puzzled at Elder Zhen’s group. They didn’t know what these people wanted to do.

Elder Star looked at Elder Zhen and said, “Enough playing tricks. I don’t believe that you have the ability to resist us.”

After saying that, Elder Star took out his Star Disk. The disk immediately shone with white light as it shot towards Elder Zhen. This light had no exact shape, but it looked like the energy beams of Zhao Hai’s magic cannons.

When this energy beam reached near Elder Zhen and the others, an electric glow suddenly appeared on the Thunder Clan’s formation. An electric strike met the white glow before Elder Star’s attacked vanished entirely.

After seeing this situation, Elder Star couldn’t help but stare for a moment. He didn’t hold back, that was his full strike. However, this attack was actually rendered useless. It was no wonder that Elder Star was surprised.

Elder Star’s ultimate weapon was the best among the ultimate weapons. One shouldn’t underestimate that white light. Actually that attack was no different to the two fists that Gold Ben used to destroy the defensive wall. Such an attack was enough to eradicate a Thunder Clan troop. However, it was actually useless against Elder Zhen and the others.

Gold Ben and the others were naturally aware that Elder Star wasn’t holding back. The Central Continent had just been cleaned up by Zhao Hai. Holding back for Elder Star was basically impossible. Elder Star’s attack being blocked was out of their expectations.

Gold Ben said, “So you have your methods. Let’s see if you can block this.” Then he immediately put on his Taurus combat suit and continually rained fists towards Elder Zhen’s group. As the first attack reached Elder Zhen, their formation immediately emitted an electric flow, blocking each attack.

Gold Ben released nearly a hundred attacks, but he still wasn’t able to break through. This caused Gold Ben’s expression to change. Elder Star and the others’ expression expression changed as well. All of them were clear about Gold Ben’s strength. Receiving 100 attacks from him would surely hurt.

In the past, these 100 hits was enough to kill tens of thousands of Thunder Clan members. However, these attacks were actually useless, the other side didn’t even budge.

As soon as they saw this, Elder Star and the others’ expression turned very heavy. Elder Star released another attack using his Star Disk. But the result was the same as Gold Ben. An electric strike just made the white light disappear.

When Jie Yu saw this, his expression sank. He didn’t know how the Thunder Clan managed to do this.

After Elder Star launched about a hundred attacks, he stopped. After all, they were already in the Thunder Clan, and Zhao Hai could come back at any time. Moreover, the Thunder Clan could also counter attack. It wouldn’t be a great idea for him to waste energy. He still needed to save some strength to protect himself.

When Jie Yu saw Elder Star stop, he immediately took a step forward. But this time, he didn’t attack Elder Zhen’s group. Instead, he waved his hand, equipping his ultimate weapon, and then attacking the mountain valley instead. However, Elder Zhen’s formations still sent forth electric strikes in order to negate the attack.

Jie Yu slightly knit his eyebrows. Then he flew forwards and before long he was about 100 meters away from Elder Zhen. However, Elder Zhen’s formation had yet to make a response.

Jie Yu couldn’t help but smile. Then he got closer and closer to the formation. 50 meters, 30 meters, 20 meters, but Elder Zhen and the others still didn’t respond.

However, when Jie Yu was about ten meters away from Elder Zhen, the formation quickly lit up and sent a strike towards Jie Yu. The electric strike arrived too quickly. Before Jie Yu could defend, the attack already struck his body.

Fortunately, Jie Yu had his Cancer combat armor on. The combat suit’s defensive capability was very good. When Jie Yu felt his chest being caved in, he immediately retreated and didn’t dare to go forward anymore.

The reason Jie Yu retreated was because he only wanted to find a way to bypass the formation in order to attack the mountain valley. But now it seems like it was impossible.

Elder Star turned his head towards the others and said, “It seems like their formation is primarily used for defense. Everyone take turns to attack. I don’t believe that we can’t break through. When the Thunder Clan is eliminated, we’ll proceed towards the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus.”

The group nodded before they took turns attacking. But amidst all the attacks, Elder Zhen and the others were still standing there, nobody made any moves.

A day passed by, but Elder Star and the others still didn’t have any progress. They continued to take turns to attack the Thunder Clan’s formation. However, they were still standing there, unmoving.

Two days went by, the Supreme Elders bagan to worry. However, Elder Zhen and the others were still standing there. They looked like dead people, just stood there without any reactions whatsoever.

On the third day, Elder Star and the others had forgotten to worry. At this point, the thing inside their minds was to break through this formation and see what the Thunder Clan did in order to block attacks for such a long time.

Fourth day, Elder Star and the others already had blood red eyes as they looked at Elder Zhen and the others. The Thunder Clan’s defenders were still unaffected. At this point, the Supreme Elders couldn’t wait to extinguish all of the Thunder Clan.

In the evening of the fourth day, white lights poured down on Elder Zhen’s formation. An electric strike proceeded to cancel everything out. But then, Elder Zhen and the others’ totem stick began to darken. The radiance began to disappear bit by bit.

Chapter 932: Cursing Before Death!

When Elder Star and the others saw this situation, they couldn’t help but feel ecstatic. However, they didn’t lower their guard. They were afraid that Elder Zhen was just playing with them.

However, their worries quickly vanished. After the light on Elder Zhen’s totem stick vanished, Elder Zhen’s body began to flake into ashes. When the wind passed by, Elder Zhen and the others’ body slowly scattered before totally vanishing.

Upon seeing this result, Elder Star and the other immediately understood. The opposite party certainly used a self-sacrificing method. Because of this, they were able to block the attacks for four days straight. To be honest, matching the Supreme Elders for this long was worthy of respect.

Originally, Elder Zhen and the others used the sacrifice ritual in order to buy Fei’er and the others ten days of time. However, after being attacked continuously for four days, and by Supreme Elders at that, they weren’t able to hold on anymore. The constant attacks completely depleted their energy.

Elder Star looked at where Elder Zhen and the others were. He couldn’t help but feel a trace of fear. If the entire Thunder Clan went all out, then it might be impossible for the Supreme Elders to stand where they were. They would surely be dragged on while Zhao Hai was attacking the entire Divine Race territory.

After thinking about this, Elder Star and the others couldn’t help but turn to where Elder Zhen and the others vanished and then gave a short bow. But although Elder Zhen and his troop became respected foes, war was war, Elder Star and the others couldn’t just let the Thunder Clan go. Therefore, they immediately rushed towards the mountain valley.

Elder Star took his Star Disk out and launched several attacks towards the valley. Rumbles were heard as the mist on the valley disappeared. However, Elder Star and the others were left stunned. Nobody was inside the valley.

Elder Star and the others slowly approached the place. There were traces of people inside the valley. The traces revealed that everybody was heading in, nobody was going out. The disappearance of the people in this valley had become a total mystery.

When Elder Star saw this situation, his expression couldn’t help but change. He took a glance at the surrounding before he said, “Go take a careful look around. There has to be clues. It’s impossible for the Thunder Clan to just disappear into nothing.”

Gold Ben and the others nodded before they examined the entire place. They had fought many battles, so they were very experienced with analyzing terrain.

After the group looked throughout the valley, they immediately found something suspicious. There were truly a lot of people inside this valley. What made Gold Ben and the others surprised was that all of the footprints lead to a certain place. They led to the innermost part of the valley, a place where there was a large piece of mountain wall.

The group stood in front of the mountain wall. They saw that the footprints were headed here before they just cut off.

The Supreme Elders inspected the wall but they couldn’t see anything special with it. This confused them.

Gold Ben went forward and touched the wall. It was cold and made of stone. Besides that, nothing else could be seen.

Gold Ben proceeded to punch the wall. A banging sound reverberated inside the valley as a ten meter hole appeared. However, no new clues were found, it was still a mountain wall.

Gold Ben returned to Elder Star’s side. His face was was ugly as he looked at the mountain wall and said, “What is happening? Did the Thunder Clan just stepped into this wall and vanished?”

Upon hearing Gold Ben, Jie Yu’s face quickly changed before he exclaimed, “Not good! Zhao Hai has a Spatial Divergent Ability! It’s possible that Zhao Hai used this valley in order to move the Thunder Clan.” When Elder Star and the others heard this, their expressions turned ugly as well. Elder Star replied, “It’s possible. Let’s quickly leave this place. Gold Ben, between the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus, which one is closer?”

Gold Ben replied “We’re closer to the Winged Pegasus. Let’s go now. We can reach the Winged Pegasus in five days. We’re short on time, we need to attack them immediately.”

Elder Star and the others nodded. After receiving news that the Cancer Continent had been eliminated, Gold Ben and the others knew that they didn’t have the opportunity to slack. If they couldn’t compel Zhao Hai to return, then that would be the end of the Divine Race.

They never expected this outcome when they came up with this plan. But now, it was already too late to feel regret.

After the group reached a decision, they immediately took off and soared towards the Winged Pegasus. Meanwhile, at this time, Fei’er was inside the Space along with Ding and Shan.

Fei’er’s eyes were blood red. He hadn’t slept in the past few days. He was finally able to settle his clan. But after looking at his people, Fei’er’s happiness took a big blow. Although there were already several million Thunder Clan members inside the Space, this was just about a thirtieth(1/30) of the original Thunder Clan population. In other words, only 1 out of 30 Thunder Clan members survived.

Ding and Shan were also aware of Fei’er’s situation. Their moods were also very heavy. Thunder Clan suffered today, and their clan might be the same tomorrow. If their clans didn’t move towards the Space soon, then their situation would become much worse compared to the Thunder Clan.

Ding looked at Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, what are you planning to do now? Do you think mister will come back and help us?”

Fei’er smiled bitterly and said, “How can we just ask Mister to come back? Mister is very strong, but the nine Supreme Elders are ready to go all out. If mister loses, then not only us, the vassal races and the foreign races would be finished.”

Ding didn’t answer. He also knew that Fei’er was telling the truth. But in this case, they don’t have any other plan.

Shan couldn’t find a way either. Fei’er looked at the two and said, “We can only do one thing. I will go with you to see your clans. We need to persuade them. They need to enter the Space immediately. The pressure on Mister right now is too great. You should know about Mister’s temperament. If Mister has the means then it would be impossible for him to withhold it from us.”

Ding and Shan nodded. They fully trust Zhao Hai. They believed that Zhao Hai has a reason for not coming back.

Fei’er looked at the two before turning his head to Shan and said, “Shan, me and Ding will go with you to convince your Patriarch. I hope that we can convince him to move to the Space. If he agrees then we’ll immediately see the Barbarians. The Winged Pegasus are closer to the Thunder Clan. If the Supreme Elders wanted to deal with us, then their next target would be you.”

Ding and Shan nodded. At this moment, this was the best move for them. Moreover, they also thought that Fei’er was correct. The Thunder Clan can be described as eliminated at this point. At this time,  the Supreme Elders would certainly attack the Winged Pegasus or the Barbarians next. However, the Winged Pegasus’ plane was nearer to the Thunder Clan compared to the Barbarians. Naturally, the Supreme Elders would go and deal with the Winged Pegasus first.

After deciding on their action, the three immediately left the Space and appeared inside Shan’s room in the Winged Pegasus Clan. Upon returning, Shan immediately led the two to see the Patriarch in the Assembly Hall.

In the past few days, the Patriarch of the Winged Pegasus has also been receiving information from the Thunder Clan. When they were dealing with the Divines with Zhao Hai, they were using the messenger fishes to communicate. Because of this, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch was aware of what was happening with the Thunder Clan.

During those days, every information regarding the Thunder Clan made the Winged Pegasus Patriarch more and more disappointed. Even after the Thunder Clan was eliminated, Zhao Hai still didn’t appear. In the end, even at the death of the Thunder Clan Patriarch, he was cursing Zhao Hai.

The situation with the Winged Pegasus Clan wasn’t very good lately. After knowing about the fate of the Thunder Clan, the Winged Pegasus Clan soon became flustered. It was getting harder and harder to control the situation.

Because of this, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch felt more and more stressed. He didn’t want to enter the Space. He was already fond of having full power of his people. He didn’t want to give that up.

But if he didn’t give it up, then their result would be the same as the Thunder Clan. If they were eliminated by the Supreme Elders, then what would be the use of his power?

Upon hearing the Thunder Clan Patriarch curse Zhao Hai even at his death, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch became set on never entering Zhao Hai’s Space.

At this time, a report came from the hall entrance. Shan, Ding, and Fei’er were asking for an audience. Upon hearing the names of these three people, the Patriarch couldn’t help but knit his brows. He knew that these people had followed Zhao Hai for a long time. Moreover, they were adamant on entering the Space. To be honest, the Patriarch didn’t like them.

However, these three people were the ones who spearheaded the attack on the Taurus Divines. Their prestige was very high among the three clans. This was especially true for the young people. Because of this, the Patriarch needs to consider his attitude when meeting them.

After thinking for a moment, the Patriarch finally said, “Let them in.” The servant complied before turning around to leave. Before long, Shan and the others came in and gave a salute to the Patriarch.

The Patriarch looked at Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, your family has been met with a terrible catastrophe. Why are you here? You should be with your people.”

When he heard these words from the Patriarch, Fei’er couldn’t help but knit his brows. He discovered that convincing the Winged Pegasus Patriarch would be a very hard thing to do. It seems like the Patriarch didn’t have a good impression of him.

Chapter 933: Order For Arrest!

Although he had discovered this, Fei’er still answered, “Patriarch, the environment inside Mister Zhao Hai’s Space is very good. My clansmen are living very well. I visited the Winged Pegasus Clan in order to persuade the Patriarch. Please don’t go the same road as the Thunder Clan.”

The Patriarch looked at Fei’er and coldly snorted, “Living very well, is it? So you think that living inside that place is very good? At the point of your Patriarch’s death, he told me that the crisis of the three clans was artificially created by Zhao Hai. When he attacked the Divines, we even offered him some help. But when the Divines attacked us, he didn’t come to our rescue. You might be willing to go under that kind of person, but I couldn’t.”

Fei’er looked at the Patriarch and sneered, “The Patriarch is really good at making jokes. Because of his greed for power, the Thunder Clan Patriarch buried our people along with him. Such a person is not worthy for the Thunder Clan. The Great Elder even tried to persuade him, but he didn’t listen. He still intended to hold on to his little power until the moment he died. He couldn’t blame anybody for his decisions.”

Fei’er continued, “Patriarch, do you really think that you can deal with nine Supreme Elders? Those people won’t accept surrender, they never left anybody alive. They’re here to eliminate the three clans.”

The Patriarch’s expression turned ugly, but Fei’er didn’t stop, “Patriarch said that we helped Mister Zhao Hai in the battle against the Taurus Divines. But I want to ask the Patriarch this, do you really think that Mister Zhao Hai couldn’t deal with the Taurus Divines without our help?”

When Fei’er said this, the Patriarch couldn’t reply. He knew that the three clans only sent their troops in order to have an equal standing with Zhao Hai. But even if they didn’t send their troops, Zhao Hai was still able to defeat the Taurus Divines.

Fei’er went on, “Patriarch might not see Mister Zhao Hai’s help, but Mister is currently helping us avenge ourselves. Mister didn’t come here because he is currently dealing with the Divine Race territory. He wanted to cause pressure to the Supreme Elders. He even gave us three tokens so that our people could enter his Space. Isn’t this enough of a help? I ask Patriarch to think about it carefully.”

The Patriarch’s expression was uglier than ever. After Fei’er finished talking, he slapped his table hard and said, “Quite a sharp mouth! Do you think exaggerating everything would make me move to the Space? You Thunder Clan are low in population, that’s why you cannot deal with the Supreme Elders. But with my well-trained and well-equipped Winged Pegasus Army, I can definitely go all out against the Divine Race!”

Fei’er, Ding, and Shan’s expression changed. They looked at the Winged Pegasus Patriarch as though he was an idiot. They couldn’t believe what the Patriarch said. Does he actually plan to drive the Winged Pegasus into extinction?

Right, the Thunder Clan had the least population among the three clans. However, the Thunder Clan’s abilities were the strongest among the three. Even if there were more Barbarians and Winged Pegasus soldiers, they still wouldn’t be able to easily deal with a Thunder Clan army. What the Winged Pegasus Patriarch was talking about was completely nonsense.

Fei’er looked at the Patriarch, “Since the Patriarch says so, then we won’t persuade you any further. This matter is your clan’s, this Fei’er cannot just interfere. I have already said my piece, since the Patriarch won’t listen, then this Fei’er will have to say goodbye.”

When he heard Fei’er, the Patriarch couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t think that Fei’er would just walk away. But then he suddenly remembered something. When Fei’er fell out with the Thunder Clan Patriarch, a rebellion was started, causing the Thunder Clan to be unstable. This made the Thunder Clan unable to deal with the Supreme Elders. Now that Fei’er wanted to leave, would he start another revolt?

When he thought of this, the Patriarch’s expression immediately changed. All of a sudden, he loudly exclaimed, “Where do you think this is? Do you think you can just come here and leave whenever you want? Since you came here, then you might as well stay. Men, take them!”

Fei’er and the others couldn’t help but stare. They never expected the Patriarch to do this. After Fei’er left, he initially wanted to have Shan talk to the Patriarch instead. Who would’ve thought that the Patriarch would want to seize them?

Fei’er looked at the Patriarch and saw that the Patriarch’s eyes were blood red. He looked insane. At this time, the sound of footsteps can be heard outside. The Winged Pegasus guards have arrived.

Fei’er looked at Shan before grabbed his command token. A spatial rift appeared, taking the three people in and then vanished. It looks like they weren’t here at all.

However, the Patriarch just sat there, the look of defeat on his face. He knew that he was in trouble now. Shan was held in high regard among the youths of their clan. If Shan decides to act, then the trouble would be big.

The Patriarch immediately commanded his subordinates, his face flushed as he said, “Quick, immediately send this news. Shan brought the Thunder Clan’s Fei’er and the Barbarian Clan’s Ding to assassinate me. Immediately order their arrest!”

When his subordinates heard this, they couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Shan’s position in the Clan was very high, this was the same for Fei’er and Ding. Why would they come here to assassinate the Patriarch? Was that even possible?

After seeing that his men were unresponsive, the Patriarch roared, “Why are you just standing there? Immediately pass my order!”

The Pegasus guards looked at each other in dismay. They didn’t dare violate the order of their Patriarch, so they turned around to fulfill their duties.

Meanwhile, Shan and the others reappeared from the Space. The place where they were in right now was inside Council Speaker Fang’s room.

Shan knew that he had already offended the Patriarch. Needless to say, he still needed to convince his people to move.

Shan and the others were smart people, they knew that the Patriarch couldn’t kill them. Because of this, they left the assembly hall to meet with Council Speaker Fang.

Council Speaker Fang wasn’t having a great time lately. To be honest, he really wanted the Winged Pegasus to enter the Space. After all, he had met Zhao Hai and saw how Zhao Hai treated the Demons. Speaker Fang believed that after entering the Space, Zhao Hai definitely wouldn’t treat them unfairly.

The Patriarch’s firm disagreement made Speaker Fang feel awkward. Although the Council Speaker still held a great amount of authority, it still couldn’t contend with the Patriarch. Moreover, the reason why the Patriarch’s words held great control was because of the Council members.

If only those Council members supported him, then Council Speaker Fang would’ve been able to confront the Patriarch. However, the Patriarch was a wise man and his hunger for control was much greater compared to the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch. Because of this, he began to pull the Council Members to his side. In the past, the Patriarch sent Council Speaker Fang to Zhao Hai in hopes that the speaker would be killed off by the Divines. And even if the Council Speaker survived, with his absence, the Patriarch could recruit more council members.

So when Speaker Fang returned to the clan, he suddenly discovered that a lot of council members began to ignore his words. This caused Speaker Fang to turn passive, his authority was greatly reduced. As time went by, the Winged Pegasus Clan began to move towards a dictatorship.

When Zhao Hai sent word, Shan immediately approached Speaker Fang so that he could relay the information to the Patriarch. The plan was to evacuate the Winged Pegasus Plan to the Space. However, the Patriarch didn’t agree. The council discussed this matter several times. But since the council was already under the Patriarch’s control, the result of the discussion always ended on bad terms.

Speaker Shan’s hair almost turned white from worrying about this matter. But he had yet to find a solution.

At this time, a servant suddenly gave a report. Shen, Fei’er, and Ding were asking for an urgent audience. When Speaker Fang heard this, he immediately said, “Invite them in, quick.” The servant ran and before long Shan and the others walked in.

Speaker Fang looked at the three and said, “Shan, Fei’er, Ding, why did you come here?”

Shan looked at Speaker Fang and sobbed, “Uncle Fang, you have to help us. We just went to see the Patriarch and……” What followed was an explanation about what happened inside the Assembly Hall.

When Speaker Fang heard this, his expression drastically changed. He slammed his table with force and angrily said, “Did the Patriarch go mad? He’s going to lead the clan into ruin.”

Just as he said that, a servant came with another report. The servant voice was heard from outside the door, “Old Master, not good. There are a lot of troops outside. They said that they wanted to catch the Young Master. They said that the Young Masters Shan, Fei’er, and Ding attempted to assassinate the Patriarch. At this time, the whole clan is looking for them.”

Speaker Fang stared, his face turned even uglier as he said, “Absurd! Really absurd! Who would believe that? He’s gone blind, crazy. He’s gone insane!”

Shan didn’t expect the Patriarch to really order for their arrest. Shan turned to Speaker Fang and said, “Uncle, this, we’ll enter Mister’s Space. The Patriarch wouldn’t be able to get us there. I want to ask the Speaker to bring the clan into the Space no matter what. Find those who are willing. Send word to my room every midnight, I will be there. When the time comes, I will open a spatial rift, what do you think?”

When Speaker Fang heard this, he understood what Shan wanted to do. He thought for a bit before he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s do that. Remember to wait inside your room every midnight.”

Shan nodded. Then Fei’er used the command token before the group entered the Space. After seeing this, Speaker Fang felt relieved.

After Fei’er and the others entered the Space, the three of them couldn’t help but look at each other in dismay. They didn’t know what to say for some time. A few moments later, Shan sighed and said, “It looks like our clan wouldn’t fare smoothly. Fei’er, why do you think the Patriarch turned into that? It wasn’t like this when the Divines are still in control.

Fei’er sighed, he didn’t know the answer either. He hadn’t had the taste of authority. Moreover, he was taught from an early age that he must serve the Thunder Clan. Upon seeing the Patriarchs turning into that, he couldn’t help but feel disappointed.

Shan looked at the two and smiled bitterly. Their Patriarch had caused this, he felt like he had shamed the whole clan.

Fei’er looked at the two and forced a smile, “Alright, let’s go to the Barbarians next. No matter what, we cannot give up. This matter is related to the life and death of the three clans.”

As soon as they heard Fei’er, the two nodded. This matter truly involves the survival of the three clans. They needed to grasp every little opportunity they could see.

However, the three prepared themselves to get the same treatment from the Barbarian Patriarch. Ding sighed for a moment before he used his command token and appeared back inside his room.

Just as the three appeared, they couldn’t help but freeze. This was because there were Barbarians in and around Ding’s room.

The trio stared for a moment before their expression changed. They suddenly thought that the Barbarian Patriarch might have come to capture them. Luckily, Ding still had the command token in his had. In the worst case, he could use the command token to run away. Because of this, Ding looked at the Patriarch and said, “Patriarch, what is this?”

The Barbarian Patriarch looked at Ding and said, “You came out, fantastic. Ding, I just heard from the Winged Pegasus Patriarch. He said that you tried to assassinate him, what is that about?”

Ding looked at his Patriarch’s expression and couldn’t help but turn blank. They thought that the Patriarch would capture them immediately. But that doesn’t seem to be the case. Ding looked at the Patriarch and said, “Patriarch, did the Winged Pegasus Patriarch talk to you?”

The Barbarian Patriarch nodded and said, “He said that you three tried to kill him. He is currently ordering for your capture. Did the three of you really try to assassinate him?”

Ding smiled bitterly and said, “How could that be possible. Patriarch, we asked for the Winged Pegasus Patriarch’s audience in order to persuade him to send the Winged Pegasus Clan to the Space. But he didn’t just disagree, he even tried to capture us. Fortunately, mister gave command tokens to the three of us, allowing us to escape to the Space. I didn’t expect you to get word about this immediately. Patriarch, do you want to catch us and turn us in?”

Chapter 934: Attitude Decides Destiny

The Barbarian Patriarch looked at Ding, Shan, and Fei’er. He could clearly see the wary expression on their eyes. A good indication for this was the fact that Fei’er and Shan hadn’t opened their mouths after appearing in this room.

The Patriarch couldn’t help but smile bitterly. He was clearly aware why these three would have such an expression. Both the Thunder Clan and Winged Pegasus Patriarchs had treated them wrongly. It would be strange if they weren’t careful this time.

The Barbarian Patriarch gently shook his head and then forced a smile. He said, “Ding, I admit that I was wrong before. I shouldn’t have been selfish and disagreed to moving towards Mister Zhao Hai’s Space. But after knowing about what happened to the Thunder Clan, I decided to agree to the Barbarian Clan’s migration. That’s the reason why I’m here.”

Upon hearing the Patriarch, Ding couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t expect the Patriarch to say those words. In the past, the Patriarch strongly disagreed to enter the Space. Who would’ve thought that the Barbarian Patriarch would be different compared to the Winged Pegasus Patriarch. Instead of strengthening his resolve to disagree, he actually decided to change his mind.

Similar event, but the Barbarian Patriarch and the Winged Pegasus Patriarch reached a different conclusion. Perhaps this had something to do with their character.

The Winged Pegasus were quite intelligent people. One could see this from their method of governance. Both the Thunder Clan and the Barbarians had set up an Elder’s Assembly. This congregation was headed by the Great Elder. The status of the Great Elder was quite high. Even if he had no elders supporting him, the Great Elder could still hinder the actions of the Patriarch

On the other hand, the Winged Pegasus had their council headed by the Council Speaker. Although the Speaker had the authority to limit the Patriarch, he still needed the support of the council members. When talking about distribution of authority, the Winged Pegasus had it thinner compared to the Barbarians and the Thunder Clan.

However, the more intelligent one was, the more power one would desire. Because of this, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch has been blinded by his ambition. He would do his best just to cling on to his power and influence.

Meanwhile, the Barbarian Patriarch was different. He wasn’t as smart as the Winged Pegasus Patriarch. It can be said that the Barbarian Patriarch’s character was blunt and honest. Because of this, he was quickly awakened from the illusion of power and prestige. What precisely woke him up were the curses of the Thunder Clan Patriarch towards Zhao Hai.

What Fei’er’s group didn’t know was the fact that the Thunder Clan Patriarch completely believed that he had all the cards in his hands. And when the nine Supreme Elders began to attack his city, the Thunder Clan Patriarch still wasn’t ashamed of what he’d done. Instead, he thought that their current suffering was entirely Zhao Hai’s fault!

The Thunder Clan Patriarch believed that the Thunder Clan was essential during Zhao Hai’s battle against the Taurus Divines. He thought that Zhao Hai owed them a lot because of the losses that the Thunder Clan had suffered. He was truly convinced, up until the end, that Zhao Hai had been unfair to the Thunder Clan.

The Patriarch thought that it was Zhao Hai’s unforgiving character that pushed the Supreme Elders to show no mercy to the Thunder Clan.

When the nine Supreme Elders attacked the Thunder Clan, Zhao Hai should’ve been there to provide help. But since Zhao Hai was absent, the Thunder Clan Patriarch was compelled to fight. He didn’t regret or even think about his decisions prior to the event. He fully believed that he didn’t do anything wrong; everything was Zhao Hai’s fault. Because of this, the Thunder Patriarch maniacally cursed Zhao Hai in the messenger fish. He kept sending messages to the Winged Pegasus and the Barbarians about this sentiment.

It must be said that the ravings of the Thunder Clan Patriarch had bore some fruits. At the very least, the Winged Pegasus Patriarch was affected. The Winged Pegasus Patriarch hadn’t thought about this before. He thought that they had cooperated with Zhao Hai in order to gain benefits in dealing with the Divines. Moreover, Zhao Hai went to attack the Divine territories in order to block the revenge of the Divines, allowing the three clans to live in peace.

But now, Zhao Hai’s action actually caused the three clans to be in mortal peril. In the minds of the Thunder Clan Patriarch and the Winged Pegasus Patriarch, Zhao Hai owed them while they don’t owe anything to Zhao Hai.

Because of this thought, both the Winged Pegasus and the Thunder Clan Patriarchs would resort to drastic measures just to not enter Zhao Hai’s Space. In their opinion, it was Zhao Hai’s duty to come back and help them. If Zhao Hai didn’t come, then he was ungrateful. At this point, entering the Space and being under Zhao Hai’s umbrella was something they couldn’t accept.

In this case, the Thunder Clan and the Winged Pegasus Patriarch chose to not enter the Space. This idea went to the point of obsession. And because of this obsession, they had turned deaf and blind to the approaching disaster.

On the other hand, the Barbarian Patriarch was different. The Barbarians are simple and honest people. They knew how to repay gratitude as well as avenge enmity. Their distinction between right and wrong was very clear. Moreover, their opinions couldn’t be influenced by anyone.

The curses of the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch was also heard by the Barbarian Patriarch. However, the only thing he heard was the Thunder Clan’s Patriarch not having proper conscience. In the very beginning, even if they wanted to deal with the Taurus Divines, they still didn’t have the opportunity to do so, they were still unprepared.

When Zhao Hai from the Ark Continent came in, he made the Divines suffer hard. Because of this opportunity, the three clans should be thankful to him.

And during the fight against the Taurus Divines, it was the three clans who willingly sent troops over, Zhao Hai didn’t ask them to provide help. And since the three clans and Zhao Hai had a common grudge against the Taurus Divines, the cooperation was just an equal exchange. There shouldn’t be any talks about gratefulness to anybody. Zhao Hai needed to owe the three clans? Where did that come from?

To say that Zhao Hai was having a hard time with the Divines, was that really true? The three clans were aware of the Divine Race’s strength. They had been preparing for a rebellion for many years, so they had made some investigations themselves. During the Battle, the Taurus Supreme Elder even came to reinforce the Taurus Divines. But in the end, he was driven away by Zhao Hai. With no Supreme Elder supporting them, the Taurus Divines further dell into a critical situation.

And even if Zhao Hai hadn’t come back to rescue them, Zhao Hai destroyed the Central, Scorpio, and Cancer Continents in the meantime. The destruction of these three continents would surely put an immense pressure on the Supreme Elders. The longer they stay in the Taurus Continent, the more troubled their minds would be.

If Zhao Hai returned to the Taurus Continent in order to fight the nine Supreme Elders, then he would plunge himself into a very hard fight. The odds of him winning should be very small. And if Zhao Hai was defeated, then the three clans would completely vanish off the map.

Instead of saying that Zhao Hai didn’t help them, Zhao Hai had give them the opportunity to escape to his Space. As long as they enter, then they would be safe from harm. This was equal to extending the lifespan of the three clans. If they don’t go through this process, then they would subject themselves to a very dark future.

If you were asking for death, then why would Zhao Hai rescue you? How much friendship did the two of you have? Is it to the point of self-sacrifice?

Because of these thoughts, the Barbarian Patriarch finally decided to allow the Barbarians to move to the Space. In this case, the person’s character decided their destiny. Just a small but crucial aspect managed to sway the path for the Barbarian Clan.

Ding stared blankly at the Patriarch. In the past, he was completely against moving to the Space. But now it seems like the Patriarch had made a sudden full turn.  This caused Ding to feel awkward, he looked confused at the Patriarch. He still wasn’t sure if the Patriarch was speaking the truth or not.

The Patriarch looked at Ding and smiled bitterly. “Alright, there’s no need to doubt me. I’ve already informed our clansmen to prepare their belongings for migration. Most of our people have already prepared their things. We’ve been waiting for you to open a spatial rift. We don’t want to be here when the Supreme Elders arrive.”

When he heard the Patriarch, a smile immediately bloomed on Ding’s face. His entire person seemed to glow with happiness. He immediately complied and began to prepare.

The Patriarch looked at Fei’er and Shan. Then he patted Fei’er’s shoulder and said, “Fei’er, don’t sulk. It’s already good that you managed to survive. Moreover, you still have some of your family that managed to escape. You need to look after your people well. If you experience some problems later on, you can come and see me. I’ll do what I can to help.”

A tear couldn’t help but drop from Fei’er’s eyes as he nodded and said, “Thanks, Patriarch, I will remember it.”

The Barbarian Patriarch sighed. Then he turned to Shan and said, “After taking care of things here, I will personally try to persuade the Winged Pegasus Patriarch. I hope he’ll understand if I’m the one to tell him.”

Shan just gave a small smile and a nod. He didn’t say anything. Upon seeing this, the Patriarch sighed once more before he turned around and left.

Looking at the Barbarian Patriarch’s departing back, Fei’er and Shan couldn’t help but feel bitter. They really hoped that their Patriarchs would be the same. If that was the case, then more of their clansmen would have been saved.

Fei’er turned his head to Shan who also returned the gaze, then the two of them smiled bitterly before heading out as well. Although they were envious of Ding, he was still their brother for life. At this time, they would naturally help him take care of things.

Fei’er and Shan didn’t say anything else and just helped the Barbarians. They already had experience in settling their people. So with their management, the Barbarians were able to move smoothly.

More and more Barbarians entered the Space. When night came, Ding’s management was no longer needed. With a migration as huge as this, the Barbarians naturally had departments made in order to replace Ding and the others. They were even doing a better job in organizing the population.

Chapter 935: Fight for People We Can Fight For

Zhao Hai was aware of the matters of the three clans. Giving Fei’er the command tokens wasn’t for nothing. Moreover, Cai’er can take over control over the Space to help Fei’er and the others. And she was also better at spying at the three clans.

To be honest, upon seeing how the Winged Pegasus Patriarch was adamant on not entering the Space, Zhao Hai solidified his intention of not helping them. The Winged Pegasus Clan needs to strive for survival.

On the other hand, the response of the Barbarian Patriarch came unexpected. Zhao Hai didn’t think that the Patriarch would arrive at his decision this quickly. This truly shocked Zhao Hai.

If the Supreme Elders suddenly changes their target to the Barbarians, then Zhao Hai would not mind helping them. After all, with such an honest race, Zhao Hai couldn’t just be unfair to them.

However, since the nine Supreme Elders went to attack the Winged Pegasus Clan, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t come and help. At this time he was currently dealing with the Sagittarius Clan.

But at this moment, Cai’er came to Zhao Hai with new information. The O’Neal Family’s Army just arrived outside the Spatial Rift to the Divine Realm. They were now prepared to launch a large attack on the spatial rift’s defensive line.

After hearing this, Zhao Hai gawked. At this point, time was very important for Zhao Hai. He was still doing battle in the Divine Race territory. The Divines were too populous. If he wanted to deal with them all, then he would need quite some time. In this case, he wouldn’t be able to muster up some strength to deal with the O’Neal family.

Zhao Hai made some calculations. He had already destroyed the Taurus, Central, Scorpio, and Cancer Continents. And in the meantime, he was battling the Sagittarius Divines. As long as he managed to deal with the Sagittarius Divines, then he might free up some military strength. However, this military strength wouldn’t be able to cope with the O’Neal family’s army.

All this time, the O’Neal Family had amassed more than twenty thousand magic armors. This number shouldn’t be underestimated. It would take Zhao Hai about 2 million undead in order to block them.

Besides the magic armors, the O’Neal family also has about 5000 War Tanks accompanying the army. At the same time, energy cannons were also brought over.

The strength of these energy cannons surpasses those on the War Tanks. From Zhao Hai’s estimate, he would need about ten million undead to block the O’Neal Family’s army. Moreover, he would also need to use the defensive line effectively in order to succeed.

This didn’t mean that Zhao Hai didn’t have confidence in his own Undead. In fact, his undead has been increasing every since he began attacking the Divines. Moreover, the overall quality of the undead have also been improving. At this point, all of the undead that Zhao Hai used in his battles were God-rank. And the number of undead had reached an astonishing four hundred million.

However, Zhao Hai still wouldn’t dare to underestimate the O’Neal Family. The route of civilization that the O’Neal Family took was different. The O’Neal family took the technological path while Zhao Hai and the others took the path to unlocking the human potential.

One couldn’t precisely say which of the two paths was better. But in terms of manpower, the O’neal family was in the lead. They had hot weapons. And with the addition of magic formations, their weapons were much better compared to the magic cannons that Zhao Hai uses. In this case, Zhao Hai would have his undead fight the opposite party using their own bodies. This was akin to a fight between someone wielding a knife and someone who had a gatling gun.

Because of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown upon hearing Cai’er’s report. Although he had several hundred million troops, majority of them were used to deal with the Sagittarius Divines. The Sagittarius Divines were very hard to deal with. Their archers were very strong so Zhao Hai was unable to end the fight in a short time. In this case, Zhao Hai simply didn’t have the time to face the O’Neal family.

Laura and the others were beside Zhao Hai. They were also aware of Zhao Hai’s worries. The group frowned before Laura spoke after some time, “Brother Hai, should we take some troops in order to deal with the O’Neal family?”

Without even waiting for Zhao Hai to speak, Lizzy shook her head and said, “If we do that, then we would be stuck in the Sagittarius Continent for even longer. When the Supreme Elders are done with the Winged Pegasus, they will immediately know about the disappearance of the Barbarians. Then they will certainly return here to look for us. When the time comes, we would have lost the best opportunity to deal with the Divine Race. Our losses would be too great.”

Laura nodded, she was aware of this result. But aside from what she suggested, what other methods could they use? Laura couldn’t help but turn her head to Zhao Hai.

Seeing that everybody was looking at him, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Why would we block them? Just let them come. The Barbarians are already moving to the Space. Since the Winged Pegasus doesn’t want to enter, then there’s no need to waste time on them. What we do next is to fight for what we can fight for.”

When Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but gawk. Laura looked puzzled at Zhao Hai and asked, “Fight for what we can fight for? What does Brother Hai mean?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Foreign Races!”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others immediately understood what he meant. At this time, the three foreign races were stable. It can be said that there’s no need for them to worry. What Zhao Hai and the others needed to do right now was to finish off the Divine Race and then proceed to the next step. This was to have the foreign races enter the Space.

However, how could they make the foreign races enter the Space? This was a major problem. At this time, the foreign races were having the best moment of their lives. Zhao Hai was dealing with the Divines. The foreign races had already sent troops to battle. It can be said that with Zhao Hai’s existence, the foreign races had gained an upper hand against the Divine Race. Under such circumstances, why would the foreign races enter the Space?

So the only way for it to be possible was to introduce an even more powerful enemy!

Obviously, it can be seen that the O’Neal Family was extremely strong. The Divine Realm was much bigger compared to the Ark Continent, and was even bigger than the Demon Realm. If the O’Neal family discovers the Divine Realm, would they be willing to let go of it? The answer was no. They will never give it up. In this case, they will surely explore the Divine Realm. When they confront the foreign races, then the foreign races would surely suffer a loss. When that time comes, it wouldn’t be impossible for them to enter Zhao Hai’s Space.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to let the O’Neal family into the Divine Realm before, this was because the O’Neal family would be appearing in the Taurus Continent. When the time comes, the one who would face them first wouldn’t be the foreign races nor the Divines, it would be the Thunder Clan, Winged Pegasus, and the Barbarians.

But now, the situation was different. The Barbarians were migrating to the Space. Since they had made ample preparations, the move went smoothly. In a few days, their move would be complete.

As for Gold Ben and the others, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about them. They would enter the Winged Pegasus’ plane any time soon. Therefore, when the O’Neal family arrives in the Divine Realm, the Barbarians should have finished moving while the Winged Pegasus were entangled with the nine Supreme Elders. At that time, the Winged Pegasus should be on the cusp of extinction. In this case, the first ones to meet the O’Neal family would be the nine Supreme Elders.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to allow the O’neal family to enter the Divine Realm. The existence of the O’Neal family would make the Divine Realm’s situation even muddier. When the time comes, Zhao Hai would be able to catch fish in muddled waters.

Upon exposing his plan to Laura and the others, Zhao Hai quickly got their approval. They also thought that it was time for the O’Neal family to stir things up.

At this time, the O’Neal family had divided their troops into three. One against the Underworld, one to the Demon Realm, and the last one was to attack the defensive line. The latter being the one with the most manpower used so far.

If the O’Neal family discovers the large plane behind the spatial rift, would they still be interested with the Ark Continent? The Demon Realm? It’s highly probable that they would slowly shift their whole attention towards the Divine Realm. This wouldn’t only turn the Divine Realm’s waters muddier, this would also allow Zhao Hai to acquire more magic armors.

It was because of all these reasons that Laura and the others fully supported Zhao Hai’s plan. In their view, there wouldn’t be any harm done to Zhao Hai if the O’Neal family arrived in the Divine Realm.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled, “The O’Neal family is about to attack. We’ll call the undead creatures back for now. However, we can’t just make them have a good time. We’ll proceed to harass them constantly.”

When Laura heard this, she couldn’t help bit smile and said, “Good, we should harass them. This will inform them that the Ark Continent’s people aren’t useless. This would attract their attention even more.”

Lizzy nodded, “Moreover, we can buy more time. We can even use our ambushes to lure the O’Neal family over to the Supreme Elders. This way, we wouldn’t worry about them not meeting.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then it’s settled. I want to see how the O’Neal family deals with our harassment. Although their magic armors are fast, they still fall short compared to the Space. I’ll make the O’Neal family taste how terrifying our ambushes are.”

Megan smiled, “I also want to see how the nine Supreme Elders would react upon seeing the O’Neal family’s magic armors. In the past, when they discovered  the Goblins making magic armors, they immediately exterminated them. Compared to the Goblins, the O’Neal family’s magic armors are more advanced. The reaction of the Supreme Elders would certainly be worth watching.”

Chapter 936: A Thousand Troops Are Easy To Get, But Finding One Good Talent Is Difficult

Axe was calmly looking at the Spatial Rift. Compared to before, he was now more familiar with the world. Arriving at the Ark Continent made him understand a lot of things.

He was very clear about how much the Family had invested in the Ark Continent. If the family couldn’t recoup the cost, then the O’Neal family would greatly suffer.

What makes this situation funny was the fact that the O’Neal family’s greatest desire at this point was to see their enemies. Ever since they arrived at the Ark Continent, they had never seen a single person. Even if it was an enemy, they badly needed to see one.

Since the discovery of this spatial rift, the O’Neal family finally managed to calm down. At this moment George went to the side of Axe and said, “Junior Patriarch, we have tried attacking the other side several times. However, their counterattacks were very fierce. But at this time, we have a general observation of their troop positions.”

Axe turned his head to George and nodded, “Alright, good work. If we succeed, then the Clan will remember your great contribution.”

A glint flashed in George’s eyes, he quickly gave a salute and said, “I thank Junior Patriarch Axe!”

Axe nodded and said, “We’ve just arrived, so we’ll rest for two days before attacking. In those two days, draw me a map of the area. It’ll be useful for our operation.”

George nodded, “Young Patriarch, the map has been prepared. I will send it to you in a while.”

A glint of praise appeared on Axe’s eyes. He patted George’s shoulder and said, “Good job, George. You handle things very well.”

Upon hearing Axe’s praise, George’s body couldn’t help but feel light. He quickly replied, “Thank you, Junior Patriarch. I’m just doing things I’m meant to do.”

Axe nodded, “Alright, I’ll be waiting for the map. Go back and rest well.”

George nodded, “Then I’ll ask to be excused, Junior Patriarch. I’ll immediately have the map delivered.” Axe nodded before he turned to look at the War Tanks. Nobody knew what kind of thoughts were running in his mind.

Axe had been inside a War Tank for several days. They were hurrying along without stopping so he was very tired. Magic armor pilots weren’t strong themselves, so they get exhausted more easily.

But although he was very tired, he still wouldn’t dare to fall asleep. There were too many things running along Axe’s mind. His head has been processing them nonstop, there was no time for sleep.

In the end, Axe’s thoughts drifted to Zhao Hai. After thinking about how they met, Axe couldn’t help but feel stupid. Everytime Axe thought of Zhao Hai, he would always feel anger.

At that time, he thought that Zhao Hai was the fool. But as it turned out, it was Axe who had been played. Axe had an inkling that Zhao Hai was on the other side of this spatial rift, this feeling was very strong. Because of this, Axe heavily lobbied to be allowed to come here, even if his father didn’t agree.

While Axe was deep in thought, the War Tank suddenly stopped. The war tank driver turned to Axe and said, “Junior Patriarch, we’re here. You should go to your room and take a rest.”

Axe slowly opened his eyes and looked all around. Then he nodded and said, “You go rest as well.” Then he opened the door and left.

Just after Axe entered his room, his servant’s voice was suddenly heard outside. “Young Master, Mister George is seeking an audience. He said that he had brought the troop deployment of the spatial rift.”

Axe nodded, “Let him in.” Before long, George entered Axe’s room. In his hand was a map of the spatial rift’s defensive line.

Axe waved his hand to the servant and said, “Go prepare some food and drinks with me. George, stay here. Let’s eat while discussing the map.”

Although George was happy, he didn’t let it show outside. He just nodded and sat on the table as he unfolded the map.

It was a very detailed map. Terrains and landmarks were properly labelled. One could see George’s attentiveness from the map.

After looking at the map, Axe gave a favorable nod and said, “Very good. This map is very well made. Are you certain that this is the location of all the enemies?”

George shook his head and said, “I’ll be honest to the Junior Patriarch. I cannot guarantee that this complete. The enemy is very strong. Moreover, we discovered that the other party was very prepared to fight with the magic armors. I’m afraid of being entangled by them, so we didn’t dare to go too far for scouting. However, the general situation depicted here shouldn’t be wrong.”

Axe nodded, “It’s fine. There’s no need to worry about it. Right, how is their attacking power?”

George complied, he pointed at the map and said, “Junior Patriarch, the enemies on the other side of the spatial rift uses an inferior version of our energy cannons. It seems like they’re quite big and heavy, they aren’t easily movable. The attacking strength seems to be average, but there was a lot of them. At the same time, they also have a kind of explosive javelin. The explosion the javelins produce is stronger than the energy cannons. And the most difficult to deal with were the operators of these energy cannons and javelins. They were all used by the undead, and those undead are very strong.”

Axe frowned, “I didn’t expect the other party to use undead as cannoneers. Perhaps the undead are related with the Dark Mist? From what you can see, how many troops would we need in order to break through the enemy line?”

George thought about it and said, “I probably need 1000 energy cannons, 200 war tanks, and 1000 magic armors. If we have those numbers, maybe we can control the casualties to about 100.”

Axe moved his eyebrows and said, “Oh, you’re that confident?”

George nodded, “Although they’re defense is quite strong, I can see that they still fall short compared to the magic armors. More importantly, although the spatial rift wasn’t small, it wasn’t big either. We can’t send a lot of people at a time, but this also meant that the other party wouldn’t be able send a lot of troops to defend. So 1000 magic armors should be enough. We could use energy cannons as covering fire while the magic armors and the war tanks slowly push forward with their shields. We should be able to take control of the area in a short period of time. We can also establish our own defensive line in case the enemy sends reinforcements.”

Axe nodded, “Good. Go back and write a detailed plan for me. I will let the Generals see your plan and if it is feasible, we’ll have you lead the operation. After all, compared to any of us, you are the most familiar with the situation.”

Although George was a well-mannered person, he still couldn’t help but conceal the glee on his face upon hearing Axe. He quickly gave a salute and said, “George thanks the Junior Patriarch for the promotion!”

Axe patted George’s shoulder and said, “I promoted you because I can see that you’re competent. Alright, go and prepare. Remember to call me Young Lord from now on.”

George became even happier. One shouldn’t underestimate this name change. The address ‘Junior Patriarch’ can be used by everyone to address Axe. However, only a few people could call him by the name of Young Lord. Only those with good relations with the O’neal family, the older generations, and trusted subordinates were able to call Axe this name. Being able to address Axe this way was a sign of status. For George, this was an extremely good news.

George happily replied, “Yes, Young Lord, I will go prepare right away.” After he said that, he turned and left. Although he had already left Axe’s room, George was still very motivated. His family wasn’t powerful, so everything he achieved up to this day was due to his hard work. George was very familiar of the O’Neal family, judging by the fact that he had climbed his way up from being the lowest ranked soldier. He knew that for people like him with no background, he would need to rely on powerful people. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to go far in life.

Axe giving his favor was akin to George getting a powerful backer. What better backer was there other than the Junior Patriarch, the future leader of the O’Neal family? With the Junior Patriarch at his back, reaching his dream of being an official wouldn’t be that far off.

After looking at George’s departing back, Axe couldn’t’ help but smile faintly. After having a deep understanding about the family’s matters, Axe knew how important it was to train competent subordinates.

Yes, the family already had loyal and devoted elder officials. But because their qualifications were established long ago, it wasn’t certain that they would be by the Junior Patriarch’s side. With the pressure of these elder official, people like George would find it hard to go high up the ladder. So as long as Axe provided people like George with support, then they would be loyal and devoted to him. They would become Axe’s personal strength, something that belonged to his own.

These were matters that his father had taught him. Since his father was aware that Axe was coming here, he sent several young and capable men with no backgrounds along. These people had been pressured by old officials. Their statuses weren’t able to bring them to the rank of general. Because of this, Axe would find it easier to command them. At the same time, they would also do their best to curry favor with the Junior Patriarch.

Axe was very grateful for this procedure that his father had laid out. He knew that his father was already paving the road for him in order to smoothly transition into the position of Patriarch.

After thinking about this, Axe couldn’t help but lightly sigh. He turned and left to rest in his bedroom, the meal that the servant sent was left uneaten.

The next morning, just after Axe finished having his breakfast, a servant’s voice was heard, “Young Master, Captain George is asking for an audience.”

Axe nodded and said, “Let him in.” The servant complied as George walked in not long after.

Although George’s eyes were blood red, his facial expression shows that he was extremely motivated. After seeing Axe, George immediately bowed and said, “Young Lord, I’ve finished the battle plan. Please take a look at it.”

Axe looked at George and frowned, “George, have you been busy since yesterday evening? Didn’t I tell you to take a rest?”

After seeing Axe frown, George couldn’t help but stare and quickly replied, “Yes, I ask the Young Lord for forgiveness. I’m afraid of causing the Young Lord’s mission to make mistakes. So I worked overnight to finish the battle plan.”

Axe looked at George and sighed, “George, don’t do this in the future. The battle plan isn’t an immediately need. You need to take care of your body. The only thing you truly own is your body. You can contribute more in the future. When the time comes, I don’t want your body to be unwell if I need you.”

As soon as he heard this, George’s expression loosened. Then he gave a sharp bow and said, “Yes, Young Lord. This George thanks the Young Lord for the concern.”

Axe nodded and said, “Leave the plan behind. You go back and rest well. Come to me after. Go.” George nodded before he placed the plan on the table. Then he gave Axe a salute and left.

When George left, Axe took the battle plan and gave it a glance. After a while, a smile couldn’t help but appear on Axe’s face.

George’s battle plan was very good. It was very detailed and had considered a lot of aspects. The combat process was divided into several parts. The first part was the attack. The main goal was to break through the spatial rift’s defensive line.

The second part was seizing the defensive line. Upon doing so, they would be able make a counter-attack on the enemy.

The third part was exploiting their victory. After defending their ground, they would immediately send the energy cannons and war tanks in to attack the other party through the fog. This way, they would be able to see what lies behind.

It can be said that the plan was beautifully made. The first step was very clear and George even calculated how much people they would need. It included the estimated time it would take, their route of action, and reactions to certain levels of progress. If the enemy strongly resisted, then the battle plan would describe how to deal with it. All these things were carefully considered. Axe was very satisfied with the report.

Axe only gave George a small opportunity, but who would’ve thought that George would bring in such a huge surprise. Although this was only a battle plan, one could see a lot of things from it. With how well it was made, it showed the calibre of George’s skill. For Axe, this was very important.

Finding a thousand soldiers was easy, but looking for a good talent was very difficult. Those with talent are extremely crucial to any military. At this point, George became more valuable in Axe’s eyes.

Chapter 937: Superior and Subordinate

Zhao Hai was aware of the happenings in the O’Neal Family. But even if they had plans against him, he still didn’t care. After all, he was ready to deal with them. At this time, he was busy with the Sagittarius Continent. The battle was still going on, he didn’t have time to waste on anything else.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recognize how hard it was to deal with the Sagittarius Divines. Their main characteristic was their speed, they were very good at hit-and-run. They were doing guerilla warfare against Zhao Hai. This made it harder for Zhao Hai to deal with them.

At this time, Gold Ben and the others had entered the plane that belonged to the Winged Pegasus clan. Naturally, the Winged Pegasus were resisting hard. However, their strength simply couldn’t compare to Gold Ben and the other Supreme Elders.

The Winged Pegasus had prepared themselves, unlike the Thunder Clan who had been decimated by the Supreme Elders. However, they still weren’t able to pose a threat to Gold Ben and the others.

The resistance of the Winged Pegasus was much better compared to the Thunder Clan. It would be impossible for Gold Ben and the others to deal with the Winged Pegasus like the way they did with the Thunder Clan. Although the Supreme Elders were very strong inside their combat suits, they still couldn’t wear them for too long. Because of this, after attacking the Winged Pegasus for a while, they would immediately retreat. They would find a place to rest before attacking once more. In any case, with their extremely small number, they would be able to evade the eyes of the Winged Pegasus.

But one shouldn’t underestimate the method used by the Supreme Elders. They were very lethal. Even if the Winged Pegasus dispatched ten million people, the Supreme Elders could kill seven million of them before retreating.

It can be said that the situation of the nine Supreme Elders in the Winged Pegasus Clan was the same as Zhao Hai in the Sagittarius Continent. Both of them were being tied down.

One must know that the Winged Pegasus were very quick. Among the three clans, they had the most mobile troops. Because of this speed, as well as the blood lightning javelins that Zhao Hai gave them before, the Winged Pegasus were able to cause some problems to the Supreme Elders.

However, Zhao Hai finally had a method to deal with the Sagittarius Divines. The main reason why he wasn’t able to clean the Sagittarius Divines up was because he had yet to map the entire Sagittarius Continent. Because of this, Zhao Hai had a hard time finding the positions of the Sagittarius Divines.

But after several days, Zhao Hai finally mapped the entire continent. Because of this, he was now able to see where the Divines were hiding. Upon seeing the enemy, Zhao Hai would immediately release his undead to engage them in close combat.

One must know that although the Sagittarius were formidable in ranged combat, their close combat capabilities were inferior compared to most Divines. With this disadvantage, the undead were able to easily kill them off.

After Zhao Hai completely dealt with the Sagittarius Divines, Axe and the others had also finished resting and were now ready to attack the spatial rift. Axe decided to use George’s battle plan. However, it was a pity that the battle plan would have to be wasted. This was because Zhao Hai already withdrew all of his troops guarding the defensive line.

Axe stood in a place not far from the spatial rift. He looked calm but deep inside he was actually excited, and a faint trace of killing aura was starting to come out.

Right, killing aura. Axe’s heart was feeling more and more agitated. He felt that Zhao Hai was just behind the spatial rift. Therefore, this attack was like a head-on collision with Zhao Hai.

George was standing by Axe’s side. This was Axe’s request. Axe needed to tell everyone that George was his trusted aide, which made George very excited.

However, George still looked worriedly at the spatial rift. Although he was very confident in his battle plan, George still felt unease. After all, this was an opportunity for him to prove himself. If his battle plan went smoothly, then he would gain a stable footing inside Axe’s heart. But if it fails, then it was likely that Axe would give up on him. Without anyone backing him up, he wouldn’t be able to make something of himself.

Axe looked at the time. After seeing that it was appropriate, he looked at George and said, “George, pass the order to attack.”

George nodded. He took a deep breath before turning his head and loudly said, “Pass the Young Lord’s order, begin the attack!”

Axe looked satisfied at George. He rated George’s battle plan as very good, but Axe also knew that he was just a rookie commander. Therefore, he had the battle plan sent to the generals that came with him. He didn’t have the confidence to see if it was really good or not.

Very good, after looking at the plan, the Captains thought that it was perfect. This caused Axe to feel relieved. He had also paid more attention to George.

What made Axe feel more satisfied was George’s performance. George’s actions were quite good and well-measured. George could just say, “Pass the order, begin the attack!” Everyone would still be aware that it was Axe’s command. However, “Pass the Young Lord’s order, begin the attack!” sounded much better to Axe’s ears.

Axe was just a rookie commander, he still needed to increase his prestige. In fact, Axe had little to no help regarding the attack on the spatial rift. The battle plan was made by George while the operation was left to the captains. It can be said that the thing Axe did was just to issue the order to attack.

Axe hoped to increase his prestige using this attack. Because of this, he wished for people to know that he was the one in command.

After gaining experience, Axe knew that he wasn’t an average youth. Doing laborious tasks was not something he ought to do. He was a superior, and superiors wouldn’t be able to worry too much as long as his people were doing well. The battle plan was made by George, but George was found by him. This was already enough. With this action, he was already able to gain merit as a superior.

This was also something that his father had taught him. Before a superior gains influence, they would need to increase their prestige. Once your influence was unshakable, only then would you be able to relax.

At this point, Axe still needed to increase his influence. Because of this, Axe wouldn’t have liked it if George just said, “Pass the order, begin the attack!”. This would lessen Axe’s merit.

But since George said the right thing, pointing out that Axe was the commander. The subordinates would place Axe’s name in their minds. As long as the fight was won, Axe would gain a certain status inside the hearts of these subordinates. This was gaining prestige.

Because of this point, Axe was very satisfied with George. George was a thoughtful person, that’s why he decided to word his command properly.

George was an intelligent man. He was clear about Axe’s status in the O’Neal family. This young man, who used to be unpopular because of his risk-taking attitude, didn’t have a good reputation in the family. Fortunately, since he was the Patriarch’s first wife’s son, and had never wronged the family, his position as the Junior Patriarch was still quite solid.

However, the Junior Patriarch’s involvement with the Ark Continent made everyone startled. Although this was due to Axe’s risk-taking attitude, entering an unknown plane was still regarded as a courageous move by the family. Because of this, the members of the family began to see the Junior Patriarch in a new light. Moreover, the patriarch had started to make his move and train the Junior Patriarch and enhance Axe’s influence. So after thinking about it, George decided to word the order that way.

After the order was passed on, George turned to look at Axe. Axe had a faint smile on his face, he looked very satisfied. George couldn’t help but become happy, he knew that he did the right decision in addressing the Young Lord with the command.

With Axe’s order being passed on, the O’Neal family’s attack finally began. The first to move were the energy cannons. The energy cannons of the O’neal family were much bigger than the ones used by Zhao Hai. Naturally, these energy cannons had some differences. The energy cannons don’t fire beams, instead, they fire shells.

Naturally, with shells being the ammunition, the energy cannons were used differently compared to Zhao Hai’s magic cannons. The O’neal family’s cannons looked just like the ones on Earth. A lot of magic formations were inscribed on the shells. And instead of gunpowder, a magical powder was used. This magical powder had the same explosive property as gunpowder, however its might was much stronger, making them more lethal.

There were 1000 energy cannons in total. After Axe’s order, the magic cannons immediately made waves of attacks. Flames emitted from the cannons as it fired towards the spatial rift. After five rounds of firing, the cannons stopped. After that, the war tanks and magic armors, looking like ants and mosquitoes, threw themselves into the spatial rift.

Chapter 938: I’ll Certainly Find You!

Axe looked at the spatial rift. He didn’t know what the battle would be like, but one thing was for sure. The battlefield was an ever changing entity, nobody would know what would happen next. George’s plan might be very well made, but sometimes the unexpected would happen.

Axe didn’t participate in the battle. Although he had participated in battles during his explorations, he was still inexperienced when it came to large fights. Also, he didn’t join because he knew how anything can happen in the battlefield.

George was as nervous as Axe. If the attack didn’t go well, Axe wouldn’t be affected too much, he could just launch a second attack. However, for George, it would be a disaster, he would lose the trust that Axe had given him. For George who had no background, he might not even be able to keep his position of Captain.

Under the two’s gaze, the magic armors and war tanks rushed towards the spatial rift. Axe and George held their breath at the same time. It was only after some time did the two recover, but they still kept their eyes on the spatial rift.

One minute passed by and there weren’t any sounds of fighting from the spatial rift. Five minutes went by, there was still nothing. Ten minutes, half an hour, no sound could be heard.

Axe couldn’t help but turn to George and said, “George, go send someone to take a look. See what’s happening on the other side. Why aren’t there any noise? Are we carrying a silent attack?”

George nodded. But just as he was about to prepare, a black spot suddenly emerged from the spatial rift. It was a magic armor, George stopped and immediately went to protect Axe.

Axe looked at George’s action and nodded. However, his attention was still concentrated on the magic armor. He really wanted to know what happened to the spatial rift, why there was no sound.

Before long, the magic armor flew until it was 500 meters away from axe before it was stopped. Then the magic armor descended to the ground as its pilot went out. After confirming the pilot’s identity, the man was taken to see Axe.

Axe looked at the man, naturally he didn’t know him. The messenger arrived in front of Axe and then gave him a salute, “Reporting to the Junior Patriarch. Lion combat unit’s second squad messenger Bill is here on the Captain’s orders. I’m ordered to report the situation to the Junior Patriarch.”

Axe nodded, “Tell me what’s going on. Why can’t I hear any fighting?”

Bill immediately replied, “Reporting to the Junior Patriarch. There simply isn’t any fighting on the other side. We didn’t discover any enemies. We rushed through the fog and were surprised by what happened. The Captain is asking the Junior Patriarch to take a look and see the situation.”

Axe stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll take a look.”

George quickly replied, “Young Lord, please allow me to ask a few questions.”

Axe turned his head to George and smiled, “George, what do you want to ask? Go on.”

After George expressed his gratitude, he turned to Bill and said, “Bill, are there really no enemies, or have they been destroyed by us? Also, since you’re asking the Young Lord to head inside, is the situation absolutely safe?”

Bill immediately replied, “We were unable to defeat the enemy, there simply aren’t any. The terrain inside has been completely destroyed by the energy cannons, so we cannot take a look. But rest assured, the situation has been under complete control, it’s very safe.”

George nodded, then he turned to Axe and said, “Young Lord, I’ll arrange a modified Tiger War Tank to go with you.”

Axe gave a nod, “Alright, go prepare. Right, let’s go in together. I want to see what happened on the other side.”

George complied and immediately turned around and left. Before long, a modified Tiger war tank stopped beside Axe. George opened the door of the war tank and welcomed Axe in. After Axe and George was inside, the war tank immediately entered the spatial rift.

It didn’t take a long time before the war tank emerged from the other side of the spatial rift. Upon exiting, George couldn’t help but frown, then he whispered to Axe, “Young Lord, the fog is much lighter compared to before. Last time, we only have three meters of visibility, but this time it seems to be ten meters.”

Axe stared, then he turned to George and said, “Are you sure?”

George nodded, “I am absolutely sure, Young Lord. I entered this place several times. I have a good understanding of the situation here.”

Axe gently knit his brows and said, “Since the fog is disappearing, does it mean that the enemy has retreated? Did they discover our army so they decided to pull back?”

George gave a heavy nod and said, “Perhaps that is the case. I’ve been unfair to the Young Lord. My battle plan has wasted a lot of the O’Neal family’s shells.”

Axe smiled and said, “That doesn’t matter. We still managed to seize the area have we not? This cannot blamed on you. Your battle plan is perfect.”

George nodded. After a while, the war tank went through the mist. Axe and George stared as the scene appeared before them. It was a great plain, they could also see a mountain in the distance. There were trees here and there, the environment was very good.

In this plain were the magic cannons and war tanks. Naturally, these were the ones who were sent to attack. Axe calmed down after a while and looked at the plain with a smile on his face. His smile became wider and wider before it evolved into laughter.

George recovered the moment he heard Axe laugh. He also looked at the giant plain and understood why Axe laughed. Such a big land would naturally have a lot of resources, minerals, and population. If they manage to conquer this land, then the O’Neal family would become the Atlanta Plane’s top clan.

George quickly said, “Young Lord, congratulations. Compared to the Ark Cnotinent, this place seemed to be much bigger. The Young Lord has greatly contributed to the O’Neal family. Young Lord, you should tell the Patriarch about this as soon as possible.”

George opened the door as Axe jumped out of the war tank. At this time, they were approached by squad leaders as well as war tank commanders. They reported the situation to Axe. They haven’t run into any enemies, there was nothing noteworthy to report.

Axe looked at the surrounding place and nodded, “Inform the reserve troops and have them deliver the supplies immediately. Build a base here as soon as possible. And have scout troops look into the surrounding area.”

The captains immediately prepared everything. Axe excitedly looked at the land. He suddenly thought that his decision to enter the Ark Continent’s spatial rift was the most correct decision he had made in his entire life. His discovery of the Ark Continent was certainly due to his luck.

Although there was a dangerous region in the Ark Continent, the continent was abundant in resources. Discovering this new plane was a very good thing for the O’Neal family.

Before long, the follow-up team from the Ark Continent arrived and began to build a base. The scouts had also been sent out. Axe had also sent people to send word back to his father about the current situation.

After having arranged these things, Axe sat inside the war tank and looked at the busy people. He couldn’t help but feel uplifted. George was also standing right by Axe’s side. His heart was similarly moved. He knew what the discovery of this place meant for Axe. This meant that his status in the O’Neal family had become more stable. When the water rises, the boats rise as well. After thinking about this, George couldn’t help but feel excited.

After some time, Axe said, “George, you said that you met enemies here. Why didn’t they resist our entry this time?”

George, who was still daydreaming, woke up upon hearing the question. He frowned for a moment before he turned to Axe and said, “Young Lord, I think they must have noticed our reinforcements. They thought they couldn’t resist so they gave up on this place. They should be ready to deal with us on this continent. I think we need to be careful.”

Axe nodded, “That’s possible. Moreover, I suspect that this matter has something to do with that Zhao Hai I met before. Remind everyone to stay on guard. The enemy might not give us an opportunity to relax.” George nodded before he turned around and left.

Axe turned his head towards the Taurus Continent and said, “Zhao Hai, I know you’re in here. Wait for me, I will certainly find you. You’ll pay for deceiving me.”

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and smiled faintly, “Interesting. This fellow actually wanted to take revenge. Unfortunately, I cannot spare any time right now. I really wanted to play along.”

Laura smiled and said, “You don’t have to go there yourself. The undead are enough to deal with them. Right, Brother Hai, now that we have dealt with the Sagittarius Continent, where do we go next?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We’ll go to the Pisces Continent.”

Chapter 939: Laying it Out

Just as Zhao Hai prepared to attack the Pisces Continent, Fei’er and the others were also busy with something. They were sitting inside the Space with a small table in front of them. On the table were some cups as well as several side dishes.

Ding drank some liquor. He took a whiff of the cup and said, “Mister’s liquor is really tasty. Our Barbarian liquor isn’t as strong as this one.”

Fei’er also took a sip of the liquor as he smiled bitterly and said, “I don’t know why, but I feel that it’s quite bitter.”

Upon hearing Fei’er, Shan also smiled bitterly. He drank some liquor in order to forget the pain. Every Barbarian would be transported to the Space soon, they didn’t suffer any loss. On the other hand, the Winged Pegasus Clan were still yet to agree on something.

In the past few days, it can be said that Shan was the most busy. He helped the Barbarians move while at the same time returning to his room every night to wait for Speaker Fang.

However, the clan’s current situation wasn’t doing good. Nobody knows why, but the nine Supreme Elders weren’t attacking strongly. This gave hope to the clan. Some people who decided to enter the Space changed their mind after hearing about this.

At this time, there were less than 100 thousand Winged Pegasus households inside the Space. This was what Shan was most worried about. He didn’t believe that the Supreme Elders would let them off easily. The reasons why the Supreme Elders slowed their attack might be because, first, they wanted to exert pressure on Zhao Hai so that he would return. And second, they wanted to keep the Winged Pegasus’ hope, so that they would be able to eliminate them all when the time comes.

However, Shan was currently a criminal in the Winged Pegasus Clan. He simply didn’t dare to appear in public. But at the same time, Speaker Fang’s authority had been limited. Although he was a Council Speaker, his actual rallying strength wasn’t good.

Because of these reasons, most of the Winged Pegasus members weren’t willing to enter the Space. This was something Shan didn’t want to see the most. At this rate, then there would be more Thunder Clan members in the Space compared to the Winged Pegasus.

Ding looked at the two and sighed, “Brothers, we can only do what we can do right now, and leave everything else to fate. How about this, Shan, how about we talk to mister about this. It might be possible for Mister to come and help you. No matter what, we can’t have the Winged Pegasus be eliminated by the nine Supreme Elders.

Shan smiled bitterly and said, “I want to contact Mister, but I think he is also having a hard time. Moreover, with the performance of my clan, will Mister still help us?”

Just as Shan said that, Zhao Hai’s voice suddenly came, “How will you know if you don’t try?”

The three stared before they turned to see Zhao Hai. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Fei’er immediately said, “Mister, you’re back? How come you’re here?”

Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled, “I’ve heard of your current situation so I came back. I’m still preparing to deal with the Pisces Continent. But do you really need me here?”

Shan quickly knelt down and said, “Mister, I ask you to please rescue my people. Although they have wronged you, I still ask Mister to help them.” Then he proceeded to kowtow to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, making Shan get up, then he said, “I’m aware of what’s happening to your clan. However, even if I go and help, it’s not necessary that they would accept it. Moreover, I’ll tell you that I already have plans to deal with the Pisces Continent. At the same time, the foreign races have sent their troops to the Leo Continent. When they arrive at the Leo Continent and occupy it, then the Supreme Elders might retreat.”

Fei’er and the others looked puzzled at Zhao Hai. Why would the Supreme Elders retreat? They already reached this point, so why would they give it up?”

After seeing the expression on their faces, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If I deal with the Divines, then the Divines would want to deal with me. But if the foreign races are added to the equation, then things would become different. When the foreign races come, then the Supreme Elders might change their target and deal with the foreign races instead.”

Fei’er and the others nodded. However, they also knew that this was just a possibility, this wasn’t for certain. Although the hatred between the Divines and the Foreign Races was quite large, the hatred between Zhao Hai and the Divines weren’t small as well. It was still not certain that the Supreme Elders would shift their targets to the foreign races.

Also, the current Winged Pegasus Clan had some hatred for Zhao Hai. Even if Zhao Hai wanted to help the Winged Pegasus, it might be possible that the Winged Pegasus would not let him.

Shan didn’t know what to do in this situation. He was clear that the outcome wouldn’t be good, but he had no way of persuading the Patriarch. This caused him to feel extremely uncomfortable. At this point, he was really hoping that the Supreme Elders would change their target, just like Zhao Hai said.

Zhao Hai sat in front of the small table and took his own cup out before pouring himself some liquor. Then he looked at the three people and said, “Sit down. Let me tell you something.”

The three began to sit down and looked at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai looked at the three and began talking, “Presently, the defensive line in the Taurus Continent has fallen to the enemy. The O’Neal family’s magic armors have arrived. I’m organizing some undead to drag them down. Therefore, Ding, you need to transfer all of your people to the Space soon.”

Ding nodded. He had seen the attacking power of the O’Neal family’s magic armor. To be honest, he didn’t have the confidence to block them.

Then Zhao Hai said, “Also, there’s something else. I’m close to ascending.”

As soon as the three heard Zhao Hai say this, their expression immediately changed. No matter which race, all of them had legends about ascension. The Divines especially had plenty of ascension stories. Because of this, when the three heard Zhao Hai state that he was close to ascending, they couldn’t help but get startled. However, their thoughts quickly changed. If there was someone in the Divine Realm who had the qualification to ascend, then that would be Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and said, “The Divines have a Deity. He’s a person from the Cultivation Realm and is the one in charge of our planes. He uses the Divines in order to collect something called Faith Power. Although I don’t know what this Faith Power is, but it seems to be very important to them, they really wanted it. But this Deity has been defeated by me twice. And with how I am currently dealing with the Divines, it can be said that I have some enmity with this Deity.”

The three listened carefully to Zhao Hai’s words. This was the first time that they’ve heard of this, and they were very surprised. Zhao Hai looked at them and continued, “The reason why I made the three clans enter the Space was because I want to take you with me when I ascend. This way, you won’t be under the control of the Deity any longer. Your relationship with me, being my ally, it’s the same as offending that Deity. In that case, will he let you off when I’m gone? When the time comes, your clans could only be exterminated.”

The bodies of Fei’er and the others shook. Their expressions greatly changed. Naturally, they thought of the horror of the situation. Zhao Hai then went on to say, “I know that you’ve already discovered by this time that I’ve been using the Supreme Elders in order to force the three clans into the Space. But I had no choice. If I told you this before, then you wouldn’t have believed if. And even if you did, your people won’t.”

The three smiled bitterly. They had thought about this point before. Ever since they had entered the Space, they came to understand that if Zhao Hai wanted to help them deal with the Supreme Elders, then he certainly had the ability to do so. However, Zhao Hai actually didn’t do it. It seems like Zhao Hai was using the Supreme Elders to compel the three clans to move to the Space.

But even if they had thought about this, they still trusted Zhao Hai and didn’t say anything. In their opinion, Zhao Hai’s Space had better conditions compared to their own planes. Entering the Space wouldn’t be bad for their clan. They just didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would have an extraordinary reason.

Zhao Hai looked at the three people and smiled bitterly, “I do indeed have the ability to deal with the nine Supreme Elders. However, I won’t dare to make a move. I discovered that the plane has started to repel me. If I fight with my full strength, then I would be thrown out even if I managed to defeat the Supreme Elders. I would then be leaving the three clans behind.”

After speaking up to here, Zhao Hai sighed and said, “If you stay in this place, then your three clans can only wait to be destroyed. You’ve seen how strong my Hell King’s ship is. The Divine Race’s Deity has a lot of those weapons. As long as the Divines get their hands on a weapon like the Hell King’s ship, then dealing with you would be very easy. Because of this, I didn’t dare to make a move. I can only avoid the nine Supreme Elders. I can’t risk ascending and leaving you here.”

Fei’er and the others looked at one another. They believed Zhao Hai’s words. When they first met Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai didn’t have the Hell King’s ship. If Zhao Hai had the Hell King’s ship, then he wouldn’t have needed to fear the Divines and the Demons. The Hell King’s ship was simply an item that goes against the heavens’ will.

Ding stood up and bowed, “This Ding pledges to Mister. Starting today, the Barbarians will treat mister as a deity. This Ding is ashamed for doubting mister.”

Fei’er and Shan did the same. The two stood up and gave Zhao Hai a bow, feeling shame. They suspected Zhao Hai before, but now that Zhao Hai laid everything into the table, they couldn’t help but feel embarrassed.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Alright, I’ve made mistakes as well. If I haven’t dealt with the Divine Race’s Deity then this wouldn’t have happened. Also, you’re free to do whatever you want. Worship me as a deity or not, I don’t really care. You can believe in whoever and whatever you want, I won’t stop you.”

Fei’er and the others sat back down before Zhao Hai continued, “The Taurus Divines have used a formation in order to change the laws of the Ark Continent. This caused the barrier of the Ark Continent to collapse. The O’Neal family is from the Atlanta Plane. Originally, there was one continent in the Atlanta Place. But later on, because of a massive war, the continent was divided into three. The three continents are different from one another. One continent practices martial arts, this continent is known as the Warrior Continent. Another continent specializes in magic, it’s called the Mage Continent. And the last continent uses things like magic armors, it’s called the Magic Armor Continent. The O’neal family is just a big family in this continent. And I suspect that the Atlanta Plane isn’t managed by the Divine Race’s Deity.”

The three looked puzzled at Zhao Hai as Fei’er said, “Why does mister think so?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I think there’s a reason for this. You must have heard about the Goblin Race. They were destroyed by the Divines and turned into slaves. They were living in peace along with the Divines, but why were they suddenly destroyed?”

The three looked at each other, they haven’t thought about it before. They just thought that it was due to the ambition of the Divines. But now that Zhao Hai said something, it seems like there were some underlying facts.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and said, “The Divine Race’s destruction of Goblin Race was due to the command of their Deity. It was because the Goblins have developed magic armors.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Fei’er stared. He had seen one of these Goblin constructs before. These Goblin magic armors couldn’t even be compared to the strong ones used by the O’Neal family. So why would the Divines choose to destroy the Goblins?

Zhao Hai turned to Fei’er and said, “The problem lies here. This is where my suspicion comes from. The Goblins had just started researching magic formations and magic armors, yet they were already decimated by the Divine Race’s Deity. Meanwhile, the Atlanta Plane’s magic armors have reached an extremely high level, but the Deity just let them off. Isn’t this strange? Because of this, I suspect that the Atlanta Plane isn’t in control of the Deity. It was only because of the Ark Continent that the two planes became connected. If this was the case, then does the Atlanta Plane have another Deity managing it? If there was, then what would happen if he discovers the Ark Continent. If both sides get into conflict, then what consequences would there be?”

With Zhao Hai laying out the facts, the expression on Fei’er and the others’ faces continually changed.

Chapter 940: The O’Neal Family’s Worry

To be honest, Fei’er and the others haven’t thought about this before. They were too small for matters like these. What were these people? They were Deities, the managers of planes. Compared to the Divines Race’s Supreme Elders, these people were much more powerful.

However, the one thing they could understand was that the moment these two existences fought, small people like them would surely be affected. What would happen if these two deities fight and take their treasures out to deal a fatal blow? It would be impossible for small people to survive such an impact. Moreover, in the eyes of these two people, those on the lower planes were merely tools used to gather Faith Power.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and sighed, “Presently in the Ark Continent, besides the O’Neal family, the underworld’s undead and magic beasts are also present. The undead and magic beasts are currently hiding inside the poisonous Dark Mist. If we go in, not only would we get poisoned, we would be assaulted by the underworld’s creatures as well. Among these creatures are beings with spiritual wisdom, much like humans. At this time, the Underworld had seized the Aksu Empire and it will slowly swallow the entire Ark Continent. After that, the Dark Mist would surely enter the spatial rifts and enter the Divine Realm. When that time comes, the Divines wouldn’t be able to stop them, much less you.”

After speaking up to here, Zhao Hai let out a long breath and said, “Because of these reasons, I have to use some methods in order to compel you to enter the Space. At the very least, I would be able to provide you with absolute safety. You can live here with relief, nobody will come to attack you. You won’t need to worry about having something to eat.”

Zhao Hai continued, “I can help you block the nine Supreme Elders, but I cannot use my full strength. I could only entangle the Supreme Elders, but this will just waste even more time. Most importantly, I cannot stay in this plane for too long. If I couldn’t send you to the Space as soon as possible, then I would risk leaving you behind when I ascend. Because of this, I can only resort to this terrible plan. Although your clans would suffer serious losses, you won’t be exterminated at the very least. You’re clan could still continue and develop slowly.”

After speaking up to here, Zhao Hai looked at the three people’s eyes and said, “I don’t care about what you might think right now. You may hate me or blame me, I only did what I think is correct.”

Fei’er and the others stayed silent. They understood what Zhao Hai meant. However, even after hearing the truth from Zhao Hai, the three still couldn’t blame him. Fei’er shook his head and said, “Mister, we won’t be unfair to you. You have tried your best, the ones to be blamed should be us.” Ding and Shan nodded in agreement.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “How are you planning to deal with the Winged Pegasus now? Have you figured out a way?”

Shan frowned and replied, “Mister, the clan’s situation is already out of my control. The Patriarch accused me of trying to assassinate him, ordering the entire clan for my arrest. Because of this, the clan became in opposition to mister. Moreover, the nine Supreme Elders weren’t showing their fierce sides. This caused the clan to keep their hopes up, those who initially wanted to move to the Space changed their minds. Speaker Fang is also trying to convince our clansmen, but the result isn’t ideal.”

Zhao Hai gently knit his brows. It can be said that dealing with this ally was more difficult than dealing with an enemy. For his enemies, Zhao Hai could just dispatch his troops and throw them to the Space. But to an ally, this wouldn’t be a good idea.

Ding said, “The Barbarian Patriarch will enter the Space in about two days. He said that he would try to persuade the Winged Pegasus Patriarch in hopes that he would enter the Space.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “I’m afraid that this wouldn’t be easy, it may not succeed. But go on and still try it. I don’t much time to take care of your affairs recently, I can only leave this matter to you. Let’s just hope that the Supreme Elders would shift their target to the foreign races. Otherwise, the situation would become more dangerous.”

Shan and the others had a heavy heart. In this case, they had less methods to use. Even if Zhao Hai was willing to help them, things still wouldn’t be positive. After all, Zhao Hai can’t just forcefully take the Winged Pegasus Clan and throw them to the Space.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and then said, “Alright, I already told you what you need to know. I must go back and prepare to deal with the Pisces Divines so I won’t be staying here for long. You need to be careful. And Shan, you need to find a solution as soon as possible.”

Shan nodded. Then Zhao Hai’s figure flashed before disappearing. After Zhao Hai left, Shan turned his head to Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, do you think that what mister said was real?”

Fei’er nodded and said, “It should be at least 80% true. You had seen the O’Neal family. The Divine Race had ruled the Divine Realm for a long time. If they really allowed the study on magic formations, then they surely would have magic armors no lesser in ability compared to the O’Neal family. But after such a long time, did the Divine Race’s magic formation change even a little bit? Because of this, I believe that mister was telling the truth. Just like mister said, if our three clans don’t enter the Space, then sooner or later we would be eliminated.”

Shan and Ding nodded. They agreed with Fei’er’s words. Given Zhao Hai’s strength, if it wasn’t for their relationship, then Zhao Hai would just completely ignore them. They believed that Zhao Hai didn’t lack people. The three suspected that the Ark Continent’s people, the Demons, and even the Taurus Divines were also inside the Space. Zhao Hai wouldn’t have any losses if he leaves the three clans behind. This also made Shan worry. Zhao Hai had shown them the future, but his clansmen still weren’t moving. This caused Shan to be at a difficult position.

Zhao Hai emerged inside the Hell King’s ship upon exiting the Space. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Laura said, “Brother Hai, why did you suddenly decide to tell Fei’er and the others everything?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They already had suspicions, so I might as well tell them the truth. In any case, they are already inside the Space. If they wanted to leave then that won’t be a problem. If they decide to leave, then nobody could blame me for what happens to them.”

Laura nodded, she also knew that what Zhao Hai said was true. Zhao Hai agreed to move the three clans to the Space because of the current situation. It can be said that the three clans moving to the Space would offer no immediate advantage to Zhao Hai. They would only provide Faith Power in the far off future.

Lizzy looked at the monitor, it was currently showing the situation with the spatial rift. She turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, now that the O’Neal family has entered the rift, how do you plan to deal with them? Will you try to direct them towards the Winged Pegasus clan?”

Zhao Hai slightly smiled and said, “Right, let’s just lead them over. Let’s see how strong the magic armors really are. There are God-rank magic armors in the O’Neal family. I want to see how formidable those are.”

Lizzy nodded and said, “What about now? Do we attack their base? Stop them from building it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Just let them build it. The O’Neal family isn’t doing very well. We will to deal with the Pisces Divines first.”

Zhao Hai’s words weren’t cursing the O’Neal family. The O’Neal family really weren’t having a great time. The O’Neal Patriarch was currently sitting inside his study, a letter in front of him. The letter was written by those in the northern defensive line.

They had made the proper arrangements for the northern defensive line, even sending strong energy cannons. But in the letter, the general in charge of the north reported that the energy cannons were doing a poor job in holding the dark mist back. Even if they used all of their firepower, the dark mist was still expanding, it wasn’t showing any intention to stop. To say it bluntly, all of their previous efforts were useless.

This was the most worrying thing for the O’neal family. If the northern army couldn’t defend, then what could they do? The expansion of the Dark Mist was almost constant, it wouldn’t reduce its speed for anything. It wasn’t that fast, but it couldn’t be said to be slow either.

If the Dark Mist continued expanding at this speed, then in a few months it would prove to be a threat to the O’Neal family. This caused the Patriarch to have a headache.

At this time, footsteps were suddenly heard. Then a servant’s voice was heard, “Patriarch, the Junior Patriarch has sent word.”

When the Patriarch heard his servant, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment before his expression changed as he said, “Give it here, quick.” The servant complied immediately and opened the door to enter and deliver the letter to the Patriarch.

The Patriarch looked at the letter, then he broke the seal before opening it. He thought that Axe had suffered setbacks in the attack and was asking for reinforcements. But after reading the letter, the Patriarch’s expression couldn’t help but light up. He placed the letter down on the table and laughed.

The letter’s arrival was too timely. There’s no need to worry about the northern defensive line now. This letter happened to give them a way out.

At this point, the Patriarch believed that Axe was the O’Neal family’s good fortune. Not only did he discover the Ark Continent, he even found a new plane.

Chapter 941: Skeleton King!

Lewis looked at the Dark Mist. He was the northern army’s first squad commander. Because of this, he remained behind. Moreover, he was continuously entrusted with heavy responsibilities.

Lewis was clearly aware about how much importance the clan attached to the northern defensive line. Moreover, he also understood the present situation. The methods the Clan prepared to deal with the Dark Mist were simply useless. The Dark Mist was still expanding. For the family, this was a great trial. If they don’t do well, then the family would suffer a loss.

But there was no other method for Lewis. The innate Yin domain appearing here was strange in itself. The fact that it was also expanding made it even more mystical.

Lewis was constantly worried. However, today, he was feeling extra worried, and he didn’t know why. He seemed to have an apprehensive feeling.

Lewis was very convinced of this feeling. This ability wasn’t born with him, but instead he acquired it after suffering a serious injury. This intuition was very strange, but it was real. And this feeling has helped Lewis several times. After he became a war tank driver, he managed to avoid several dangers by relying on his intuition.

And now, the danger he felt was unprecedented. This caused Lewis to feel fear and apprehension. The people who were with Lewis couldn’t help but feel strange, this was because Lewis looked very anxious this particular day.

Lewis couldn’t explain his feeling to them. Even if he did, the others wouldn’t necessarily believe in him. Because of this, Lewis can only prepare to deal with the emergency the moment it happened.

Although the sun was hanging high up in the sky, making it the hottest time of the day, Lewis still felt a wave of chills. He would have a cold sweat from time to time.

Suddenly, the Dark Mist in front of them tumbled. Lewis became even more anxious. But the strange thing was his heart beginning to calm down. He knew that his intuition was acting up again, something was about to happen.

Lewis didn’t think too much, he didn’t want to wait until something happened. He immediately turned his war tank around and began to run away as fast as possible.

Lewis’ action made the people around him feel strange. The person who opened his mouth to talk to Lewis was Theo. Theo looked at Lewis strangely and asked, “Big Brother Lewis, what’s wrong? Why are we retreating? Shouldn’t we stay to observe the Dark Mist?”

Lewis shook his head and said, “It’s not good, the place has become dangerous.”

Just as Lewis said that, a magic armor pilot suddenly called out in alarm. Lewis and Theo quickly looked at the war tank’s rear view mirror. What they saw made them turn blank.

Flying out from the dark mist was a group of people. Or it could be said to be a group of undead. Most of these undead were golden yellow, they looked like they were cast from gold.

The golden yellow skeletons were riding similarly golden yellow magic beasts. In their hands were golden yellow weapons that seemed to have extraordinary might.

In the middle of these undead was another group of crystal skeletons. The appearance of these skeletons was just like the golden yellow undead but they looked much more advanced.

And in the very middle of these crystal undead was a carriage. It was a very unusual carriage as it was made out of bones. Pieces of crystal bones made up the pieces of the carriage, and it was pulled by four crystal undead magic beasts.

Inside this carriage was an undead. However, this undead was different from the others. This undead was wearing full body armor!

Correct, it was a full body armor. It was a radiant, golden armor. It seemed to be made out of gold but if you look closely it was made the same way as the carriage. The armor was made out of small pieces of bone, all connected to form this golden crystal bone body armor.

At the same time, the helmet, shoulder, elbow, and knee armors were all made out of golden skulls. Not only did it look defensive, it looked terrifying as well.

The helmet itself looked very special. It was made with a golden ox-head. Its horns pointed to the skies, looking extremely domineering.

On the back of the undead was a cape. However, the cape didn’t look very neat, it looked like it was worn for a very long time. But although it was ripped and fragmented, the cape didn’t make the undead look inferior. Conversely, the cape increased morbid feeling one would feel upon gazing at the undead.

There was a visor on the helmet, but at this time, it was opened. As the undead sat there, its two golden eyes were burning, giving people a huge sense of pressure.

The undead just sat quietly inside his bone carriage. His body was motionless but his aura announces a presence of a king. The king of all skeletons.

When Lewis saw these undead, he couldn’t help but violently shake. His expression changed for the worse as he sped up even more towards the southern part of the Aksu Empire.

It didn’t take too long before the undead discovered them. A squad of golden skeletons immediately charged. Lewis opened the war tank’s doors as Theo and other people entered their magic armors and shot towards the sky.

Lewis paid extreme attention to the current matter. He told Theo and the others to not stray away from the war tank. The nearer they were to the war tank, the easier would it be for the war tank to provide support. If they were far, then they risk getting into a dangerous situation.

Theo and the others have experienced actual comboat, so they were quite aware of what to do during battles. They didn’t fight the undead head on. Instead, they used their magic armors to fire energy beams towards the enemy.

But much to the surprise of Theo’s group, the undead were very agile. They were able to dodge the energy beams as they continued to rush towards the magic armors.

Theo and the others stared before they became shocked. They didn’t think that the undead would be this agile. Moreover, they were quite fast. The magic armors that they were proud of actually couldn’t escape the undead’s pursuit.

Theo and the others immediately launched bombs. After a loud explosion, the undead came out. They were basically uninjured, causing Theo to be startled once more.

At this moment, several energy beams hit the undead. The golden undead shook fiercely before the fell.

Theo and the others stared before they looked at the direction where the energy beams came from. The group couldn’t help but turn red as they immediately began to lure the undead around.

But at the same time, the undead also noted the war tank on the ground. Ten undead immediately rushed towards the war tank. Lewis wildly drove the war tank around to get away from the undead while also firing energy beams.

However, not everyone manage to notice that the undead who fell to the ground didn’t actually die. Instead, the fires in their eyes just became faint. But when they fell to the ground, spatial rifts suddenly opened, taking them all in. Once the undead entered the spatial rift, the rift would also disappear.

Although not everyone manage to notice this, the Skeleton King did. Upon seeing his golden skeletons vanish, he seemed to stare. Then he stood up and slowly went towards the carriage door. A crystal undead quickly opened the door for him.

The Skeleton King stepped out of his carriage and descended as though he was walking down a staircase. Every undead stopped in place, aside from those who were fighting Theo’s group.

Before long the Skeleton King reached the ground. He arrived at a place where a golden skeleton vanished. He carefully examined the ground, only to find nothing special there. Even a hint of energy was absent from the area.

At this time, a spatial rift suddenly opened while a person walked out of it. The Skeleton just looked at the person that appeared before him. He didn’t make a move.

This person was wearing a black magic robe. In his hand was a blood red crystal skeleton staff. He had a smiling expression on his face. There was no need to say about he man’s status, he was a Dark Mage.

This person was Zhao Hai. When the skeletons went out of the Dark Mist, Cai’er immediately informed him. Because of this, Zhao Hai paid attention to the scene. After seeing the golden skeletons falling to the ground, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but absorb them into the Space. Although the Space issued some prompts, it was actually very short. It just identified them as robots and improved the defensive abilities of the Space’s undead.

But when he saw the Skeleton King’s movements, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get curious. Because of this, he decided to personally meet the Skeleton King.

While the Skeleton King was sizing up Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai was also observing the Skeleton King. To be honest, this was the first time that Zhao Hai had seen an undead as eye-catching as this one. At this moment, the Skeleton King sent a spiritual wave towards Zhao Hai. This wasn’t an attack, but instead a means to communicate.

Zhao Hai had also experienced a similar situation before, so he wasn’t startled as he sent a similar spiritual wave to meet the other party. Upon contact, Zhao Hai suddenly felt an ancient but domineering voice inside his mind, “Who are you? Are you the one who took my subordinates?”